you know who drank is Churchill that's
می دانی که چرچیل کی نوشیده است، این
my whole that's my guy yeah you know
تمام من است،
that's my guy right so he uh he did
پسر من است، آره می دانی که آن مرد من است، پس
so his daily routine was a big breakfast
او شامپاین می خورد، لازم نیست چیزی در مورد وینستون چرچیل به من بگویید.  یک صبحانه بزرگ
cigar coffee eggs honey Side Up toast
سیگار برگ قهوه تخم مرغ عسل سمت بالا نان تست بیکن سوسیس
bacon sausage tomato beans uh fruit
لوبیا گوجه فرنگی اوه میوه
orange juice soft Scotch cigar in bed
پرتقال آب پرتقال سیگار نرم اسکاتلندی در رختخواب بود و
and he'd sit there for three hours and
او سه ساعت آنجا می نشست و
then he get in the bathtub and drink
سپس در وان حمام می رفت و
champagne and then he'd go to lunch and
شامپاین می خورد و بعد می رفت  ناهار و
have some goose with more champagne and
مقداری غاز با شامپاین بیشتر می خورد و
then he'd take a nap and like I love
بعد چرت می زد و دوست دارم
that so every year on hit the day of his
که هر سال در روز
death I think it's January 24th I
مرگش، فکر می کنم 24 ژانویه است،
celebrate Winston Churchill's Life by
زندگی وینستون چرچیل را با
living the way he did and so I have
زندگی کردن به روشی که او انجام می داد جشن می گیرم.
breakfast in bed with a soft scotch and
صبحانه را در رختخواب با یک اسکاچ نرم بخورم و
I just party all day that would be the
من فقط در تمام روز مهمانی می‌کنم که
guy to drink with
مردی که می‌نوشد با
the following is a conversation with
موارد زیر مکالمه با
bird Chrysler a stand-up comedian
پرنده کرایسلر،
podcaster actor and a man they call the
بازیگر پادکست کمدین استندآپ و مردی است که به آنها می‌گویند
machine
دستگاه
I've been a fan of his comedy and
من طرفدار آن بوده‌ام.  از کمدی ها و
podcasts for many years and I highly
پادکست های او برای چندین سال و من به شدت
recommend you watch him on broadcast to
توصیه می کنم او را در پخش در
Bears one cave with Tom Segura his
غار خرس ها با تام سگورا تماشا کنید.
this is the Lex Friedman podcast to
پادکست فریدمن برای
support it please check out our sponsors
حمایت از آن لطفاً حامیان ما را
in the description and now dear friends
در توضیحات بررسی کنید و حالا دوستان عزیز
here's Bert Kreischer
اینجاست برت کریشر
I read somewhere that you like Ernest
من در جایی خواندم که دوست دارید ارنست
Hemingway love him there's a quote
همینگوی او را دوست داشته باشید.  موافقم موافقم موافقم
you agree with that I agree I agree well
خوب
I agree with that with journaling
موافقم با ژورنالینگ موافقم
because I can't write um
چون نمیتوانم بنویسم
I can't write stand up like I can't
نمیتوانم بنویسم مثل اینکه نمیتوانم
write a bit but if I Journal I'll find
کمی بنویسم اما اگر روزنامه نگاری کنم چیزی پیدا می کنم
something that I go just right
که درست پیش بروم
kind of writing where your the pen is
نوعی نوشتن که در آن قلم شما
moving faster than your brain and
سریعتر از مغز شما حرکت می کند و
they're kind of like doing it together
آنها به نوعی دوست دارند این کار را با هم انجام دهند،
the thing I liked about Ernest Hemingway
کاری که من در مورد ارنست همینگوی دوست داشتم،
this is so stupid
این خیلی احمقانه است،
I'm a little dyslexic and so I'm not a
من کمی نارساخوان هستم و بنابراین من
good reader and so he wrote very simply
خواننده خوبی نیستم و  بنابراین او خیلی ساده نوشت
and it wasn't until after I read a bunch
و بعد از اینکه من یکسری
of Ernest Hemingway I was working in
از ارنست همینگوی را خواندم در
Barnes and Noble and this person said
بارنز و نوبل کار می کردم و این شخص گفت آیا
don't you love his titles and I was like
عناوین او را دوست ندارید و من مثل این بودم که
yeah Sun Also Rises and they're like
بله خورشید نیز طلوع می کند و آنها مانند
yeah but Now The Sun Also Rises and I
بله، اما اکنون خورشید نیز طلوع می کند و من
was like yeah it's almost Rises and I'm
انگار آره تقریباً طلوع می کند و من
like no this no the Sun Also arises and
مثل این هستم که نه، نه، خورشید نیز طلوع می کند و
I went
من رفتم
oh
آه، بله،
yeah that is [\h__\h] badass yeah and
این خیلی بد است، بله، و
then I'm like always late to the party
بعد من مثل همیشه
with anything and then that night we
با هر چیزی به مهمانی دیر می رسم  و سپس آن شب
were all doing coke and uh it was like
همه در حال مصرف کوکاکولا بودیم و ساعت
five in the morning and we ended up on
پنج صبح بود و به
the roof of my apartment in Greenwich
پشت بام آپارتمان من در روستای گرینویچ رسیدیم.
in Florida but sunrises in New York are
یورک
electric blue like electric blue
آبی برقی مثل آبی برقی است
and I was like
و من مثل
The Sun Also Rises
The Sun Also Rises
yeah he was so good
بله او خیلی خوب بود فقط
with just a handful of words the
با چند کلمه.
sober yeah but he was good at like at
اما او در
a small amount of words to to get a
تعداد کمی از کلمات برای رسیدن به یک
point across I'm the exact [\h__\h]
نکته خوب بود.
the best one I have he goes downhill
بهترین موردی که من دارم او از آنجا به سمت پایین می رود
from there so for you editing is
بنابراین برای شما ویرایش
destroying the original the first time I
نسخه اصلی را از بین می برد اولین بار که
tell the first time I tell it it's
اولین بار می گویم
perfect
عالی است
it's perfect it just it works and then I
عالی است فقط کار می کند و بعد
go great and then I take it and I try to
عالی می روم و سپس آن را می گیرم و سعی می کنم  برای
fix it and make it better and jazzier I
درست کردنش و بهتر و جازیتر کردنش
just joke and Razzle Dazzle about my
فقط شوخی می کنم و Razzle Dazzle در مورد
daughters and I driving past the deaf
دخترانم و با رانندگی از کنار
child's line
خط کودک ناشنوا می گذرم
and uh I just told it on stage it just
و اوه من فقط روی صحنه گفتم که این
happened and Louie was in the audience
اتفاق افتاده است و لویی در بین تماشاگران بود
because I love that joke I said really
زیرا من آن شوخی را که گفتم دوست دارم.  واقعاً
he goes yeah and I just told it and I
او می‌رود بله و من فقط آن را گفتم و تمام کردم
went done Louis CK says he likes a joke
لوئیس سی‌کی می‌گوید که او یک شوخی را دوست دارد، لعنتی است، این
it's [\h__\h] it's in the special
در ویژه است
and I tried to [\h__\h] Razzle Dazzle
و من سعی کردم به لعنتی Razzle Dazzle
that joke into like a 15 minute bit it
آن شوخی را مانند یک بیت 15 دقیقه‌ای انجام دهم، کار
got to the point where it was so
به جایی رسید که آنقدر بود  خیلی
obnoxious it was so bad that I I told
بد بود که
him I I did a podcast with him I said
بهش گفتم باهاش ​​پادکست زدم گفتم
what did you like about that joke
از اون جوک چی خوشت اومد
because I can't get it to work anymore
چون دیگه نمیتونم کارش کنم
because it was just simple it was simple
چون خیلی ساده بود خیلی ساده بود
that your daughter didn't know how
که دخترت نمیدونست چطوری
they'd figure out where deaf kids lived
آنها متوجه می شدند که بچه های ناشنوا کجا زندگی می کنند،
oh that's it
اوه،
he's like yeah I was like nothing about
او مثل اینکه بله، من در مورد
gun control and he was like huh I was
کنترل اسلحه چیزی نداشتم و او مثل او بود، من
like oh [\h__\h] man I really [\h__\h] that
مثل اوه لعنتی بودم، من واقعا آن
joke up and then I had to I had to go
شوخی را به هم زدم و بعد مجبور شدم
back to the beginning of it but that
به آن برگردم.  شروع آن اما
first time
اولین بار در آن زمان است
that's when that's when the joke comes
که شوخی
out purest for me and then it's always
برای من ناب ترین ظاهر می شود و سپس همیشه در حال
chasing back to get that get that first
تعقیب است تا به این نتیجه برسم که اولاً
telling some jokes are different like
گفتن برخی جوک ها متفاوت است ، مانند
the machine obviously was a much longer
ماشین ظاهراً یک داستان بسیار طولانی تر بود
story and like in like escape room for
و مانند فرار  اتاق برای
this one the longer stories take a
این داستان، داستان‌های طولانی‌تر
little work but the the simple ones
کمی کار می‌برند، اما داستان‌های ساده‌ای
like like the deaf child in pajamas and
مانند کودک ناشنوا با لباس خواب و
those first times are perfect what do
اولین بارها عالی هستند، به
you think is it
نظر شما
is it about the machine story that works
داستان ماشینی است
that was so uh captivating for people
که برای مردم بسیار جذاب بود.  فکر می‌کنم
I think it's a I think I don't know I
این یک داستان است، فکر می‌کنم نمی‌دانم،
really wish I I don't know I think it's
واقعاً کاش نمی‌دانستم، فکر می‌کنم
a good story I think it's a good story I
داستان خوبی است، فکر می‌کنم داستان خوبی است،
think everyone has something similar
فکر می‌کنم همه چیز مشابهی
that happened in their life where they
در زندگی‌شان داشته‌اند که در
had a crazy night and that no one
آن شب دیوانه‌واری را سپری کرده‌اند.  هیچ کس
believed and they told their friends and
باور نکرد و آنها به دوستان خود و
their friend and and or they experienced
دوست خود گفتند و و یا آنها
that with a friend like that and and
آن را با دوستی مانند آن تجربه کردند و و
I think
فکر می کنم فکر می کنم این باید باشد.
think there's a part of the like our
مانند
community of Comedy fans that were that
انجمن طرفداران کمدی ما که همان
early death squad that was fun to watch
جوخه مرگ زودهنگام بودند که تماشای
someone take something from the podcast
کسی که چیزی را از پادکست می گیرد
and turn it into a bit on stage yeah I
و آن را به کمی روی صحنه تبدیل می کند، سرگرم کننده بود، بله،
think there's a lot of that but I think
فکر می کنم این چیزها زیاد است، اما فکر می کنم
people identify with a wild crazy night
مردم با یک دیوانه وحشی همذات پنداری می کنند.  شبی
that got out of control that they've
که از کنترل خارج شد که
probably had too I I think I don't
احتمالاً آنها هم داشته اند. فکر می کنم
[\h__\h] know
لعنتی نمی دانم
you think Putin knows who you are
تو فکر می کنم پوتین به
because of that story I hope so
خاطر آن داستان می داند که تو کی هستی.
me that that you gotta understand is
این که باید بفهمی
like I'm not
مثل من نیستم
I say stuff like that I'm sure there's
من چیزهایی می گویم که مطمئن هستم
someone hears that and they go who is
کسی آن را می شنود و می رود که
this [\h__\h] narcissist you're like no
این خودشیفته لعنتی است شما مثل این هستید که نه اینطور نیست
that's not it I'm just telling you the
من فقط حقیقت را به شما می گویم
truth like I understand what I'm
همانطور که فهمیدم  چیزی که باید
supposed to say well you know I don't
بگم خوب میدونی من نمی
know I you know I I don't know that's
دونم می دونم نمی دونم
hard to say but I don't [\h__\h] give a
گفتنش سخته ولی من لعنتی
[\h__\h] about that guy I'm not that guy I'm
به اون پسر بدم نمیاد من اون آدم نیستم که بهت
telling you everything that comes out of
میگم  هرچیزی که از دهنم بیرون میاد
my mouth the second it comes out I'm
اون لحظه که بیرون میاد
gonna be 100 honest I don't know any
صد صد روراست خواهم بود. هیچ
other way to live I kind of hope so that
راه دیگه ای برای زندگی بلد نیستم،
would be [\h__\h] cool and I look I know
امیدوارم که خیلی خوب باشه
he's about I guess he's a bad dude I
رفیق بد من
don't follow politics ton but it'll be
سیاست را دنبال نمی کنم اما خیلی
cool if like one day someone's like uh
خوب می شود اگر یک روز یکی مثل اوه اوه
he's he's on his computer and some guy
او روی کامپیوترش باشد و فلان مرد
goes and he's like yeah
برود و او مثل این باشد که آره و
and he's like duh
مثل دیه باشد
and he's like and it shows it to him and
و مثل دیه باشد و این را به او نشان دهد
and then he's like a [\h__\h] this guy
و  پس او مثل یک مرد لعنتی است،
huh it's not out of the realm of
اوه،
possibility that uh Putin has watched it
پوتین آن را تماشا کرده است،
and yeah this this podcast this has kind
و بله، این پادکست به
of made me realize how like small the
من کمک کرده است که بفهمم دنیا چقدر کوچک
world is I've gotten to meet some
است، من با افراد
incredibly oh like especially the
فوق العاده ای آشنا شدم.  مخصوصاً
interesting people like that's I mean
افراد جالبی مانند اینها، منظورم این است
that's the thing where I go
که این چیزی است که من می روم،
like it's gotten really crazy
انگار واقعا دیوانه شده است،
the internet's really insane and Netflix
اینترنت واقعاً دیوانه است و نتفلیکس
is really insane and the reach of like
واقعاً دیوانه است و دسترسی به
people that like this is really simple
افرادی مانند اینها واقعاً ساده است،
but like I'm a big fan of the show drink
اما انگار من از طرفداران پر و پا قرص این اینترنت هستم.  نمایش نوشیدنی
Champs I didn't think in a million years
Champs من فکر نمی کردم بعد از یک میلیون سال
Nori would ever know who I was
نوری هرگز بفهمد من کی هستم
and then he offered me to come to his
و سپس او به من پیشنهاد داد که به پادکست او بیایم
podcast and then when I got there he
و وقتی به آنجا رسیدم به من
told me he was a fan of mine and I went
گفت که طرفدار من است و من
like I remember moving to New York
همانطور که یادم می آید رفتم  حرکت به نیویورک با
listening to you and Capone like I'm
گوش دادن به شما و کاپون مثل اینکه من
sitting there going wow
آنجا نشسته ام،
like and then and the phone calls I've
وای دوست دارم و بعد و تماس های تلفنی که
gotten since the movie came out and uh
از زمان اکران فیلم دریافت کرده ام و اوه
since Razzle Dazzle came out have been
از زمانی که Razzle Dazzle منتشر شده
really insane when you realize
واقعاً دیوانه کننده بوده است، وقتی متوجه شدید که
as much as I know about people and I I
من در مورد مردم می شناسم و دوست دارم
like there's people I'm fans of that
افرادی هستند که من طرفدار آنها هستم که
don't know who I am that like that are
نمی دانند من کی هستم که اینطور هستند
like they're like some uh pitcher in
مانند یک پارچ در
[\h__\h] Florida that I follow the kids I
فلوریدا لعنتی که من بچه هایی را که دوست دارم دنبال می کنم.
like I think it's fun to watch him pitch
فکر می کنم تماشای آن سرگرم کننده است.  او زمین بازی می کرد
there was a softball player in uh Tempe
یک بازیکن سافت بال در اوه تمپه بود
that she do catching drills and I was
که تمرینات گیرایی انجام می داد و من
really into softball with my daughter
واقعاً با دخترم به سافت بال علاقه داشتم
and we watched her Casting girls there's
و دختران بازیگر او را تماشا می کردیم
a girl deglazer who me and my daughters
دختری دگلیزر وجود دارد که من و دخترانم
would watch her dance videos and then I
ویدیوهای رقص او را تماشا می کردیم و سپس من
hit her up she's like you know who I am
او را زدم.  او مثل این است که تو می دانی من کی هستم
and you're like oh yeah that's the way
و تو مثل آه، آره،
the world Works uh what world leader
دنیا این طور است، اوه،
would you drink with if you could you
اگر می توانستی
imagine Putin
پوتین را تصور کنی، با چه رهبر جهانی مشروب می
so Putin doesn't drink much yeah
خورید تا پوتین
much of course yelson would have been a
زیاد مشروب نخورد.  مطمئناً یلسون
good one you would have been a [\h__\h]
خوب بود، تو می‌توانستی آدم خوبی می‌بودی،
good one I mean like I I go Hitler was a
منظورم این است که من می‌روم، هیتلر یک
[\h__\h] like he he drank wine with it with
بیدمشک بود مثل او که با آن شراب می‌نوشید و
a cut with a spoonful of sugar in it
یک قاشق شکر در آن بود،
you've never drank what Churchill that's
شما هرگز آن چیزی را که چرچیل ننوشیده‌اید  به همین دلیل است که این
why hold on that's my guy yeah you know
پسر من است، بله می‌دانی
that's my guy right no I don't know
که این پسر من است، نه من نمی‌دانم
that's okay
این اشکالی ندارد،
so he uh he did champagne you don't have
بنابراین او شامپاین می‌نوشید، لازم نیست
to tell me anything about Winston
درباره وینستون چرچیل چیزی به من بگویید.
routine yeah so his daily routine was a
روال روزانه او یک
big breakfast cigar coffee eggs over you
صبحانه بزرگ سیگار برگ قهوه تخم مرغ روی شما
egg sunny side up toast bacon sausage
تخم مرغ آفتابی تا نان تست بیکن سوسیس
tomato beans uh fruit orange juice soft
لوبیا گوجه فرنگی اوه میوه پرتقال آب پرتقال
Scotch cigar in bed and he sit there for
سیگار نرم اسکاتلندی در رختخواب بود و او
three hours and he'd hold morning
سه ساعت آنجا می نشست و
breakfast and that's they'd come in and
صبحانه را می گرفت و آنها می آمدند  و
he'd run through his day and then he'd
او تمام روزش را می دوید و بعد
get in the bathtub for [\h__\h] an hour
یک ساعت وارد وان می شد
and drink champagne and then he'd go to
و شامپاین می نوشید و بعد به
lunch and have some Goose or whatever
ناهار می رفت و غاز یا هر چیز دیگری که
the [\h__\h] they ate back then with more
آن موقع می خوردند با شامپاین بیشتر می خورد.
and then and then I mean and then you
و بعد و بعد منظورم این است که بعد شما
take a nap and like I love that so every
یک چرت بزنید و مثل من دوست دارم که هر
year on the day of his death things
سال در روز مرگ او چیزهایی را در
January 24th I celebrate Winston
24 ژانویه جشن می‌گیرم و
Churchill's Life by living the way he
زندگی وینستون چرچیل را با زندگی کردن به روشی که او
did and so I have breakfast in bed with
انجام می‌داد جشن می‌گیرم و بنابراین من صبحانه را در رختخواب با
a soft scotch and I just party all
غذای نرم می‌خورم.  اسکاچ و من فقط تمام
[\h__\h] day that would be the guy to
روز مهمانی لعنتی می‌کنیم که اگر بتوانید کسی را
could pick anyone to drink with he drank
انتخاب کنید که با او مشروب بخورد که او
every day throughout the day he lives
هر روز در طول روزی که
like 94. and was
مانند سال 94 زندگی می‌کند با او نوشیدنی می‌نوشید و
one of the most heroic figures in human
یکی از قهرمان‌ترین شخصیت‌ها بود.
history Never Never Surrender
تاریخ بشر هرگز تسلیم نشو
I mean what a [\h__\h] badass thing you
منظورم این است که چه چیز بدی لعنتی یاد داد که به
know he taught he taught the Queen the
ملکه
queen was like uh like a like a window
ملکه یاد داد مثل یک احمق بود که پنجره را
licking idiot right like she was she had
میلیسد، درست مثل اینکه او
a third grade education so like her dad
تحصیلات کلاس سوم داشت، مثل اینکه پدرش
dies and she's like 10 or 12 or whatever
بمیرد و او مثل این باشد.  10 یا 12 یا هر
the first thing they do is they pull her
کاری که اولین کاری که انجام می دهند این است که او را
out of school that I keep done learning
از مدرسه بیرون می کشند که من همچنان یاد می گیرم که
he's just gonna be the queen you gotta
او فقط ملکه خواهد شد باید
know this is what you need to learn
بدانید این چیزی است که باید یاد بگیرید
don't make let people make eye contact
اجازه ندهید مردم با شما ارتباط چشمی برقرار کنند.
with you put your hand down like this
اینطوری دستت را پایین انداخته، اجازه
don't let people touch you so she like
نده مردم تو را لمس کنند، پس او مثل او بود که
she had like a really I saw the by the
واقعاً من دیدم، اتفاقاً من
way I didn't do this research I just
این تحقیق را انجام ندادم، من فقط
watched the crown okay and Winston
تاج را تماشا کردم که خوب بود و وینستون
Churchill kind of taught her about world
چرچیل به نوعی به او در مورد
politics and was they like coming and
سیاست جهانی و  آیا آنها دوست داشتند بیایند و
she'd be like Winston what did we do in
او مانند وینستون باشد که ما در
Africa and he's like oh this is gonna be
آفریقا چه کردیم و او مثل این است که اوه این کار سختی خواهد بود
a tough one and so yeah so but Winston
و بنابراین بله، اما وینستون
Churchill's the badass but if I had to
چرچیل آدم بدی است اما اگر من مجبور به
drink with someone living like drink
نوشیدن با کسی باشم که
there's like there's a two obvious one
شبیه نوشیدنی است  دو مورد واضح وجود دارد
like obviously it's [\h__\h] Kim Jong-un
مثل اینکه معلوم است که کیم جونگ اون لعنتی است،
right you kind of wanna he drinks no he
درست است که می خواهی او مشروب بخورد نه او می
does
زند [
[Laughter]
خنده]
you think my IVs are good in the morning
تو فکر می کنی IV های من صبح خوب هستند، می
you know Kim jong-un's IVs are next
دانی که آی وی های کیم جونگ اون بعدی هستند.
you're like I feel up and he's like it's
و او انگار
amphetamine he would be a badass to
آمفتامین است که برای
drink with but he drinks hard liquor uh
نوشیدن با آن بدخواه است اما مشروب سفت می نوشد اوه
I think it's Scotch Johnny Walker Blue
من فکر می کنم جانی واکر بلو اسکاتلندی است
like this okay so I say things like that
این چیزی است که من شنیده ام.  چنین چیزهایی،
but then I'm sure I I I I I I I don't
اما مطمئنم که من، من، من، نمی‌دانم
know if you've ever partied with someone
که آیا تا به حال با کسی مهمانی کرده‌اید
who just parties a little different than
که فقط کمی متفاوت از
you and then you notice like like
شما مهمانی می‌دهد و بعد متوجه می‌شوید که
sometimes celebr like athletes
گاهی افراد مشهوری مانند ورزشکاران
and then like you're at a strip club and
و سپس در یک باشگاه استریپ استریپ  و
then they they talk weird to a woman
بعد آنها با زنی عجیب صحبت می کنند که
you're like oh that's not me I'm so
تو مثل اوه، این من نیستم، من خیلی
sorry so that would be the thing the
متاسفم، بنابراین این همان چیزی است که
atrocities would be hard to get past
ظلم ها به سختی می توانند
with them that's just the atrocity but
با آنها کنار بیایند، این فقط ظلم است، اما
the way of being I agree with you I
من با آن موافق هستم.  شما
actually don't like drinking with
در واقع دوست ندارم با
rich and powerful people often there's
افراد ثروتمند و قدرتمند مشروب بخورم، اغلب
something weird about them yeah not not
چیز عجیبی در مورد آنها وجود دارد، بله نه
all of them and I don't like I don't
همه آنها و من دوست ندارم
like a drinking meeting like with some
یک جلسه مشروب خوری مانند برخی
of those let's let's
از آنها را دوست ندارم.
people go like hey uh I'm taking you out
اوه من امشب شما را بیرون می بریم،
tonight we're drinking yeah and then I
ما داریم می خوریم و بعد می
go oh that's not the way I like to do it
روم آه این طوری نیست که من دوست دارم این کار را انجام دهم، این به
it gives me anxiety like
من اضطراب می دهد مثل
um our lives are very different you and
اوم زندگی ما بسیار متفاوت است شما و
I yeah were you a fraternity no
من بله اگر شما یک برادری بودید نه
we could start there yet no it was not
ما می توانستیم شروع کنیم  هنوز هیچ مشکلی نیست
and the differences continue from there
و اختلافات از آنجا ادامه می یابد،
I'm sure so when you get your pleasure
مطمئنم که وقتی به لذت خود
pin uh-huh they take you out and their
پین کردی اوه-هه اونا تو را بیرون می برند و
whole thing is you're gonna we're
تمام حرفشان این است که ما
getting you [\h__\h] up yeah that energy
تو را به لعنت می اندازیم، بله این انرژی
is not my energy I don't like that like
انرژی من نیست من این را دوست ندارم مثل این است
it's I just go why don't we just get
من فقط می روم چرا مست نکنیم
drunk and feel really good about
و احساس خوبی نسبت به
ourselves like I never like took
خودمان نداشته باشیم مثل اینکه هرگز دوست نداشتم
mushrooms to see Jesus I just wanted to
برای دیدن عیسی قارچ گرفتم فقط می خواستم از
enjoy Rain-X on a windshield like so
Rain-X روی شیشه جلویی لذت ببرم  بنابراین
like that that for me
برای من
uh is like one of my things so if if Kim
مثل یکی از چیزهای من است، بنابراین اگر کیم
Jong-un flew me to North Korea to drink
جونگ اون مرا به کره شمالی می برد تا
with him I'd be like I'd have to start
با او مشروب بخورم، باید
really getting blackout drunk on the
در
plane to enjoy drinking with him that
هواپیما مست شوم تا از نوشیدن لذت ببرم.  با او در آن
day
روز
what's your favorite like different
چه چیزی را دوست دارید مانند
occasions what's your favorite drink
مناسبت های مختلف نوشیدنی مورد علاقه شما چیست
what's your favorite way of drinking
روش مورد علاقه شما برای نوشیدن این است که
it's it's I've got it varies so what are
من آن را دارم متفاوت است بنابراین
the different contexts here it's like
زمینه های مختلف اینجا چیست مانند
one-on-one
یک به یک یک
one-on-one like you sit down with I
به یک مانند شما نشسته  من
don't know Rogan invites you like it's a
نمی دانم روگان شما را دعوت می کند مثل اینکه یک
Godfather to sit down and finally have a
پدرخوانده است که بنشینید و در نهایت در
talk about something it's going to be
مورد چیزی صحبت کنید که قرار است ویسکی شود،
it's gonna be like a nice whiskey neat
مثل یک ویسکی خوب و تمیز خواهد بود
no I like it on the rocks and I like
نه من آن را روی سنگ ها دوست دارم و من
lots of rocks it won't be something
سنگ های زیادی را دوست دارم  این چیز گرانی نخواهد بود
expensive because Rogan is not he's not
زیرا روگان او
a fancy boy you know like he's a real
پسر شیک نیست، شما می دانید که او یک
regular he's a really regular dude
فرد معمولی واقعی است، او یک شخص واقعا منظم است،
he's gotten less regular the more
او هر چقدر
millions of dollars he has I think
میلیون ها دلار بیشتر داشته باشد، کمتر منظم شده است، فکر می کنم
there's parts of him where you're like
بخش هایی از او وجود دارد که شما شبیه آن هستید.
yeah like where you're like oh wow we
آره مثل جایی که تو هستی اوه وای ما می
can do this yeah
توانیم این کار را انجام دهیم آره
um but he's a right he'd be like Jack on
امم اما او حق دارد مثل جک روی
the rocks or like Buffalo Trace or one
سنگ ها یا مثل بوفالو تریس یا یکی
of the maybe a little whiskey he's
از ویسکی های شاید کمی که دارد
buying Rogan B uh whiskey rocks
راگان ویسکی روگان بی اوه می خرد
and then like that's a good one I
و پس از آن دوست دارد  این یک برنامه خوب است که من
haven't hung out with Joe by ourselves I
به تنهایی با جو همنشینی نکرده ام، می
take that back I was with him the other
پذیرم که آن شب با او بودم،
night but like I would be cool my times
اما دوست دارم که حالم باحال باشد، اوقاتم
with Joe's are are always on podcasts
با جو همیشه در پادکست ها هستند،
yeah and his I missed the times where it
بله و او دلم برای زمان هایی که در آن بود تنگ شده بود.
was we just have you and him at the
ما فقط تو و او را
store late night yeah I I'm okay with
تا آخر شب در فروشگاه داریم، بله، من با
podcasts okay I used to think this is
پادکست ها مشکلی ندارم، خوب، قبلاً فکر می کردم این شبیه به
like uh performative or something like
اجرای یا چیزی شبیه به
this but it's not really no that's just
این است، اما واقعاً نه، فقط
the chance to really sit down I enjoy it
فرصتی است که واقعاً بنشینم، من از آن لذت می برم
because of the people I could never sit
زیرا  از بین افرادی که هرگز نمی توانستم
down with ah like David Cross I would
با آه مانند دیوید کراس بنشینم من
never sit down with David Cross because
هرگز با دیوید کراس نمی نشینم زیرا
we don't run in the same circles and but
ما در یک حلقه نمی دویم و اما
it's nice he has something to promote
خوب است که او چیزی برای تبلیغ دارد
and then he comes to my house and then
و بعد به خانه من می آید و بعد
we can sit down for an hour and talk and
ما  می توانم یک ساعت بنشینم و صحبت کنم و بعد
then and then or Kevin Smith like people
و بعد یا کوین اسمیت مثل افرادی که
I would never really hang out with Tom
هرگز با تام ام ام من از
I enjoy being alone with Tom Moore off
تنهایی با تام مور لذت می برم
Mike Tom Segura yeah we have a lot of
مایک تام سگورا بله، ما تاریخ زیادی داریم،
history there's a lot of things secrets
رازهای چیزهای زیادی وجود دارد
we know about each other and there's a
ما در مورد یکدیگر می دانیم و
lot of Secrets going on in our each
رازهای زیادی در
other's lives that I would never share
زندگی یکدیگر در جریان است که من هرگز آنها را
on podcasts that I'd that I can talk to
در پادکست ها به اشتراک نمی گذارم که می توانم در
him about and I really appreciate his
مورد آنها صحبت کنم و من واقعاً از او قدردانی می کنم
and I know this isn't on brand of us
و می دانم که این در برند نیست  از اینکه ما
beating each other up but like I really
همدیگر را کتک می زنیم اما من واقعاً از
appreciate his insight as a as a dad and
بینش او به عنوان یک پدر،
as a dude and as a son
به عنوان یک دوست و به عنوان یک پسر قدردانی می کنم،
but but he makes me giggle harder than
اما او باعث می شود که من سخت تر از
anyone so doing a podcast is fun so
دیگران بخندم.
performative for you with him and then
شما با او و سپس
there's a party me and him because we're
یک مهمانی من و او وجود دارد، زیرا ما
trying to make each other laugh but I'll
سعی می کنیم یکدیگر را بخندانیم، اما به
tell you if we're going back to drinks
شما می گویم اگر دوباره به نوشیدنی برگردیم، به
I'll tell you
شما می گویم
like a great a great afternoon drink is
مانند یک نوشیدنی عالی بعد از ظهر یک نوشیدنی عالی است.
a comparti spritz it's my one of my
اسپریتز یکی از
favorite drinks I don't even know what
نوشیدنی‌های مورد علاقه من است، حتی نمی‌دانم
that is oh the party Spritz Campari is
آن مهمانی چیست اسپریتز کامپاری
an interesting alcohol
یک الکل جالب است،
because I think it's a bitter uh or it's
زیرا فکر می‌کنم تلخ است یا
a liqueur and it's got a weird rooty
لیکور است و طعم خاکی ریشه‌ای عجیبی دارد،
earthy taste it's red so it looks like
قرمز است بنابراین به نظر می‌رسد.  مثل
Kool-Aid that's why I got into it I
Kool-Aid به همین دلیل وارد آن شدم،
thought camparion ice would be oh so
فکر می کردم یخ Camparion خیلی
nice it was an old commercial but man
خوب است، یک تبلیغ قدیمی بود، اما مرد
it's [\h__\h] like sucking the green
لعنتی مثل مکیدن
Giant's dick it is earthy what's earthy
دیک سبز Giant است، خاکی است چه خاکی
it's like it tastes like Roots it's oh
است، مثل اینکه طعم آن شبیه Roots است، اوه
nice it's not it's not it's there's a
خوب، اینطور نیست  این نیست، یک
bitterness and like a it's just not
تلخی دارد و مانند یک، فقط عالی نیست
and then someone introduced me to a
و بعد یکی به من یک
Negroni which is Campari and gin and a
نگرونی معرفی کرد که کامپاری و جین و
little soda water and then the Campari
کمی آب سودا است و سپس Campari
Spritz compari Spritz is Campari
Spritz compari Spritz Campari
Prosecco and soda water in like a wine
Prosecco است و آب سودا در یک
glass and it is
لیوان شراب و
so enjoyable it's got so many different
آنقدر لذت بخش است که
profiles to it where you get the
پروفایل های مختلفی برای آن وجود دارد که در آن
bitterness but the sweetness of the
تلخی اما شیرینی
Prosecco and then it flattens it out
Prosecco را می گیرید و سپس آن را
with the soda water and it looks like
با آب سودا صاف می کند و شبیه
Kool-Aid so I love it that's one of my
کول اید است بنابراین من آن را دوست دارم که یکی از
favorite drinks to share in what context
نوشیدنی های مورد علاقه من است.  برای به اشتراک گذاشتن در چه زمینه ای
oh uh you're in Italy
اوه اوه اوه اوه در ایتالیا هستید
and you've been walking around Venice
و در اطراف ونیز قدم می زدید
and everyone went their own ways and the
و همه راه خود را رفتند و
whole family comes back together and you
همه خانواده دور هم جمع می شوند و شما
meet at a statue and and your wife's
در یک مجسمه ملاقات می کنید و همسرتان
sweating and she's uncomfortable and
عرق می کند و او ناراحت است و
your daughters are 16 and 18 and they're
دختران شما  16 و 18 ساله هستند و آنها
like are what are we gonna what are we
مثل اینکه ما می خواهیم چه
doing with the rest of the day and you
کار کنیم بقیه روز را چه می کنیم و شما
go hey guys it's Europe does anyone want
بروید هی بچه ها اینجا اروپا است آیا کسی می خواهد
to come party Spritz and everyone goes I
بیاید مهمانی اسپریتز و همه می روند من
don't know what that is and you go
نمی دانم این چیست و  می‌روی
[\h__\h] party spreads now it's minor in
مهمانی لعنتی پخش می‌شود حالا در
alcohol so it's not going to light them
الکل جزئی است، بنابراین آنها را روشن نمی‌کند،
up but it gives them a little bit of a
اما کمی
buzz where they're like Dad These are
سر و صدا به آن‌ها می‌دهد که مثل بابا هستند اینها
nice Island didn't drink her so I drank
خوب هستند جزیره او را ننوشید پس من مال
hers I Georgia had hers Leanne had hers
او را نوشیدند من جورجیا داشتم.  Leanne مال او بود
and we ordered another round I ordered
و ما یک دور دیگر سفارش دادیم که من سفارش دادم
and they're
و آنها
[\h__\h] refreshing and the buzz is
بسیار با طراوت هستند و صدای وزوز عالی است،
perfect it's not too much because it's
زیاد نیست زیرا
just a little bit of champagne and some
فقط کمی شامپاین و مقداری
Campari if the buzz is perfect and then
Campari است اگر وزوز عالی باشد و سپس
a couple of them and then they kind of
چند تا از آنها و سپس  آنها یک جورهایی
disappear and then you're just walking
ناپدید می شوند و بعد دوباره در حال راه رفتن هستید،
around again that's a great [\h__\h]
این یک
drink you ever drink alone
نوشیدنی لعنتی عالی است که تا به حال به تنهایی می نوشید
[Laughter]
[خنده]،
so there's a two kinds of a loan one is
بنابراین دو نوع قرض وجود دارد که یکی
alone like at a bar oh wait there's
تنها است مانند یک بار، صبر کنید،
other people but they're strangers right
افراد دیگری هستند اما آنها غریبه هستند  درست است
they're kind of like out there
آنها به نوعی شبیه به آنجا هستند که به راه خود
keep going yeah don't walk me through
ادامه دهند، بله، من را از طریق
all the alarms and then I'll tell you
همه آلارم ها راه ندهید و سپس به بقیه می گویم که همه
the rest there's all kinds of there's a
جور آدمی
alone on a train we're transporting
در قطار است که ما وسایل حمل می کنیم
and then there's just the lone in a in
و سپس فقط  تنها در
an empty home or a hotel room hotel and
یک خانه خالی یا یک هتل اتاق هتل هستید و
it's Sunday night Sunday night and
یکشنبه شب است، یکشنبه شب است و
you're packing your bag and you got a
شما دارید چمدان خود را می بندید و ساعت
flight at six a.m yeah but Roadhouse is
شش صبح پرواز دارید، بله، اما Roadhouse
on and you're like [\h__\h] so you go down
روشن است و شما مانند یک گنده هستید، بنابراین به پایین می روید.
to the front desk and go is the bar
میز جلو و میروم بار
still open and they go yeah can I order
هنوز باز است و آنها می روند بله می توانم
something to take to my room sure how
چیزی سفارش بدهم که به اتاقم ببرم، مطمئن شوید که
about six Heinekens six Heinekens yeah
شش تا هایینهکن شش هاینکن بله،
my wife wanted one too she's not up
همسرم هم یکی می خواست
there you murdered her and you just say
او آنجا نیست، شما او را به قتل رساندید و فقط
to yourself I'm just getting six so that
به خودتان بگویید من  من فقط شش می گیرم تا
if I have four I just know I have two
اگر چهار تا داشته باشم، فقط می دانم که دو
extra ones and then you go through six
تای اضافی دارم و سپس شما شش تا را پشت سر می گذارید
and you're like oh man I'm not done yet
و مثل این هستید که اوه مرد، من هنوز تمام نشده ام
dude I've drank in every alone scenario
دوست من در هر سناریوی تنهایی نوشیده ام،
you can possibly think of I've drank uh
احتمالاً می توانید فکر کنید  من به
I've drank alone in a helicopter with a
تنهایی در هلیکوپتر مشروب خوردم با یک
dude who didn't know I was drinking uh
دوست که نمی دانست من می نوشم آه
he was I was like kind of drinking here
او بود من مثل این بود که اینجا مشروب می خوردم
and he's like absolutely not and then I
و او کاملاً نه و بعد
poured it into a flask and opened it and
آن را در یک فلاسک ریختم و باز کردم  آن را
drank it and he's like dude we're in a
نوشید و او مثل رفیق است که ما در یک
[\h__\h] helicopter you don't think I
هلیکوپتر لعنتی هستیم، فکر نمی کنید من
spelled that the best alone drinking you
نوشتم که بهترین نوشیدنی که
can ever do in my opinion now we're
می توانید به تنهایی انجام دهید به نظر من اکنون داریم
getting into the Weeds on it is alone
وارد علف های هرز می شویم این است که تنها
behind someone's back
پشت سر کسی باشد.
what do you mean like when they don't
آیا منظورت این است که وقتی آنها نمی
know you're drinking but you're drinking
دانند شما مشروب می خورید اما
like Christmas shopping uh
مثل خرید کریسمس می نوشید و
and your wife says all right let's all
همسرتان می گوید خوب بیایید همه از هم
split up and you go cool and it's like
جدا شویم و شما باحال بروید و
it's like 11 o'clock on a Sunday and
مثل اینکه ساعت 11 است  یک یکشنبه و
they just opened that bar by the
آن‌ها نوار کنار
elevator in the Beverly Center and you
آسانسور در مرکز بورلی را باز کردند و تو
just sneak over and you go hey man
دزدکی می‌روی و می‌روی هی مرد،
can I get a double Jack on the raw socks
می‌توانم یک جک دوتایی روی میله‌های جوراب خام بیاورم،
rods like sure and you just have it you
مطمئناً و تو فقط آن را داشته باشی،
just go let's just and then you're off
برو بیا و سپس  تو رفتی
and then you're like yeah yeah and then
و بعد مثل اینکه آره آره و بعد
you just little sneak one sneak it and
تو فقط یه دزدکی اون رو دزدکی میزنی و
sneak it and then buzz and nobody knows
دزدکی میکشی و بعد وزوز میکنی و هیچکس نمیدونه و
and then your wife's like wait have you
بعد همسرت مثل اینکه صبر کن،
been drinking like
مثل اینکه آره من
yeah I'm drinking by myself in a [\h__\h]
خودم میخورم
mall yeah on Christmas how sad do you
مرکز خرید لعنتی آره در کریسمس فکر می‌کنی چقدر غمگینم
think I am and then you go yeah I am uh
و بعد تو برو آره من آهان، خلق و
what about mood do you ever drink in a
خوی شما تا به حال در یک
dark place so I broke I I had a chick
مکان تاریک نوشیدنی می‌نوشید، بنابراین
uh when I was when I came back from
من شکستم.  وقتی از
Russia and she's something with my best
روسیه برگشتم و او با بهترین دوستم دوست است
and I didn't know how to deal with the
و من نمی دانستم چگونه با
emotions I had and my buddy Mike Osborne
احساساتی که داشتم کنار بیایم و دوستم مایک آزبورن
said I can tell you this if you drink
گفت می توانم این را به شما بگویم اگر بنوشید
they go away and I went okay
آنها از بین می روند و من خوب رفتم
and that was the first and kind of last
و آن  اولین و آخرین
time I ever did that
باری بود که این کار را انجام دادم
because I did it I've done it I've done
چون این کار را انجام دادم،
it a couple times but it I try to avoid
چند بار انجامش دادم، اما سعی می کنم از آن اجتناب کنم،
I try to avoid if there's emotion going
سعی می کنم از آن اجتناب کنم، اگر احساسی
to alcohol like meaning not when it's
به الکل می رود، یعنی نه زمانی که الکل است.
anxiety but like depression yeah I kind
اضطراب اما مثل افسردگی آره من به نوعی
of sit in the depression because or
در افسردگی می نشینم چون یا
anxiety I lean towards alcohol like
اضطرابی که به الکل متمایل می شوم مانند اضطراب
anxiety like about flying or or
در مورد پرواز یا یا یا
or just like getting worked up on over
فقط دوست دارم سر چیزی مشغول شوم
but with depression I try to avoid
اما با افسردگی سعی می کنم از
alcohol and just sit in it
الکل اجتناب کنم و فقط در آن بنشینم.
um because I I because I've gone there
من چون قبلاً به آنجا رفته بودم
before but anxiety is up I land I land
اما اضطراب زیاد است من زمین می گیرم
all the time but depression heartbreak
همیشه فرود می آیم اما افسردگی دل شکسته
all that you just sit in the feeling
همه اینها که تو فقط در این احساس می نشینی
yeah heartbreak's a weird one for me so
آره دلشکستگی برای من عجیب است پس
like the last time I got my heart broken
مثل آخرین باری که قلبم شکست
it Leanne dumped me
لیان آن را رها کرد  من
um we were dating for like four months
حدود چهار ماه با هم قرار داشتیم
and she broke up with me and my instinct
و او از من جدا شد و غریزه من این
was to have a drink my friends went to
بود که یک نوشیدنی بنوشم دوستانم به
this uh this uh middle eastern
این
restaurant and I told him what was going
رستوران خاورمیانه رفتند و من به او گفتم که
on in my buddy of course like let's get
در رفیقم چه خبر است.
a cocktail and I was like I don't want
یک کوکتل و من فکر می‌کردم که نمی‌خواهم،
one I gotta figure this out because I
باید این را بفهمم، زیرا من
want this chick and if I start drinking
این جوجه را می‌خواهم و اگر شروع به نوشیدن کنم،
I'll be like ah [\h__\h] it
مثل آه لعنت به آن خواهم بود،
so I gotta figure it out like I wonder
بنابراین باید آن را بفهمم، در عجبم که
I'm gonna find out my dad dies one day
می‌خواهم بفهمم  پدرم یک روز می میرد
or my mom but my dad will be the ruffle
یا مادرم، اما پدرم سرگردان خواهد بود،
my mom will be equally as rough my dad
مادرم به همان اندازه خشن خواهد بود پدرم
and I were really close
و من واقعاً صمیمی بودیم
and I wonder if I thought about this a
و نمی دانم که آیا من خیلی به این موضوع فکر کرده ام
lot if I'll have a drink
آیا می توانم یک نوشیدنی
dealing with that
بنوشم.
like I think about that a lot I keep
من خیلی به این موضوع فکر می کنم و مدام می
saying everything I get with my dad is
گویم هرچه با پدرم می گیرم
extra my dad my dad had a 100 blockage
اضافه است پدرم پدرم
in his Widowmaker twice and both times
دو بار 100 انسداد در Widowmaker خود داشت و هر دو بار
they saved his life and he got a stint I
آنها جانش را نجات دادند و
think 12 or 13 years ago and then he
فکر می کنم 12 یا 13 سال پیش و پس از آن مدت کوتاهی کرد.  او
just got a stint this last year
همین سال گذشته یک دوره بازی دریافت کرد،
but that's why everything I get to do I
اما به همین دلیل است که من احساس می کنم هر کاری که انجام می دهم
feel like is extra and so you know he
اضافی است و بنابراین می دانید که او
was just at the premiere of my movie and
در اولین اکران فیلم من بود و
he got to see that and he had a very
او آن را دید و او
emotional response and I got to I got
واکنش بسیار احساسی داشت و من دریافت کردم  من
that from him and I was like that that's
این را از او گرفتم و من اینطور بودم که
a little ice on the cake I did you know
کمی یخ روی کیک است.
getting with them are all extra so I
همراهی با آنها همه چیز اضافی است، بنابراین من می
have you know at least 74 so
دانم که حداقل 74 سال داشته باشید، بنابراین بله،
yeah that'll be a tough one well at the
در اولین
premiere here's what proud yeah he came
نمایش بسیار سخت خواهد بود.
and I was like what he was like and he
من مثل اون بودم و اون
just and he was shaking yeah he goes I
فقط و می لرزید آره میره من
just underestimated you I didn't know I
فقط تو رو دست کم گرفتم
didn't know I didn't know you were this
نمیدونستم نمیدونستم تو این بودی
I didn't do whatever it was really hard
من هر کاری که واقعا سخت بود انجام ندادم
to understand him to be honest with you
او را درک کن تا با تو روراست باشد،
I don't know totally what he said he
من نمی دانم که او چه گفت که
might just not like the movie
ممکن است از فیلم خوشش نیاید،
I I think you uh were hearing what you
فکر می کنم تو داشتی چیزی را می شنیدی که
wanted to hear uh would you learn about
می خواستی بشنوی، آیا در مورد
life from your father
زندگی از پدرت یاد می گرفتی،
uh it's not gonna make sense
اوه، منطقی نیست.  می‌خواهم احساس کنم
I want to feel like sometimes I'm like a
گاهی شبیه یک
professional [\h__\h] wrestler because
کشتی‌گیر حرفه‌ای لعنتی هستم، زیرا
all I care about is you come and see me
تنها چیزی که به آن اهمیت می‌دهم این است که تو بیایی و ببینی که
do stand up so whatever I got to do to
ایستاده‌ام، بنابراین هر کاری که باید انجام دهم تا
get you there but
تو را به آنجا برسانم، اما
the number one thing my one takeaway
اولین چیزی که من
from that man's humility and
از تواضع و فروتنی آن مرد می‌توانم برداشت کنم.
I applied I've applied it in different
من درخواست دادم و
ways throughout my career
در طول زندگی حرفه ای ام
on my 26th birthday he gave me a really
در تولد 26 سالگی ام به روش های مختلفی از آن استفاده کردم. او یک سخنرانی واقعاً تهاجمی به من ارائه داد
he
او
I was hungover and I just thought he was
خماری کرده بودم و فقط فکر می کردم او می
going to say good happy birthday so I
خواهد تولدت مبارک را بگوید بنابراین
picked up the phone
تلفن را برداشتم
and I was like Hey and he was like you
و من جواب دادم.  مثل هی و اون مثل اینکه تو
are a tremendous piece of [\h__\h]
یه تیکه بزرگی هستی
and he broke me off you have no humility
و منو قطع کرد تو هیچ تواضعی
you have no this you'll never succeed in
نداری اینو نداری هیچوقت تو
anything you you're you're lying to
هیچ کاری موفق نخواهی شد تو به
yourself you're lying to everyone around
خودت دروغ میگی به همه اطرافیان دروغ میگی
you you're not doing what you're going
تو کاری را انجام نمی دهی که
after your dream I broke you I failed
دنبال رویاهایت می روی، من تو را شکستم،
you as a father this and that I was like
تو را به عنوان یک پدر ناکام گذاشتم و این که
I thought you're gonna wish me happy
فکر می کردم می خواهی تولدم را تبریک بگویی
and so
و بنابراین
in that speech he told me if I wanted
در آن سخنرانی به من گفت اگر می خواهم
something I had to go at it and I had to
کاری که باید انجامش می‌دادم و باید
go after it as as hard as I could
تا جایی که می‌توانستم دنبالش می‌رفتم
and I had to do whatever it could I
و باید هر کاری از دستم بر می‌آمد انجام می‌دادم تا به آن برسم
could do to achieve that in this case it
که در این مورد،
was working offering to do anything at
پیشنهاد انجام هر کاری در
the comedy club to get on stage
باشگاه کمدی برای به دست آوردن آن بود.  روی صحنه به
he told I told him that's not how it
او گفت که اینطوری
works and he said no that's that's how
کار نمی کند و او گفت نه
it works for some poor kid from Harlem
برای یک بچه فقیر از هارلم اینطوری کار می کند
because that kid needs it he goes you've
زیرا آن بچه به آن نیاز دارد او می رود شما در
grown up with privilege your whole life
تمام زندگی خود با امتیاز بزرگ شده اید و به
you don't need it you think you're going
آن نیاز ندارید.  تو فکر می کنی
to be fine
خوب می شوی
and so I went and I ended up getting a
و بنابراین من رفتم و در
job at the door but I
نهایت شغلی پیدا کردم، اما من
it was it was it was it's humbling it's
همینطور بودم، این
really like uh it's it makes me feel it
واقعاً متواضعانه است، واقعاً این باعث می شود که احساس کنم
made me feel uncomfortable
احساس ناراحتی به من می کند
and so that humility
و بنابراین  فروتنی
uh is it's the first time I really
اوه این اولین باری است که من واقعاً
understood humility and I've applied
فروتنی را درک می کنم و
that in many respects in like in like
از بسیاری جهات این را به کار می برم، مثلاً
getting to be a paid regular at The
در
Comedy Store that happened late in life
فروشگاه کمدی که در اواخر زندگی
for me and which I think most people
برای من اتفاق افتاد و فکر می کنم اکثر مردم از آن دست
would give up and be like ah [\h__\h] that
می کشند، به عنوان یکی از افراد معمولی با حقوق دریافت کردم.  و مثل آه لعنتی باش که
I'm already a touring comic I'm on TV I
من در حال حاضر یک کمیک تور هستم، من در تلویزیون حضور دارم، به
don't need that but it's something I
آن نیازی ندارم، اما این چیزی است که
wanted and I knew I wanted so I I just
می‌خواستم و می‌دانستم که می‌خواهم، بنابراین با
humbly went after it
فروتنی دنبالش رفتم
and then I think I I still apply it when
و بعد فکر می‌کنم هنوز هم آن را اعمال می‌کنم.
selling tickets or or selling a project
فروش بلیت یا فروش پروژه
to the fans
به طرفداران
or even doing podcasts I try to be as
یا حتی انجام پادکست‌ها، من سعی می‌کنم تا جایی که
honest as I can about whatever I'm going
می‌توانم در مورد هر کاری که می‌گذرم
through or whatever I'm dealing with but
یا با آن سر و کار دارم صادق باشم، اما
when it comes to like selling things I
وقتی صحبت از فروش چیزهایی است که
don't I don't have a problem
انجام می‌دهم.  من مشکلی ندارم که
trying to make fun of myself or or
بخواهم خودم را مسخره کنم یا
get in front of people so that they know
در مقابل مردم قرار بگیرم تا آنها بدانند
that that I have a show because like the
که من نمایشی دارم، زیرا مانند
thing I'm good at though
چیزی که در آن خوب هستم، اگرچه می
the one thing I know I'm good at stand
دانم که هستم.  در ایستادن خوب هستم
and and I I say that humbly but like I
و من این را متواضعانه می گویم، اما
want them to come there so like I've
دوست دارم آنها بیایند آنجا، طوری که
heard people make fun of me like before
شنیده ام که مردم مرا مسخره می کنند، مثل قبل از اینکه بله، من
they're like yeah I'm not some I'm not
یک نفر نیستم،
some clown in a speedo who's one is
یک دلقک نیستم در یک سرعت  چه کسی
gonna I'm a real comic and I go okay but
قرار است من یک کمیک واقعی هستم و خوب می روم اما می
I wanna I want them that my shows and
خواهم آنها را نمایش دهند و
you can be that guy and I'll be this guy
تو می توانی آن مرد باشی و من این مرد خواهم بود
yeah the clown the speedo yeah it's like
بله دلقک سرعتی آره مثل این است که
what are you gonna do
چه کار
funny people make fun of me for taking
خنده داری انجام می دهی  مردم مرا به خاطر درآوردن پیراهنم مسخره می‌کنند،
no one ever does it to me like no one
انگار که از پشت سرم هیچ‌کس این کار را با من انجام
Comics aren't Comics aren't Comics
نمی‌دهد.
yeah yeah but I always go like I always
برو مثل من همیشه می روم
go like who what do you care what am I
مثل کی هستی به چه کاری اهمیت می دهی من به
what do you care and you love taking
چه چیزی اهمیت می دهی و تو دوست داری
shirt off more than anything
پیراهن را از تنت در بیاوری بیش از هر چیزی که می
you know when something becomes meme it
دانی وقتی چیزی تبدیل به میم می
becomes super popular it uh
شود فوق العاده محبوب می شود اوه
anymore to get tired of it you still
دیگر به دست آوردن آن چیز را دوست نداشتن آسان می شود  از آن خسته شده ای، تو هنوز
love it well more than anything
آن را بیشتر از هر چیزی دوستش داری، من
I like being shirtless
بدون پیراهن بودن را
more than having a shirt I'm very
بیشتر از داشتن یک پیراهن دوست دارم، من
uncomfortable in a shirt yeah like right
با پیراهن خیلی ناراحتم، بله مثل
now and I've tactile issues like I have
الان و مشکلات لمسی دارم، مثلاً
legit tacked all issues
همه مسائل را حل کرده ام،
I'm most comfortable in stretchy jeans
راحت تر هستم  با شلوار جین کشدار
with a loose fitting belt and then these
با یک کمربند گشاد و بعد
shirts exactly but I don't I like more
دقیقاً این پیراهن‌ها، اما من بیشتر
like a v-neck I feel I can feel this on
شبیه یقه‌های V را دوست ندارم، احساس می‌کنم
my neck right now and I can feel it on
در حال حاضر می‌توانم آن را روی گردنم احساس کنم و می‌توانم آن را روی
my arms and so I'm I'll sit a certain
بازوهایم حس کنم.  من یه جورایی می نشینم
way because it like it just rubs me
چون مثل اینکه من را به اشتباه می مالد،
be a more comfortable shirtless I can
بدون پیراهن راحت تر باشم، من
never wear what you're wearing
هرگز نمی توانم لباسی که تو می پوشی بپوشم، آره
uh yeah well this is my shirtless each
خوب، این بدون پیراهن من است، هر
of us have to find our place in this
کدام از ما باید جایگاه خود را در این
world in terms of fashion I would love
دنیا پیدا کنیم.  مد من دوست دارم
to be able to wear what you wear yeah
بتوانم آن چیزی را که می پوشی بپوشم، بله،
because it looks good it feels like an
زیرا به نظر می رسد خوب است، احساس
escape from convention
فرار از کنوانسیون است،
because you or me both of us yeah
زیرا من یا شما هر دوی ما بله، زیرا
because this nobody wears this
این هیچکس این را نمی پوشد،
unless you work security for somebody
مگر اینکه شما امنیت را برای کسی کار کنید،
yeah but it looks good on you does it I
بله، اما برای شما خوب به نظر می رسد.  آیا این را
don't know you know I think people think
نمی دانم می دانید فکر می کنم مردم فکر می کنند من دوست
I don't like they would say like what
ندارم می گویند
what if you lose weight you can't take
چه می شود اگر وزن کم کردی
your shirt off anymore go no I can
دیگر نمی توانی پیراهن خود را در بیاوری برو نه من می توانم پیراهنم را
[\h__\h] out of your mind I'm gonna take
در بیاورم.  از ذهن تو من
my shirt off all the time
همیشه پیراهنم را در می آورم
uh you mentioned uh early on heartbreak
اوه تو گفتی اوه اوایل دلشکستگی
after the Russia trip with a girl who
بعد از سفر روسیه با دختری که
slept with your friend
با دوستت خوابید
uh let's go back to Hemingway quotes
اوه بیا برگردیم به همینگوی
the best way to find out if you can
بهترین راه برای فهمیدن اینکه آیا می توانی
trust somebody is to trust them
اعتماد کنی  یکی باید به آنها اعتماد کند،
so to go all in with the trust
پس با اعتماد تمام شود
I love Hemingway so much
من همینگوی را خیلی دوست دارم، اوم آیا
um have you been betrayed in your life
در زندگی ات به تو خیانت شده است، آره
what do you think about trust
نظرت در مورد اعتماد چیست،
it's an interesting question
این یک سوال جالب است.
life a couple times by really close
توسط دوستان بسیار صمیمی
and uh
و اوه
I'm not someone who can't like I have a
من کسی نیستم که نتوانم آن را دوست داشته باشم،
mantra that I mean I'm
منظورم این است که من هستم،
I don't know if people have heard it or
نمی دانم آیا مردم آن را شنیده اند یا
not and I'm I hate I hate sharing it but
نه و من از به اشتراک گذاشتن آن متنفرم، اما
it's but it's true the Mantra is so you
این  اما درست است که مانترا این است که شما
think I'm weak
فکر می کنید من ضعیف هستم
like do you think it's like that's my
مثل اینکه فکر می کنید این
thing because I I feel like people take
موضوع من است زیرا احساس می کنم مردم
advantage of me and I go so you think
از من سوء استفاده می کنند و من می روم بنابراین شما فکر می کنید
I'm weak
من ضعیف هستم
you forget everyone that like that and
همه را فراموش می کنید که اینطوری و
I'm named the people that have betrayed
من  m به نام افرادی که به من خیانت کرده اند
me I'm a larger man than all of them and
من از همه آنها بزرگتر هستم و و اما
and but I and so that's what really
من و بنابراین این چیزی است که واقعاً
[\h__\h] with me is I go so you think I'm
با من بد می شود این است که می روم بنابراین فکر می کنید من
weak like where I grew up when you do
ضعیف هستم مانند جایی که بزرگ شدم وقتی
stuff there was physical consequences I
آنجا کارهایی انجام می دهید  عواقب جسمی بود من
grew up in Florida like I've been beaten
در فلوریدا بزرگ شدم، مثل اینکه
up a bunch I'm not saying I can fight
یک سری کتک خورده‌ام، نمی‌گویم که می‌توانم بجنگم،
but like I'm not scared of getting
اما مثل اینکه از
beaten up
کتک خوردن نمی‌ترسم
and the the times that I've been
و از دفعاتی که به من
betrayed and and
خیانت شده است و
even I know even like by Ari whichever
حتی من  حتی مثل آری بدانم هر
people see that drugging as a betrayal
کسی که مصرف مواد مخدر را یک خیانت می‌داند
and I did for a period but it was it was
و من برای مدتی این کار را انجام دادم، اما این
only because it was Ari and he was my
فقط به این دلیل بود که آری بود و او
one of my best friends and me and him
یکی از بهترین دوستان من بود و من و او
had to work through that because I I
مجبور بودیم این کار را انجام دهیم زیرا من
couldn't not love him like I couldn't
می‌توانستم.  دوستش نداشته باشم، مثل اینکه نمی‌توانم
not have him in my life he means a lot
او را در زندگی‌ام نداشته
to have
باشم،
on with him at that time but he made a
او برای من ارزش زیادی دارد.
bad decision and I had to forgive him
تصمیم بدی بود و من مجبور شدم او را
for that because I knew he he knew my
به خاطر آن ببخشم زیرا می دانستم که او سخنان من را می داند.
I think I'm harder to trust people now
فکر می کنم
I'm I'm not as apt to trust people at
اعتماد کردن به مردم برای من سخت تر است.
but there was a moment I don't know if
نمی‌دانم آیا
I've ever shared this and I don't know
تا به حال این را به اشتراک گذاشته‌ام و نمی‌دانم
how this will sound but there was a
چگونه به نظر می‌رسد، اما
moment that information got leaked about
لحظه‌ای بود که اطلاعات در مورد
a thing and all my managers and agents
موضوعی به بیرون درز کرد و همه مدیران و عوامل من،
both both
هم
Tom and my Tom and our managers and
تام و تام من و هم مدیران و
agents would like to uh separate either
عوامل ما، این کار را انجام دادند.  دوست دارند ما را از هم جدا کنند یا یکی از ما را از هم
separate us
جدا کنند یا
or one of us one of them get both of us
یکی از ما هر دوی ما را بگیرد،
it's just more lucrative for them sure
این فقط برای آنها سودآورتر است،
so they have always kind of pitted us
بنابراین آنها همیشه
against each other a little bit and they
کمی ما را در مقابل یکدیگر قرار داده اند و آنها
do it subtly
این کار را به طرز ماهرانه ای انجام می دهند
um they'll do it to me and my team and
، آنها این کار را خواهند کرد.  با من و تیمم و
then his team will do it to me and then
سپس تیم او این کار را با من انجام خواهد داد و سپس
my team will do it to him and his team
تیم من این کار را با او انجام خواهد داد و تیم او این کار را
will do it to him
با او انجام خواهد داد
and there was a moment where information
و یک لحظه اطلاعاتی
got leaked about this thing I was doing
در مورد این کاری که من انجام می دادم به بیرون درز کرد
and my team was like just so you know
و تیم من  مثل این که بدانی تو
you're your boy Tommy is is the rat and
پسرت هستی تامی موش است و
I had to
من مجبور شدم
it was the one time and Leanne said do
این کار را یک بار انجام دهم و لیان گفت
you think Tom would do that
فکر می کنی تام این کار را انجام دهد،
I said uh I don't know how Faith Works
گفتم اوه من نمی دانم ایمان چگونه کار می کند
like I'm not a super religious person
که من نیستم  یک فرد فوق العاده مذهبی
but I will tell you that I believe in
اما من به شما می گویم که من به
Tom and I don't think he did it and I
تام اعتقاد دارم و فکر نمی کنم او این کار را انجام داده باشد و من
will stand by that ignorantly
ناآگاهانه در کنار آن خواهم
and and I will and I will ride or die
ایستاد و خواهم کرد و با او سوار می شوم یا می میرم
with him because I cannot live in a
زیرا نمی توانم در
world where I don't trust him yeah if I
دنیایی زندگی کنم  من به او اعتماد ندارم بله، اگر به
don't trust him then I am so [\h__\h]
او اعتماد ندارم، پس من خیلی لعنتی هستم و اوه و او نبود، او
and uh and it wasn't him it wasn't him
نبود
and it was it's a cool feeling to know
و احساس جالبی بود که بدانید
that you could like
می توانید دوست داشته باشید
that you could blindly trust someone
که می توانید کورکورانه اعتماد کنید  کسی
blindly have faith in someone know that
کورکورانه به کسی ایمان دارد می داند که
they're they have your best interest at
او بهترین علاقه شما را در دل دارد،
but yeah it took me a while to get there
اما آره، مدتی طول کشید تا به آنجا برسم،
Rogan helped me get there because I
روگان به من کمک کرد تا به آنجا برسم زیرا
wasn't trusting him or Joey or Tommy or
به او یا جوی یا تامی یا
anyone I wasn't trusting anyone I'd
به کسی که نبودم اعتماد نداشتم.  اعتماد کردن به هرکسی من به
gotten in a bad thing and I just wasn't
اتفاق بدی افتاده بودم و به هیچ
trusting anybody
کس اعتماد نداشتم
Rogan was like yeah man we're trying to
روگان مثل این بود که بله، ما سعی می‌کنیم
be your [\h__\h] friend and I was like
دوست لعنتی تو باشیم و من مثل این بودم که
yeah I don't I don't need friends
بله، من به دوستان نیازی ندارم، نمی‌توانم
I couldn't understand what why Rogan was
نمی فهمم چرا روگان به
interested in me and I was I said to
من علاقه مند بود و به من گفته شد که از
like someone I was like is he gay like
کسی خوشم می آید که من شبیه آن
a nice guy he was just a nice guy
هستم
that'd be hilarious if Joe was sexually
آیا او همجنس گرا بود.  در
attracted to you this whole time this
تمام این مدت جذب شما از نظر جنسی به این
whole time is the reason he keeps
دلیل است که او مدام
inviting it back I would be more excited
آن را به عقب دعوت می کند. من هیجان زده تر می شدم
I would be more excited if just if he
اگر او
tried to kiss me on the lips once just
سعی می کرد یک بار فقط و فقط روی لب های من ببوسد
and just and then like in a Scotty
و سپس مانند یک
Scotty J way from Boogie Nights where
اسکاتی اسکاتی.  J way از Boogie Nights که در آن
he's like what do you like my car yeah
او مثل چیزی است که شما ماشین من را دوست دارید بله می دانید
you know nobody would believe that story
هیچ کس آن داستان را باور نمی کرد
no one yeah if I was Joe I would kiss
نه کسی بله اگر من جو بودم
dudes all the time and then be like and
همیشه دوستان را می بوسیدم و بعد مثل و بعد
then and then when they didn't kiss back
و بعد وقتی آنها نمی بوسیدند
oh you know no one ever believe you yeah
اوه میدونی هیچکس هیچوقت باورت نمیکنه آره
well when you trust people like that and
خوب وقتی به اینجور آدما اعتماد میکنی و اونها
they [\h__\h] you over that can really
تو رو لعنت میکنن که واقعا میتونه واقعا
you end up on a treadmill
بهت صدمه بزنه در نهایت روی تردمیل
in a hotel room
تو اتاق هتل
fighting with them you fight with them
باهاشون دعوا میکنی و همیشه باهاشون دعوا
all the time you fight with them all the
میکنی
you fight with them constantly
مدام با آنها دعوا می کنی
and it's and I and I I have this uh
و من و من این
thing like where I ruminate on an idea
چیزی را داریم مثل جایی که در مورد یک ایده نشخوار می کنم
and I can't get it out of my head and I
و نمی توانم آن را از ذهنم بیرون کنم و
hear the words they say and then I and
کلماتی را که می گویند می شنوم و بعد من و ...
so all in your head on a treadmill in
همه تو سرت روی تردمیل تو
your head just fighting just [\h__\h]
سرت فقط دعوا میکنی فقط
fighting and then yeah
دعوا میکنی و بعد آره
and then one day you get past it like
و بعد یه روز ازش رد میشی انگار
one day you just go huh [\h__\h] them I'm
یه روز رفتی لعنتشون کن من
not gonna let you give them real estate
نمیذارم بهشون ملک بدی
and then you just forget about them and
و بعد فقط  آنها را فراموش کن و
then they reach out and they'll try to
بعد آنها دستشان را دراز می کنند و سعی می کنند
be a dick or a bully because they're
قلدر یا قلدر باشند زیرا آنها
bullies they're bullies is what they are
قلدر هستند آنها قلدر هستند
don't ever forget it they're [\h__\h]
هرگز فراموش نکنید آنها قلدرهای لعنتی هستند
bullies and they got bullied it's not
و مورد قلدری قرار گرفتند اینطور نیست
their fault they got bullied
تقصیر آنهاست که مورد آزار و اذیت قرار گرفته اند
and then they try to Bull you and you
و بعد سعی می کنند تو را قلدری کنند و تو
don't have any connection anymore and
دیگر هیچ ارتباطی نداری و
you're like oh you can go [\h__\h] yourself
مثل اوه که می توانی برو به خودت لعنت بزنی، در
you can actually go [\h__\h] yourself you're
واقع می توانی برو به خودت لعنت بدهی، تو
not my boss you're not my wife you don't
رئیس من نیستی، تو همسر من نیستی  تو به
[\h__\h] me don't pay me get the [\h__\h] out of
من لعنتی نمی دهی به من پول نده از
my life
زندگی من بیرون برو،
but this kind of Mantra that you're not
اما این نوع مانترا که تو
weak you still want to be able to be
ضعیف نیستی، هنوز هم می خواهی بتوانید
fragile to the world and appear weak
در برابر دنیا شکننده باشید و ضعیف به نظر بیایید،
almost well I am I am I mean that's the
من هستم  منظورم این است که
problem is I think I am pretty [\h__\h]
مشکل این است که فکر می‌کنم خیلی
weak like I think I'm not the strongest
ضعیف هستم، مثل اینکه فکر می‌کنم قوی‌ترین
dude out there I have really thin skin
آدم بیرونی نیستم، پوست واقعاً نازکی دارم،
am I get my feelings hurt all the time
همیشه احساساتم آسیب می‌بینند،
yeah and so but like but it sucks when
آره و همینطور، اما دوست دارم، اما وقتی
you watch like your friend
تماشا می‌کنی بد است  مثل اینکه دوستت
see something in you that you go
چیزی در تو می بیند که تو می روی
or they go [\h__\h] him he's not paying
یا می روند به او فک می کنند او حواسش نیست لعنت به او بیا
[\h__\h] him let's just [\h__\h] him let's take
فقط به او لعنت بزنیم
look at me he's a drunk alcoholic and
بیایید پولش را برداریم.  الکلی و
you go oh no [\h__\h] I pay attention like
تو برو اوه نه عوضی، من توجه می کنم که
I'm I'm wide awake I'm here I'm working
من کاملا بیدار هستم، من اینجا هستم، من دارم کار می کنم، تو
well that's the tough thing about like
خوب نمی خواهی لعنتی کنی، این چیز سختی است که در مورد
you and Tom Segura you're at the top of
تو و تام سگورا هستی  در راس
your game on top of the world some of
بازی شما در بالای جهان، برخی از
the most famous comics in the world and
معروف ترین کمیک های جهان و
you could see money start to creep in
می توانید ببینید که پول شروع به خزش می کند
like uh business decisions yeah
مانند تصمیمات تجاری، بله،
I don't know it's a tough it's a tough
نمی دانم سخت است،
place it's really tough it's really
مکان سختی است، واقعاً سخت است.  واقعاً
tough work you know especially as we're
کار سختی است که می‌دانی، به خصوص وقتی که ما در حال رشد هستیم،
and and uh
و اوه
I'll tell you what it
من به شما می‌گویم چه چیزی را
I don't know how much I'm allowed to say
نمی‌دانم چقدر مجاز به گفتن هستم،
but I can tell you this
اما می‌توانم این را
with a business deal
با یک معامله تجاری به شما بگویم
where feelings were getting involved
که در آن احساسات درگیر بودند
and money was involved in that and the
و  پول در آن دخیل بود و
money was causing the feelings
پول باعث ایجاد احساسات شد
and one of us said
و یکی از ما
to the other person our feelings are
به طرف مقابل گفت احساسات ما
more important than the money so let's
مهمتر از پول است پس بیایید
just split the money and it was and it
فقط پول را تقسیم کنیم و بود و بود و بود و بود و شد
and it was it was really like a solid
واقعاً مانند یک
moment where I where both of us were
لحظه محکم که در آن من هر دوی ما
like that is how we should run this yeah
چنین بودیم، این است که چگونه باید اجرا کنیم بله این
that's the interesting things like with
چیزهای جالبی است مانند با
bands you have like
گروه هایی که شما مانند
popular bands that split and even yeah
گروه های محبوبی دارید که از هم جدا می شوند و حتی بله
even though it's clear that the
حتی اگر واضح است که
contribution is not even it's like uh
مشارکت حتی شبیه آن نیست  اوه،
there's a front man and all that kind of
یک نفر جلودار و همه چیزهای دیگر وجود دارد،
stuff but it's ultimately the right
اما در نهایت
thing to do to say [\h__\h] you to the money
کار درستی است که بگوییم
for the most part and prioritize the
در بیشتر قسمت‌ها به پول لعنتت می‌رسانم و احساسات را در اولویت قرار می‌دهیم،
feelings yeah especially because like
به خصوص چون
I couldn't do it without him he couldn't
من بدون او نمی‌توانستم این کار را انجام دهم، او نمی‌توانست.  این کار را
do it without me we do it separately
بدون من انجام می دهیم، ما این کار را جداگانه انجام می دهیم، ما
we'll have guest Bears on some will blow
مهمان خواهیم داشت. برخی از آنها منفجر می شوند،
up some won't you can never figure it
نمی توانی هرگز آن را
out but when we're together it does well
بفهمی، اما وقتی با هم هستیم، این کار به خوبی انجام می شود
and so we need each other for it to work
و بنابراین ما به یکدیگر نیاز داریم تا کار کند
and we've you know
و ما  می دانی
like I said we're on a handshake deal
همانطور که گفتم ما با دو خرس در حال دست دادن هستیم
with two bears and no one likes that
و هیچ کس آن را دوست ندارد،
but we're like hey
اما ما شبیه هی هستیم،
I mean we I don't like to the point
یعنی دوست نداریم تا
where like he'll call me and go yo we
جایی که او به من زنگ بزند و برود.
have a deal to do this for x amount are
معامله ای برای انجام این کار با مبلغ x دارید
you in and I go yeah
و من می روم بله، می
I'll go check the books I don't need to
روم کتاب ها را بررسی می کنم، نیازی به آن ندارم،
I don't I don't I know him I just know
نمی شناسم او را نمی شناسم، فقط
him yeah what do you love most about
او را می شناسم بله، چه چیزی را بیشتر دوست دارید  در مورد
Thompson
تامپسون
the we saw a gay couple one time this is
که یک بار یک زوج همجنسگرا دیدیم این
a good start and there was one guy was
شروع خوبی است و یک پسر
in khakis and one guy was in jean shorts
خاکی پوش بود و یک پسر با شلوارک جین
with a python around his neck yeah and
با یک مار پیتون به گردنش آره و
Tom goes if we were gay which one would
تام می رود اگر ما همجنسگرا بودیم
you be I said I'm [\h__\h] python yeah
شما کدامیک بودید من  گفت من دارم پیتون لعنتی می کنم آره
and he was like yeah I'm khaki and I go
و اون مثل اینکه آره من خاکی هستم و من میرم
really and he goes yeah that's why we
واقعا و اون میره آره به همین دلیل ما
work and he goes all relationship for
کار می کنیم و او تمام رابطه را برای
pythons and khakis and I went really and
پیتون و خاکی ادامه می دهد و من واقعا رفتم و
he goes look at you and Leanne who do
او می رود به تو و لیان نگاه کند که
you think you are going I'm Python and
فکر می کنی می روی من پایتون هستم و
he goes she's khaki and he goes me and
او می رود او خاکی است و او به من می رود و
push I go oh she's python he goes and
هل می دهد من برو اوه او مار پیتون است او می رود و
I'm khaki it'll always be khaki and
من خاکی هستم همیشه خاکی خواهد بود و
sometimes I'll have a relationship
گاهی اوقات من
around the python but it's I'm usually a
با مار پیتون رابطه برقرار می کنم  اما من معمولا
khaki yeah and I was like yeah I am a
خاکی هستم آره و مثل اینکه بله
little bit of a lunatic I'll tell you
کمی دیوانه هستم به شما می گویم
the one of the a moment
لحظه ای
that explains
که به
me and him the world will never see it
من و او توضیح می دهد که دنیا هرگز نخواهد دید این
was just a great moment we got stem
فقط یک لحظه عالی بود ما
cells with Rogan one weekend yep and one
یک روز آخر هفته با روگان سلول های بنیادی گرفتم، بله و یک
day
روز، و من
and I'd had surgery in my arm and Ty
در بازویم عمل کرده بودم و تای
didn't want to do it I was terrified and
نمی خواست این کار را انجام دهم، ترسیده بودم و
Tom just said just come out and meet up
تام فقط گفت بیا بیرون و
with us Tom knew he was going to make me
با ما ملاقات کن تام می دانست که قرار است این کار را انجام دهد.  مجبورم کن
get them and so
آنها را بگیرم و من
I got them and he
آنها را گرفتم و او می
you know Joe's there and so we're just
دانید که جو آنجاست و بنابراین ما فقط داریم
all talking yeah yeah yeah yeah and Tom
صحبت می کنیم بله بله بله بله و تام
can see that I'm spinning out a little
می تواند ببیند که من کمی بیرون می روم
and I get in the car and you know Tom's
و سوار ماشین می شوم و شما می دانید تام
got a Porsche so we're like right next
یک پورشه گرفتم بنابراین ما دقیقاً در کنار
to each other
هم هستیم
and I just want to feel if it's swollen
و من فقط می خواهم احساس کنم که آیا متورم است
and it is a little swollen because I
و کمی متورم است زیرا من تازه
just got an injection and then and Tom's
تزریق کردم و سپس و تام
driving and he's got his hand on the
رانندگی می کند و او دستش را روی
thing he just puts his hand on my arm
چیزی که گذاشته است گرفته است.  دستش را روی بازوی من گذاشت
and he goes you're okay he's just he's
و می رود تو حالت خوب است او فقط دارد
watching he knows me so well that he
تماشا می کند من را آنقدر خوب می شناسد که می
knows that I'm spinning out of control
داند من از کنترل خارج می شوم
he's like you're okay
او مثل اینکه تو خوب هستی
and then I was like and I felt okay I
و بعد من خوب بودم و احساس کردم
was like you're right I'm okay what the
خوب است  شما درست می گویید من خوبم
man that guy got so much love in him
دارم چه کار می کنم.  آیا
that dude did to create that dude he hit
آن شخص برای ایجاد آن شخص انجام داد، او
it out of the [\h__\h] park because he
آن را از پارک لعنتی بیرون زد، زیرا او
so much
آنقدر
uh love that he doesn't need
عشق دارد که
reciprocated like at all like he can
اصلاً نیازی به پاسخ متقابل ندارد، مثل اینکه
just love and then he feels good for him
فقط می تواند دوست داشته باشد و بعد احساس خوبی دارد که
to give and to like take care of someone
بدهد و دوست داشته باشد.  از کسی مراقبت کن
and like you know he started the whole
و مثل اینکه می دانی او همه چیز
birthday gift thing because and he
هدیه تولد را شروع کرد زیرا و
didn't need to he just was like hey man
نیازی به آن نداشت فقط مثل هی مرد بود که
I had this bike I thought you'd like it
من این دوچرخه را داشتم فکر می کردم دوستش داری
and then of course I've turned it into a
و البته من آن را به آن تبدیل کردم
[\h__\h] bit
کمی لعنتی
and now we're upside down I'm 120 upside
و حالا ما وارونه هستیم من 120 ساله هستم و
down on a [\h__\h] race car that we can't
در یک ماشین مسابقه ای لعنتی وارونه هستم که نمی توانیم
make our money back on I love it uh what
پول خود را با آن
I could go on and on about Joe Rogan Joe
برگردانیم.  و در مورد جو روگان جو
Rogan is the most selfless individual
روگان فداکارترین فردی است که
I've ever met he doesn't care if he has
تا به حال ملاقات کرده ام، برایش مهم نیست که
you on the podcast he wants you to be
شما را در پادکست داشته باشد،
the funniest person in the room he wants
او می خواهد که
you to be the smartest person in the
شما بامزه ترین فرد در اتاق باشید.
room let me tell you something Joe Rogan
اجازه بدهید چیزی به شما بگویم جو روگان
is 10 times smarter and funnier than me
10 برابر باهوش‌تر و بامزه‌تر از من است،
he wants you to shine he wants you he
او می‌خواهد تو بدرخشی او تو را می‌خواهد او می‌خواهد
wants to put you over to his fans he
شما را به طرفدارانش بسپارد، او
that [\h__\h] did not exist before he
که قبل از
started doing his podcast people didn't
شروع پادکستش وجود نداشت، مردم آن را به
share you with their fans no one was
اشتراک نمی‌گذاشتند.  تو با طرفدارانشون هیچکس
like Hey man come on on the road with me
مثل هی مرد بیا تو جاده با من اونها منو
they brought me on the road because they
آوردند تو جاده چون
wanted you to suck and they put you in
میخواستن تو بمکی و تو رو تو
bad scenarios Joe Rogan wanted you to
سناریوهای بد قرار میدن جو روگان میخواست تو
shine he gave he gave so many people
بدرخشی او به خیلی ها
beautiful gave them careers gave them
خوشگل داد  به آنها شغل داد به آنها
Joe could have looked at his podcast as
جو می توانست به پادکست خود به عنوان چیز او نگاه کند.
might be me might be I might talk over
ممکن است با مردم صحبت کند
people and not listen really well Joe
و خیلی خوب گوش ندهد، جو
had did the opposite now look I've tried
برعکس عمل کرده بود، حالا ببین من سعی کردم
to learn from Joe on my podcast and do
از جو در پادکستم یاد بگیرم و
the same that guy when you think about
همین کار را انجام دهم، وقتی به
it you name 10 of his friends I bet
آن فکر می کنی، 10 نفر از دوستانش را نام ببر، شرط می بندم که
eight of them are doing Arenas right now
هشت نفر از آنها هستند.  در حال انجام Arenas در حال حاضر
they're all doing theaters all his
همه آنها در حال انجام تئاتر هستند همه
friends do theaters all his friends do
دوستانش تئاتر انجام می دهند همه دوستانش
theaters he is he is just
تئاتر بازی می کنند او فقط
you know I I he and he won't accept this
شما می دانید من او و او این تعریف را نمی پذیرد
compliment I tried paying it to him uh
من سعی کردم آن را به او پرداخت کنم
in Austin when I was in Austin last well
در آستین زمانی که من بودم  در آستین،
he's not good at accepting compliments I
او در پذیرش تعارف خوب نیست، من
gave him a gift too and I say hey I need
هم به او هدیه دادم و می گویم هی، باید به
I need to show you I can't just tell you
شما نشان دهم، نمی توانم فقط این را به شما بگویم،
this because it's going to fall in deaf
زیرا این موضوع در گوش شما قرار می گیرد،
ears I need to give you a minute so you
باید یک دقیقه به شما بدهم  بنابراین تو
have something so you know that I think
چیزی داری تا بدانی که من
about you and I'm grateful for having
به تو فکر می کنم و از اینکه
you in my life a lot for many reasons I
تو را در زندگی ام دارم بسیار سپاسگزارم به دلایل زیادی من
have more friends in my life because of
دوستان بیشتری در زندگی ام دارم به خاطر تو
you he taught me how to trust people
او به من یاد داد چگونه دوباره به مردم اعتماد کنم
again I have a career because if you
من یک شغل دارم  چون اگر
have a major motion picture because of
به خاطر تو یک فیلم سینمایی بزرگ داشته باشی، من به خاطر تو
you I do Arenas because of you without
بدون
you in my life a lot of these these
تو در زندگی ام آرنا را انجام می دهم، بسیاری از این
things maybe never would have happened I
چیزها شاید هرگز اتفاق نمی افتاد، من هرگز
never would have told the machine on
روی صحنه به دستگاه نمی گفتم که نمی
stage I wouldn't have gotten I would
رسیدم.  من
have never started a podcast I wouldn't
هرگز پادکست را شروع نکرده ام، من
have three podcasts like I mean all
سه پادکست ندارم، یعنی همه
these things are are things he not just
این چیزها چیزهایی هستند که او نه فقط
he didn't just take me to the water one
یک بار مرا به آب برد
time and give me a drink he he gave me a
و به من نوشیدنی داد، او به من یک
machete and he said this is how I get to
قمه داد و گفت  اینگونه است که من به
the water you gotta put your own path
آب می رسم تو باید مسیر خودت را بگذاری
but just give me a heads up you can also
اما فقط به من سر بزن و
use my path whenever you want I mean he
هر وقت خواستی می توانی از مسیر من استفاده کنی منظورم این است که او
he is the most selfless individual he
فداکارترین فردی است که
will go down in history as one of the 10
به عنوان یکی از 10 نفر در تاریخ ثبت خواهد شد.
most important people in stand-up comedy
مهم ترین افراد در استندآپ کمدی
without a doubt he changed the game it
بدون شک او بازی را تغییر داد
didn't exist like this before him and uh
قبل از او اینطور نبود و
and he won't accept that compliment well
او این تعریف را نمی پذیرد خوب این
it's a gift you give him I can't tell
هدیه ای است که به او می دهید من نمی توانم به
you is it a dildo he was a dildo
شما بگویم آیا این یک  دیلدو او یک
double-sided dildo I go hey when you get
دیلدو دو طرفه بود من می روم هی وقتی
free time can we scissor [\h__\h] each other
وقت آزاد پیدا کردی می توانیم همدیگر را قیچی کنیم
uh you're happily married uh for 19
اوه شما 19 سال است که با خوشحالی ازدواج کرده اید
so I think you're a good man to ask how
بنابراین فکر می کنم شما مرد خوبی هستید که بپرسید
do you find love how do you find how do
چگونه عشق را پیدا می کنید  آیا می‌دانی چگونه
you date in order to find a love of your
قرار می‌گذاری تا عشقی از زندگیت را پیدا کنی
life of a lifetime this is gonna sound
که به نظر می‌رسد،
but don't
اما
don't tie yourself down meaning like
خودت را بند نده، به این معنا که
don't spend time
وقت خود را صرف
[\h__\h] with those little mini shrimp
لعنت کردن با آن میگوهای کوچک
and peeling them every night when you
و پوست کندن آنها نکن  هر شب وقتی می‌دانی
know you're looking for a lobster yeah
دنبال یک خرچنگ می‌گردی،
like and so I think what happens a lot
بله، و بنابراین من فکر می‌کنم چه اتفاقی می‌افتد، خیلی
of guys they just they're so busy and
از بچه‌ها فقط سرشان شلوغ است و
like just getting [\h__\h] and going from
دوست دارند از
here to here to here I was never that
اینجا به اینجا به اینجا بروند، من هرگز آن
guy I always wanted I always wanted to
مرد نبودم.  همیشه می خواستم من همیشه می خواستم
find someone who understood me I always
کسی را پیدا کنم که مرا درک کند من همیشه
wanted that and so you know granted I
این را می خواستم و بنابراین می دانید که من
haven't had sex with a lot of chicks but
با جوجه های زیادی رابطه جنسی نداشته ام اما
that's and it's and it's not by choice
این و این است و این از روی انتخاب نیست
I'm saying like maybe there was times I
من می گویم شاید بارهایی وجود داشته است که من
would have done it but I but I know that
این کار را انجام می‌دادم اما می‌دانم که
I was always looking for someone to
همیشه به دنبال کسی بودم که
figure out to get me and then and then I
بفهمد مرا به دست بیاورد و بعد و بعد
will say this when you know you know
این را می‌گویم وقتی بدانی می‌دانی وقتی می‌دانی می‌دانی
when you know you know when you think
وقتی فکر می‌کنی
there's I can't imagine a life without
وجود دارد، نمی‌توانم تصور کنم  زندگی بدون
this person
این شخص
that that happened to me and I can only
که برای من اتفاق افتاد و من فقط می توانم
say my experiences I had Leanne I loved
تجربیاتم را بگویم من لیان را داشتم دوستش داشتم و
her and I and I didn't even realize it
من و حتی متوجه نشدم و
and the second she dumped me I went oh
دومی که او مرا رها کرد رفتم اوه نه نه نه نه اوه
no no no no no oh I I don't get to live
من
a great life without her she's the thing
بدون او زندگی خوبی داشته باشم او چیزی است
that's going to give me a great life I
که به من یک زندگی عالی می دهد من
knew it Undisputed I went for a run and
می دانستم بدون چون و چرا رفتم دویدم و او مرا
uh she dumped me I went to my shower I
رها کرد رفتم دوش گرفتم
cried I went to Barnes Noble I bought
گریه کردم به بارنز نوبل رفتم
men from Venus women from Mars I've
مردهایی را از آن خریدم  زنان ونوس از مریخ من
watched Fight Club in my closet I didn't
باشگاه مبارزه را در کمدم تماشا کردم، مشروب نخوردم،
drink I drink a lot of Nyquil to sleep
مقدار زیادی نایکیل نوشیدم تا بخوابم
and then I went for a hike in Runyon
و سپس برای پیاده روی در Runyon Canyon رفتم.  در حال
was setting and I just said God if
تنظیم بود و من فقط گفتم خدایا اگر
you're listening
گوش می کنی،
just give me this check back I'll never
فقط این چک را به من پس بده، من هرگز
[\h__\h] it up this is the one I won't [\h__\h]
آن را لعنتی نمی کنم، این همان چیزی است که من آن را لعنتی نمی کنم،
it up I won't cheat I'm not gonna be a
تقلب نمی کنم، من
bad dude I want to have kids with her
آدم بدی نمی شوم  من می خواهم با او بچه داشته باشم،
I'll be there I'll be a great [\h__\h]
من آنجا خواهم بود، یک دوست لعنتی عالی خواهم بود،
dude I'll take her out on dates like
او را در قرار ملاقات هایی بیرون می برم، مثل اینکه
I'll love this chick
عاشق این جوجه خواهم بود و
and I got home and she was in my room in
به خانه برگشتم و او در اتاق من بود با
a sundress yeah and I was like oh [\h__\h]
یک سارافان آره و  من مثل اوه لعنت به
you I didn't know he was real yeah I was
تو بودم، نمی دانستم که او واقعی است، آره،
like [\h__\h] man give me like one more
مثل یک مرد مزخرف بودم، به من بده مثل یک
night let me give some strange tail real
شب دیگر، بگذار یک دم عجیب و غریب بدهم،
quick yeah before I commit forever but I
بله، قبل از اینکه برای همیشه متعهد شوم، اما
think when you know you know this is so
فکر می کنم وقتی می دانی که اینطور است
silly but I follow that in business
احمقانه است، اما من این را در تجارت دنبال می کنم،
like when you know you know and like my
مانند وقتی می دانید که می دانید و از
assistance with us and someone goes how
کمک من با ما خوشتان می آید و کسی می رود که چگونه
do you find a good assistant I go when
یک دستیار خوب پیدا کنید، من می روم وقتی می
you know you know like people will show
دانید که می دانید مانند مردم به شما نشان می دهند که
you who they are uh I can tell you when
آنها چه کسی هستند، می توانم به شما بگویم چه زمانی
I fell in love with my assistant
من عاشق دستیارم شدم که
we were doing a TV show and and that we
داشتیم یک برنامه تلویزیونی انجام می دادیم و اینکه
worked past dinner and all the dinner
بعد از شام کار کردیم و همه
places were closed and he just said hey
جاهای شام بسته بودند و او فقط گفت هی
I got like four meals I didn't know
من چهار وعده غذا خوردم نمی دانستم
which one you'd want so I got four
کدام یک را می خواهید پس من  چهار وعده
different meals for you I ordered them
غذای مختلف برای شما گرفتم، سفارش دادم آنها
they're up in your room and just let me
در اتاق شما هستند و فقط به من
know whichever you want I'll take care
بگویید هر کدام را که می خواهید، من
of the rest of them yeah and I was like
از بقیه آنها مراقبت خواهم کرد، بله و من مثل
oh that that dude thinks about other
اوه که آن شخص قبل از خودش به دیگران فکر می کند.
people before himself he didn't even get
حتی برای
himself dinner he just got me four
خودش شام هم نخورد، او فقط چهار وعده شام ​​برایم گرفت
dinners and I was like [\h__\h] yeah I did
و من مثل اینکه لعنتی آره،
the same thing with my social media
همین کار را با مدیر شبکه های اجتماعی ام انجام دادم،
the way she was operating was I was like
به روشی که او کار می کرد،
I feel like she's thinking about me yeah
احساس می کردم که او به من فکر می کند، بله
and we connected on so many levels on so
و با هم ارتباط برقرار کردیم.  سطوح بسیار زیادی در
many levels I could talk to her about
سطوح مختلف می‌توانستم با او در مورد
things and ideas I had and then I was
چیزها و ایده‌هایی که داشتم صحبت کنم و بعد
like okay I want her I want him I want
خوب بودم، او را می‌خواهم، او را می‌خواهم،
I think you I think it's got to be that
فکر می‌کنم تو، فکر می‌کنم
thing when you know you know and it can
وقتی بدانی که می‌دانی و  می تواند
be so simple as like
بسیار ساده باشد
like a personal trainer or like a jiu
مانند یک مربی شخصی یا مانند یک
jitsu class or like just where you go oh
کلاس جیو جیتسو یا مانند جایی که شما می روید اوه
I'm connecting right now but you have to
من در حال حاضر در حال اتصال هستم اما شما باید به
allow yourself to notice that person you
خودتان اجازه دهید که متوجه آن شخص شما شوید.
to put yourself out there and you have
برای اینکه خودت را بیرون بگذاری و باید
to be available for it
برای آن در دسترس باشی، می‌دانی
you know that's the hardest part is just
که سخت‌ترین بخش این است که
being available for it
برای آن در دسترس باشیم،
because so people so many people just
زیرا بسیاری از مردم فقط می‌خواهند فقط
want to be busy just dating I just want
مشغول قرار ملاقات باشند، من فقط می‌خواهم
to have someone in my life I don't want
کسی را در زندگی‌ام داشته باشم.  نمی خواهم
to be bored I don't want to what if I
حوصله کنم نمی خواهم چه کنم اگر
die alone I don't wanna I like just be
تنها بمیرم نمی خواهم دوست دارم فقط
available for it uh what is it you said
برای آن در دسترس باشم آه این چیست که گفتی
peeling the baby shrimp yeah when you
پوست میگو را پوست کندن بله وقتی
could be having a lobster
ممکن است یک خرچنگ داشته باشید
yeah
بله
Lobster's still a lot of work I have to
خرچنگ هنوز یک  خیلی کار دارم باید
say yeah but well yeah but it's Lobster
بگم آره ولی خب آره اما این خرچنگ هست
this is a [\h__\h] baby shrimp or like
این یه بچه میگوی لعنتی یا شبیه اونه
and you ever guess you ever get the ones
و شما همیشه حدس میزنید که اونهایی رو
in Brazil where you just go [\h__\h] eat
در برزیل میگیرید که فقط میری لعنتی
the shell I don't care anymore
اون صدف رو بخوری من مثل من دیگه برام مهم نیست.
like I'm so [\h__\h] hungry you just
خیلی گرسنه ام لعنتی، فقط یک
handful of lobster like it's popcorn or
مشت خرچنگ مثل ذرت بو داده یا
maybe shrimp like it's popcorn
شاید میگو مثل ذرت بو داده است.
to successful marriage
ازدواج موفق
what do uh women want or a Crusher oh
چه چیزی را زنان می خواهند یا یک سنگ شکن اوه
[\h__\h] that's I'm the wrong guy to answer
لعنتی این است که من اشتباه می کنم که پاسخ می دهم که
that I think how to make love to a woman
فکر می کنم چگونه با یک زن عشق ورزی کنم نوشته
by Bert Kreischer how do you make
برت کریشر
yeah uh
اوه
I go down on her first
من اول به او می روم
make sure she has an orgasm yeah and
مطمئن می شوم که او به ارگاسم رسیده است بله و
then I get my turn and that's over
سپس من نوبت به من می رسد و این
pretty quick
خیلی سریع تمام می شود،
it's like it's like your ears pierced it
مثل این است که گوش های شما سوراخ شده است،
doesn't feel a little prick and it's
احساس نمی کند که او کمی خراشیده شود و
over
تمام شده است
I don't know if I've done a great job
من نمی دانم  اگر کار بزرگی انجام داده باشم که
keeping her happy I think I keep her
او را راضی نگه داشته باشم، فکر می کنم او را
interested like I think I I I
علاقه مند نگه می دارم، فکر می کنم من او را
keep her occupied like I'm like a little
مشغول نگه می دارم،
bit of a rodeo clown like I don't know I
مثل یک دلقک کوچولو که نمی
mean like I I know we're happy right now
دانم.  در حال حاضر خوشحالم می
I know we're really happy
دانم که ما واقعاً خوشحالیم،
but I don't know if I ever did
اما نمی دانم آیا تا به حال
as good a job as she did like she's
کارم را به خوبی او انجام داده ام، مثل
always been
همیشه که
like she's always been a gangster like
همیشه یک گانگستر بوده است.
she does it all she does everything like
همه چیز مثل
[\h__\h] everything and she loves it she
لعنت کردن به همه چیز و او آن را دوست دارد، او
just does it and then she shows Love For
فقط این کار را انجام می دهد و سپس
You by taking care of you and so like I
با مراقبت از تو عشق به تو را نشان می دهد و مثل اینکه من
have a lot of time just been this like
زمان زیادی دارم، فقط
almost like step and repeat husband
مثل قدم زدن و شوهر تکراری بودم
where it's like I come in to take a
که انگار من وارد شدم  یه
picture like hey money Tuesday I'm all
عکس بگیر مثل هی پول سه شنبه حالم
right I'm on the road Wednesday take
خوبه من در جاده هستم چهارشنبه در راه هستم
care guys or like a travel channel I
بچه ها مراقب باشید یا لایک کانال مسافرتی من
lived for two weeks at a time I left for
دو هفته زندگی کردم در زمانی که
the movie for three months so like I
سه ماه برای فیلم رفتم پس مثل اینکه
don't know that I've ever done
نمی دانم  که من تا به حال
a bang-up job
یک کار هولناک انجام داده‌ام،
I buy it like I go I remember one time I
آن را می‌خرم که می‌روم، یادم می‌آید یک بار انگار به
was just like I don't cheat on her I
او خیانت نمی‌کنم، او را
don't hit her I don't yell at her I'm a
نمی‌زنم، سرش فریاد نمی‌زنم، من
pretty good fighter I'm a really good
زیبا هستم  جنگنده خوب من یک جنگنده واقعاً خوب هستم،
fighter like like I'm good at like going
مثل اینکه در رفتن مثل رفتن خوب هستم
like Hey we're on the same team Oh you
هی ما در یک تیم هستیم اوه
mean de-escalation I'm really good at
یعنی تنش زدایی من واقعاً خوب هستم
like I'm very self I'm very accountable
مثل اینکه خیلی خودم هستم. خیلی پاسخگو هستم
I'm very self-correcting like if if
من خیلی خودم را تصحیح می کنم، مثلاً اگر
we're in a fight and she points
ما در حال دعوا هستیم و او به
something out and I go oh you're right I
چیزی اشاره می کند و من می روم اوه شما درست می گویید من می روم به
go [\h__\h] you right about that you're
شما که درست می گویید که شما
right you're totally wrong oh in the
درست می گویید شما کاملاً در اشتباه هستید اوه در این
moment in the moment I'm really good at
لحظه  لحظه ای که من واقعاً در این کار خوب هستم
huh and my wife's not she's not a good
و همسرم نه، او عذرخواهی خوبی نیست،
apologizer like she needs to sleep on an
مثلاً باید با
apology and then she can do it I can
عذرخواهی بخوابد و بعد بتواند این کار را انجام دهد،
apologize in the moment if I realize I'm
اگر متوجه شدم اشتباه می کنم و دارم می توانم همان لحظه عذرخواهی کنم.
wrong and I'm really quick to find my
خیلی سریع عیب خودم را پیدا کردم،
fault yeah I look for my fault because I
بله، به دنبال عیب خودم می‌گردم، زیرا می‌روم به
go tell me what I did
من بگو چه کار
adversely as a parent
بدی به عنوان یک پدر و مادر انجام داده‌ام،
I have pulled my daughters aside and
دخترانم را کنار کشیده‌ام و
been like yo that wasn't you
مثل تو بوده‌ام که تو نبودی
that was Mom yeah I'm giving you a heads
که مامان بودی، بله، دارم به تو سر می‌زنم.
up because I don't want because I got
بالا، چون نمی‌خواهم، چون در
really confused as a kid because my dad
بچگی واقعاً گیج شده‌ام، زیرا پدرم
always made sure I knew I was wrong
همیشه مطمئن می‌شود که من اشتباه می‌کنم
and sometimes I wasn't yeah and then as
و گاهی اوقات بله نمی‌دانم، و بعد در
a kid you kind of [\h__\h] up you're like
کودکی به نوعی لعنتی می‌کردی که
well how do I know if I'm wrong and I
خوب می‌شوی.  می‌دانم که اگر اشتباه می‌کنم و
think that raises so I was really good
فکر می‌کنم این افزایش‌ها را افزایش می‌دهد، بنابراین من واقعاً خوب بودم که
with my girls going like yo
دخترانم مانند شما رفتار کنند
and then and then parenting Georgia
و سپس والدین در جورجیا
taught me a lot about self-correcting
چیزهای زیادی در مورد اصلاح
self-correcting was that my oldest
خود اصلاحی به من آموخت این بود که بزرگ‌ترین
I'd only if I parented like my dad
من فقط اگر  مثل پدرم پدر و
parented like just like Raise Your Voice
مادر شد مثل صدایت را بلند کن
get up to here that's it no that doesn't
تا اینجا را بلند کن که اینطوری نیست که
have goddamn leashes on the collars on
لعنتی نیست، آره چطور سگ ها قلاده های گردنشان را ندارند
and so with Georgia I had to learn
و بنابراین با جورجیا مجبور شدم از
through therapy
طریق آن یاد بگیرم  درمان
that if if the if the consequence is
که اگر نتیجه اگر اینجاست
and it and the highest it goes is here
و بالاترین نتیجه اینجاست،
then why the [\h__\h] wouldn't they lie and
پس چرا لعنتی دروغ نمی گویند و
do everything because they go well I
همه کارها را انجام نمی دهند چون خوب پیش می روند، من می
know what it's like to hear but if you
دانم شنیدن چه حالی دارد، اما اگر
can vary your consequence with a child
می توانی نتیجه خود را با  یک کودک
and find some conversation in it then
و یک مکالمه در آن پیدا کنید، سپس
all of a sudden they're like well [\h__\h]
ناگهان آنها مثل این هستند که خوب لعنتی
well I don't want to lie cause this does
خوب، من نمی خواهم دروغ بگویم، زیرا این باعث می شود که این کار
this does suck like I like this I like
مثل این است که من این را دوست دارم من دوست دارم
where we talk and he says write a
جایی که ما صحبت می کنیم و او می گوید
thousand words on why driving around
هزار کلمه بنویس  چرا دور زدن
your kids in a car kids in a car is bad
بچه‌هایتان در ماشین بچه‌ها در ماشین بد است،
so threaten extreme violence every once
بنابراین هر چند وقت یک‌بار به خشونت شدید تهدید کنید،
in a while just to yeah let them know
فقط به آنها بگویید که
the dog can [\h__\h] bite yeah the dog
سگ می‌تواند گاز بگیرد، بله، سگ
can bark the dog can bite but if you pet
می‌تواند پارس کند، سگ می‌تواند گاز بگیرد، اما اگر
him on his belly he'll wag its tail yeah
او را به او نوازش کنید.  او دمش را تکان می‌دهد، بله، آیا
uh do you worry about being away too
شما نگران دوری بیش از
much I mean you're one of the most
حد هستید، منظورم این است که شما یکی از
creative content pushers and creators
خلاق‌ترین تولیدکنندگان محتوا و تولیدکنندگان محتوا هستید،
out there you're just constantly
فقط دائماً در
innovating constantly putting stuff out
حال نوآوری هستید و دائماً چیزهایی را بیرون می‌آورید،
there but do you worry that pulls you
اما آیا نگران هستید که باعث شود
away from like uh the mundane experience
از تجربه دنیوی
of Life yeah that can bring contentment
زندگی دور می شوی بله که می تواند رضایت
and happiness yeah I feel like sometimes
و شادی به ارمغان بیاورد بله احساس می کنم گاهی اوقات
it cannibalizes your real life where you
زندگی واقعی شما را آدم خوار می کند جایی که
start going you start thinking in promo
شروع به رفتن می کنید در
videos or you start looking at a
فیلم های تبلیغاتی فکر می کنید یا به
vacation as a bit Yeah like we should go
تعطیلات مانند ما نگاه می کنید.  باید
ziplining
زیپلینگ بزنی
why don't you do ah what shoes you wear
چرا نمی‌کنی آه چه کفشی می‌پوشی
or not like it can it can definitely
یا دوستش نداری می‌تواند قطعاً می‌تواند
cannibalize your life
زندگی شما را آدم‌خوار کند.
started saying stuff like dad hits mom
گفتن جملاتی مثل بابا به مامان ضربه میزنه
whoa guys they're like no put your phone
بچه ها مثل نه گوشیت رو
away yeah dab less boys and I'm like
بذار کنار آره پسرها رو کم کن و من مثل اینکه آره اوه اوه چیه اوم
online and all the everything you've
چه چیزهایی هست.  شما
learned you're kind of like the the Mr
آموخته اید که به نوعی شبیه آقای
Beast of Comedy just the innovating
هیولای کمدی هستید، فقط
in terms of how to promote stuff in
از نظر نحوه تبلیغ چیزها از نظر
terms of how to present stuff across the
نحوه ارائه مطالب در
different social media and across
رسانه های اجتماعی مختلف و در
YouTube podcasts all that stuff
پادکست های YouTube، تمام آن چیزها،
I think the number one thing is don't be
من فکر می کنم تعداد آنها، مدام نوآوری می کنید.  یک چیز این است که از مکیدن نترسید
no one sees the [\h__\h] the socks
هیچ کس چیزهای بدی را نمی بیند که جوراب ها
doesn't get views I just guess forgot
بازدید نمی کنند فقط حدس می زنم فراموش کردم
yeah it gets forgotten the good stuff
بله چیزهای خوبی که
they remember and then that's all they
به یاد می آورند فراموش می شود و سپس این همه چیزهایی است
bring up the stuff that sucks just goes
که آنها چیزهای بد را مطرح می کنند.
away and they're like oh yeah did you do
آنها مثل اوه، بله، آیا شما این کار را کردید،
that I don't even think I saw that [\h__\h]
من حتی فکر نمی کنم من آن را دیدم لعنت به
it who cares yeah you know it's like
کسی که اهمیت می دهد، بله، شما می دانید که مثل این است که
it's like I watched uh one of my
من تماشا کرده ام، یکی از
favorite stories about this is uh
داستان های مورد علاقه من در مورد این،
a guy named uh Sean Patton
اوه مردی به نام شان پاتون
I was explaining Instagram stories to
بود.  توضیح دادن استوری های اینستاگرام به
him and Ari and Mark Norman and I was
او و آری و مارک نورمن و من
explaining that you can now sell tickets
توضیح می دادم که اکنون می توانید
on Instagram stories it was back when
در استوری های اینستاگرام بلیط بفروشید، برگشته بود که
they swiped up instead of tap the button
به جای ضربه زدن روی دکمه
swipe up
swipe up بالا کشیدند
and they didn't understand it and I said
و متوجه نشدند و من گفتم
let me show you and I put up tickets for
اجازه بدهید نشان بدهم.  من و شما بلیت‌ها را برای فروش گذاشتیم
and I said you know hey guys swipe up
و گفتم می‌دانید هی بچه‌ها انگشتتان را بالا بکشید
and then I just showed him in 10 minutes
و بعد من فقط در عرض 10 دقیقه به او نشان دادم که
look there's so many people swipes up
تعداد زیادی نفر بالا می‌روند
it's 145 people it's a lot of people to
و 145 نفر هستند که افراد زیادی
buy tickets for a [\h__\h] comedy club
برای یک کلوپ کمدی لعنتی بلیط می‌خرند.
and they were like whoa
آنها مثل او بودند
and they're like what do you do stories
و آنها مثل این هستند که شما چه کار می کنید داستان هایی
about go find anything who gives a [\h__\h]
در مورد آنها بروید هر چیزی را پیدا کنید که
just anything and some things work some
فقط هر چیزی را به دردسر می اندازد و بعضی چیزها جواب می دهند بعضی
things don't
چیزها کار نمی کنند
and I watched Sean Patton shout out to
و من تماشا کردم که شان پاتون به شان پاتون فریاد می زد و
Sean Patton try for about 15 minutes to
سعی کرد حدود 15 دقیقه
do an Instagram story about uh his cup
انجام دهد.  یک استوری اینستاگرام در مورد اوه اوه فنجان
of tea he was making a cup of tea and he
چایش داشت یک فنجان چای درست می کرد و داشت
was making and he kept going hey okay
درست می کرد و به راهش ادامه می داد هی باشه
hold on [\h__\h] hold on to me yeah I was
لعنتی نگهم دار آره داشتم
filming him from the couch yeah I was
از روی کاناپه ازش فیلم می گرفتم آره داشتم از
filming all these attacks the whole
تمام این حملات فیلم می گرفتم
thing yeah I filmed every single one of
چیزی که بله، من از هر یک از
my like 15 different stories of him
15 داستان مختلف خود فیلم گرفتم که
trying to do that I had 145 000 views on
سعی می کرد انجامش دهم که من 145000 بازدید از
each story he never posted it
هر استوری داشتم که او هرگز آن را پست نکرد،
he never posted it and I was like I was
هرگز آن را پست نکرد و من
like man if he had just posted that one
مثل یک مرد بودم اگر او همین یکی را پست کرده بود.
he never posted anything in his stories
او هرگز چیزی در استوری هایش پست نکرد،
yeah that one 145 5 000 people would
بله، یک 145 5000 نفر
have gone to a story to see that cup of
به یک استوری می رفتند تا ببینند که آن فنجان
tea being made and see which one he
چای درست می شود و ببینند که
finally went with and so sometimes I
بالاخره با کدام یک رفت و بنابراین گاهی اوقات
think the biggest mistake you can make
فکر می کنم بزرگترین اشتباهی که می توانید انجام دهید
is just not doing it just do it just
این است که ندهید.  با انجام این کار، فقط آن را انجام دهید، فقط آن را
post it turn the camera on the idea will
ارسال کنید، دوربین را روشن کنید، ایده
show up and that that's the number one
ظاهر می شود و این اولین
thing you just turn the camera on and
چیزی است که فقط دوربین را روشن می کنید و
it'll come up you'll figure it out you
ظاهر می شود، متوجه خواهید شد که
do multiple takes or no maybe I do three
چندین عکس را انجام می دهید یا نه، شاید من  سه تا لایک کن
like and I'm talking even like in the
و من دارم حرف می زنم حتی مثل
dance video I did where I did the
ویدیوی رقصی که در جایی که
hip-hop dance I did two takes on that
رقص هیپ هاپ انجام دادم،
um when I had the marching band kind of
وقتی که گروه راهپیمایی در
my house I did two takes on that
خانه من بود، دو تا اجرا انجام دادم.
um once you start doing more takes you
شروع به انجام کارهای بیشتر طول می‌کشد که
lose the fun of it I think and uh
لذت آن را از دست می‌دهی، فکر می‌کنم و اوه، و
and then the fun ones I mean my favorite
سپس آن‌های سرگرم‌کننده که منظورم آن است که مورد علاقه‌ام است که
one I've ever done without a doubt my
تا به حال انجام داده‌ام، بدون شک
favorite promo I've ever done
تبلیغ مورد علاقه‌ای که تا به حال انجام داده‌ام
is uh
این است که اوه
I needed they added a second show in
من نیاز داشتم که نمایش دومی را اضافه کنند.
some City and uh and
چند شهر و اوه و
and they had a second show like Friday
و آنها یک نمایش دوم داشتند مثل جمعه
and Saturday and our third show and I
و شنبه و سومین برنامه ما و من
said I they just told me I was like [\h__\h]
گفتم فقط به من گفتند که لعنتی هستم
I'm leaving like tomorrow I need to sell
مثل فردا می روم که باید
tickets so I said real quick girls meet
بلیط بفروشم بنابراین گفتم دختران سریع واقعی با
me outside and lands like girls are
من ملاقات می کنند.  بیرون و زمین‌هایی مثل دخترانی که
doing homework I'm gonna take five
مشغول انجام تکالیف هستند، پنج
seconds I put on a speedo I got the
ثانیه طول می‌کشم، یک اسپیدو گذاشتم،
American flag I gave Isla the hose I
پرچم آمریکا را گرفتم، شلنگ را به ایلا دادم،
Georgia the Drone and I just had Georgia
دمنده برگ را به لیان دادم و به جورجیا هواپیمای بدون سرنشین را دادم و همین الان از جورجیا
drone it back to reveal the leaf blower
آن را با پهپاد پس گرفتم.  برای فاش کردن دمنده برگ
and this the mist you were seeing was
و این غباری که شما می دیدید
coming from Isla and Leanne yeah I'm in
از ایسلا می آمد و لیان آره من سوار
a speedo with American flag I have Bob
سرعتی با پرچم آمریکا هستم باب
Seger playing rambling Grambling man
سیگر دارم بازی می کند گرامبلینگ مرد
yeah
آره
and and that night Larry the Cable Guy
و آن شب لری کیبل گای
texted me and he goes this is [\h__\h]
به من پیام داد و او می رود.  این یک
genius and I was like it was just and it
نابغه ی لعنتی است و من مثل آن بودم و
was just like yo just let's just shoot
مثل این بود که فقط بیایید به
something who gives a [\h__\h]
چیزی شلیک کنیم که لعنت به چیزی مثل
like just shoot something just just just
شلیک به چیزی فقط فقط
say something and and put a little just
یک چیزی بگو و و کمی فقط
do a little movement into it and and
یک حرکت کوچک در آن انجام دهیم و  من
those are my back and that was I used to
پشتم هستم و قبلا بودم
be I watched a bunch of my promo Clips
کلیپ های تبلیغاتی ام را نگاه کردم آن
back from back in the day I used to be
روزها
really good now it's like
خیلی خوب بودم الان مثل اینکه دارم خیلی
I'm promoting so [\h__\h] many things I'm
چیزها را تبلیغ می کنم لعنتی خیلی چیزها را می کنم
just like I'm almost like I'm exhausted
مثل اینکه
about my promotions
از تبلیغاتم خسته شده‌ام،
yeah because you know the the well can
بله، چون می‌دانید که چاه می‌تواند
dry up in terms of ideas yeah and it's
از نظر ایده‌ها خشک شود، بله، و
like how many times am I going to show a
مثل این است که چند بار می‌خواهم عکسی از الاغم نشان دهم که
picture of my ass my ass smells really
الاغم بوی خیلی
good that's whatever my ass is on
خوبی می‌دهد، هر چیزی که الاغم روی آن باشد.
Instagram [\h__\h] million views
اینستاگرام لعنتی میلیون بازدید
guaranteed a million views your ass and
تضمین یک میلیون بازدید از الاغ و
and and and inner and it's and it's an
و و و و درونی شما و این است و این یک
active post like people are like I did
پست فعال است مانند مردم مانند من
the best one I did the other day was
بهترین کاری را که روز قبل انجام دادم
where I superimposed my ass on my front
جایی بود که الاغم را روی جلوی خود قرار دادم
and it just looked beautiful yeah no
و فقط زیبا به نظر می رسید  بله بدون
views
بازدید آه این چیزی است که بله
is that what it was yeah I think so but
من فکر می کنم اما
like but yeah my ass like I'm I'm in a
دوست دارم اما آره الاغ من مثل من
place right now where I am promoting
در حال حاضر در جایی هستم که در آن تبلیغ می کنم.
promoting this movie until it goes to a
این فیلم را تبلیغ خواهم کرد.  به یک
streamer I'll be promoting it uh
پخش کننده می رود من آن را تبلیغ خواهم کرد اوه
shamelessly I'm proud of it I I had a
بی شرمانه من به آن افتخار می کنم من از
great time shooting it it's in theaters
فیلمبرداری آن لذت بردم در سینماها
it'll be on video on demand it'll be on
در صورت تقاضا به صورت ویدیویی خواهد بود در
a streamer I'm sure I don't know but I'm
یک پخش کننده خواهد بود مطمئن هستم که این کار را نمی کنم  نمی دانم اما
sure I'm promoting fully loaded My
مطمئن هستم که
Summer Festival with 19 different Comics
جشنواره تابستانی من را با 19 کمیک مختلف تبلیغ می کنم.
I'm promoting the top soft World Tour
دارم تور جهانی نرم برتر را
that starts again this fall I'm
که پاییز امسال دوباره شروع می شود
promoting my cruise the fully loaded
تبلیغ می کنم.
Cruise I'm promoting Red Rocks I'm
Rocks من
promoting so many things
چیزهای زیادی را تبلیغ می کنم
that today was the very first time in my
که امروز اولین بار در کارم بود
where I said in January I'm going to
که در ژانویه گفتم می خواهم
take a break I'm going to take a break
استراحت کنم
and go like hey man let's let's get your
و مانند هی مرد بیایید قلب آرام شما را بدست آوریم.  آره بیایید
get some sleep
کمی بخوابیم بیایید بیایید
let's let's maybe take off like three
سه
months from drinking like that's just
ماه از نوشیدن الکل دور شویم، مثل این است که
really like slow it down and and also
سرعتش را کم کنید و همچنین
not think when you're thinking in promo
فکر نکنید وقتی در تبلیغات مدام فکر می کنید
it it can be a little exhaust I mean you
ممکن است کمی خسته کننده باشد.
think you think it's exhausting to look
فکر می کنید
at my feed it's exhausting to be my feed
دیدن فید من خسته کننده است، خوراک من بودن طاقت فرسا است
I'm my feed
من فید من
sometimes less is more
گاهی اوقات کمتر است بیشتر
but one of the things that nope one of
اما یکی از چیزهایی که نه یکی از
the things that inspires me about Rogan
چیزهایی که در مورد روگان به من الهام می دهد
is um
این است که
he almost never does this kind of stuff
او تقریباً هرگز انجام نمی دهد.  این جور چیزها
yeah yeah and how suddenly does this
بله بله و چقدر ناگهانی این پادکست انجام می شود
podcast because you write less is more
زیرا شما کمتر می نویسید بیشتر است که چگونه
how what does he do it like once a month
او این کار را یک بار در ماه انجام می دهد بله
yeah no he does it three times a [\h__\h]
نه او آن را سه بار در هفته انجام می دهد
week yeah
بله
more is more is perfect but for example
بیشتر است عالی است اما برای مثال
when he does like a story or something
وقتی انجام می دهد  مثل یک داستان یا چیزی
like this he does one take
شبیه به این که او انجام می دهد یک جورایی
it's kind of shitty it's the same day
مزخرف است، همان روز است که
it's the same it's elk with a bunch of
گوزن با یک دسته
jalapenos a knife that he had sent to
جالاپنو یک چاقو که
him by a [\h__\h] knife maker and him
توسط یک چاقوساز لعنتی برایش فرستاده بود و او می
going look at this look at this Traeger
رود به این نگاه نگاه کند.  این
smoker I reverse seared this this is
سیگاری Traeger من معکوس سرخ کردم این چیزی است که
what's great look at this I'm about to
عالی است نگاه کنید به این که من می خواهم
put in the butter and like this is
در کره بریزم و مثل این کره ای است که
right with guys like Rogan when he does
با علف تغذیه می شود این شیر واقعاً تستوسترون من را افزایش می دهد.
do a story if they're a little precious
اگر کمی باارزش هستند، داستانی می‌سازد،
yeah and there's I don't think he's he's
بله، و فکر نمی‌کنم او
ever done a second take a name of those
تا به حال این داستان‌ها را انجام داده باشد، اسمی از آن
stories no it is you have to really
داستان‌ها بیاورید، نه، این است که شما واقعاً باید
admire that like uh if the shot is
آن را تحسین کنید، مثلاً اگر عکس در
framed poorly if the audio sucks doesn't
کادر ضعیفی باشد، اگر  صدا مهم نیست،
matter do you remember when he this is
یادت می‌آید وقتی او
like like I can get in the Weeds on
مثل من می‌توانم وارد علف‌های هرز در
Rogan but and especially when it's
روگان شوم، اما و مخصوصاً وقتی
Instagram do you remember when he got
اینستاگرام است، به یاد می‌آوری زمانی که او
his Polar Plunge and he couldn't sit in
Polar Plunge خود را گرفت و نتوانست در
a minute and then the next day and then
یک دقیقه بنشیند و سپس  روز بعد و بعد
he must have gotten it on the internet
باید آن را در اینترنت دریافت کرده باشد،
bad yeah he must have gotten it bad yeah
بله، حتما بد شده است، بله
the next day he sat in for 20 minutes
روز بعد او 20 دقیقه در آنجا نشست
and he lowered his core temperature by
و دمای هسته خود را
like two degrees and it took him like a
حدود دو درجه کاهش داد و یک
month to get that back yeah that is that
ماه طول کشید تا به آن برسد.  برگشت آره اون
[\h__\h] man what an interesting you know
مرد لعنتی چه جالب میدونی
what I told you at the beginning we were
چی بهت گفتم اولش
just talking
فقط داشتیم حرف میزدیم دوست دارم
I like I really enjoy I draw inspiration
خیلی لذت میبرم
for men I'm not like um
از مردها الهام میگیرم مثل
you David Goggins cam Hanes
تو نیستم دیوید گوگینز cam Hanes
um Andrew heberman huberman I love uh uh
um Andrew Heberman Huberman من عاشقشم  اوه اوه اوه
uh [\h__\h] I mean there's so many guys
لعنتی منظورم اینه که پسرای زیادی
like that Rogan you know Tim Kennedy
مثل اون روگان هستن که تیم کندی رو میشناسی
like there are a lot of guys that are
مثل خیلی از بچه ها هستن که
like just very different men than me and
با من خیلی فرق دارن و
I love Jocko willnick like I love
من جوکو ویلنیک رو دوست دارم مثل اینکه
I love reading their stuff or listening
دوست دارم مطالبشون رو بخونم یا
to their audio books or what listen to
بهشون گوش بدم  کتاب های صوتی یا چه چیزی به پادکست آنها گوش می دهم
their podcast because I'm so not like
زیرا من اینطور نیستم
that but that for me when I add a little
اما برای من وقتی
bit of that in my life like I remember
کمی از آن را به زندگی ام اضافه می کنم مانند یادم می آید که رفتی
you went I don't know what you were
نمی دانم چه می
doing
کردی
but you were walking us through your day
اما داشتی ما را راه می دادی  در طول روز شما
and it was so
و آنقدر
fascinating
جذاب بود که
it was like it was like I ran eight
انگار
miles today I listened to an audiobook I
امروز هشت مایل دویدم، به یک کتاب صوتی گوش دادم که
was running eight miles and then I came
هشت مایل می دویدم و سپس آمدم و
and I worked for about three hours
حدود سه ساعت به طور
straight on AI stuff and I'm like and I
مستقیم روی چیزهای هوش مصنوعی کار کردم.  من
was like wait you sat at a desk like you
مثل این بودم که صبر کن تو پشت میز نشستی مثل
like sat at a desk and like and I I
اینکه پشت میز نشستی و دوست داشتم و من
actually
در واقع
I wouldn't even know what to do I would
حتی نمی‌دانستم چه کار کنم،
start doing crafts like I would like
شروع به کاردستی می‌کردم، مثل اینکه دوست دارم
that you went I was like is your
تو بروی، مثل اینکه
computer like yeah have you sat for like
کامپیوترت مثل آره است.  آیا شما
four hours
چهار ساعت نشسته اید و
focused on a single task me yeah no no
روی یک کار متمرکز شده اید من بله نه آه من به
oh I have a hard time sleeping for four
سختی چهار
hours yeah like I I don't have that I I
ساعت می خوابم بله مثل من ندارم که من
don't have a brain that like I really
مغزی ندارم که
admired it when I listened to you do it
وقتی گوش می کردم واقعاً آن را تحسین می کردم  به تو این کار را بکن
because then you were like you're taught
چون آن وقت انگار به تو یاد داده اند
you were fasting at the time you're
در زمانی که
doing your fast and then you talk about
روزه ات را می خوانی روزه گرفته ای و بعد در مورد
what you ate and I was jealous I wanted
چیزی که خوردی صحبت می کنی و من حسادت می کردم که می خواستم
to be able to be like that and I think
اینطور باشم و فکر می کنم
at that time we started I think you're
در  زمانی که ما شروع کردیم، فکر می‌کنم شما در حال
doing maybe bone broth or something and
انجام دادن آبگوشت استخوان یا چیز دیگری هستید و
we started doing bone broth
ما شروع کردیم به انجام دادن آبگوشت استخوان
pretty religiously and adding that into
کاملاً مذهبی و اضافه کردن آن به
a fast because I was like
روزه‌داری، زیرا من اینطوری بودم که
it does for someone like me it does feel
برای کسی مثل من این کار را انجام می‌داد.
life so integrating a little bit of a
آنقدر به زندگی ادغام می شود که کمی
way of being from another person that
از یک شخص دیگر بودن را ادغام می کند که
you're not like yeah like like uh like
شما مثل آره مثل آهان مثل اینطور نیستید،
so so David Goggins is consistently
بنابراین دیوید گوگینز دائماً به
pushing himself
خودش فشار می آورد من
I love I did it I did it over the
دوست
pandemic more but I loved going today
دارم این کار را انجام دادم.  امروز
I'm running a marathon I'm gonna get on
دارم یک ماراتن می دوم روی
the treadmill and it's not gonna be all
تردمیل می روم و یکدفعه انجام نمی شود،
at once but I'm gonna get through a
اما
Marathon today so let's get up give me
امروز از یک ماراتن عبور می کنم، پس بیا بلند شوم به من
some coffee and let's see if we can do
قهوه بده و ببینیم آیا می توانیم
like five miles and then know that we
مانند پنج مسابقه انجام دهیم.  مایل ها و سپس بدانید که ما از
started there and that was really fun
آنجا شروع کردیم و این واقعاً سرگرم کننده بود،
because like
زیرا مانند
um cam Haines does that too where he
ام کم هاینز این کار را انجام می دهد، جایی که
goes like
می رود، انگار که
he almost just sets the limit and then
تقریباً فقط حد را تعیین می کند و سپس
and then achieves that his son Truitt is
و بعد به این نتیجه می رسد که پسرش ترویت
really fascinating because it's untrue
واقعاً شگفت انگیز است زیرا نادرست است که در
it's right now is trying to get the and
حال حاضر درست است.  تلاش برای به دست آوردن و
like I bet people would never think that
مثل شرط می‌بندم که مردم هرگز فکر نمی‌کنند
this is who I watch but I get real
این کسی است که من تماشا می‌کنم، اما من واقعاً
inspiration from those people because I
از آن‌ها الهام می‌گیرم زیرا به
showed Jocko I showed a clip to Jocko to
Jocko نشان دادم کلیپی را به Jocko به
Isla because Isla's like me like like a
Isla نشان دادم زیرا Isla شبیه من است مانند
a person of her fluids impulse
یک فرد از تکانه‌های مایعاتش است.
I walked in on her one time she was in
یک بار با لباس
the pantry in a bathrobe in the dark
حمام در تاریکی داخل انباری رفتم و
the door and she went I said what she
در را باز کردم و او رفت، گفتم چه می‌رود،
goes I thought you were mom shut the
فکر کردم مامان هستی
door and I shut the door to let her
در را ببند و من در را بستم.  بگذار
finish the root beer yes she has a hard
آبجو ریشه را تمام کند بله او به سختی از
time waking up so Isla come in here I
خواب بیدار می شود بنابراین ایسلا بیا اینجا می
want you to see this clip from Jocko she
خواهم این کلیپ را از جوکو ببینی او می
goes who's Jocko I say he's a Navy SEAL
رود که جوکو است من می گویم او نیروی دریایی است
she goes he works at the zoo I went no
او می رود او در باغ وحش کار می کند من رفتم نه
he said Navy [\h__\h] seal I got some
او گفت  نیروی دریایی فک لعنتی من
badass job she goes it's a silly name
کار بدی پیدا کردم او می گوید اسم احمقانه ای است
and I went no it's not it isn't a silly
و من رفتم نه
name these guys are the toughest dudes
اسم احمقانه ای نیست این بچه ها سرسخت ترین آدم های دنیا هستند.
never even realized that oh yeah you
متوجه شدم که اوه، بله، شما
talk to a child yeah and so I go watch
با یک کودک صحبت می کنید، بله، و بنابراین من می روم
this what he says about waking up so it
این را تماشا کنم که او در مورد بیدار شدن می گوید تا به
hits the thing and Joker Goes
چیزی برخورد کند و جوکر
first thing you do when you hear that
اولین کاری که می کنید با شنیدن
alarm clock
ساعت زنگ دار که
you could roll over you could go back to
می توانید روی آن بچرخانید، می توانید به
bed you could hit snooze but you get out
رختخواب برگردید.  می‌توانی چرت بزنی اما
of bed and that's your first Victory and
از رختخواب بلند می‌شوی و این اولین پیروزی شماست و
Isla has paused and she goes
ایسلا مکث کرده است و
how great is that nap right after you
چرت زدن درست بعد از
hit snooze though it is pretty funny
ضربه زدن به چرت چقدر عالی است، اگرچه خیلی خنده‌دار است که
you're missing the point yeah this whole
شما نکته را از دست می‌دهید، بله، کل این
speech he's with Casey neistat when he's
سخنرانی او با کیسی است.  neistat وقتی داره
telling this speech he's with Casey
این سخنرانی رو میگه با کیسی
neistat yeah and uh so I hit it and then
نیستت آره و اوه پس من بهش زدم و بعد
he goes and then you've got a victory
میره و بعد تو
under your belt then you go to the gym
زیر کمربندت پیروز میشی بعد به باشگاه میری
and you work out like are you listening
و مثل اینکه
to this island she goes yeah and he goes
به این جزیره گوش میدی تمرین میکنی  می رود بله و او می رود
then when you go to the work now you've
سپس وقتی شما به محل کار می روید، اکنون
got two victories you've worked out and
دو پیروزی کسب کرده اید که تمرین کرده اید و
you've woken up on time you didn't hit
به موقع از خواب بیدار شده اید،
that snooze button so when you go into
دکمه چرت زدن را نزنید، بنابراین وقتی به
that break room and you see donuts and
اتاق استراحت می روید و شما  دونات ها را ببین و
she hits the balls she goes
او به توپ ها ضربه می زند.
done listening I was definitely gonna
او می رود
say no to Donuts do you think he's gonna
اگر او می خواهد به دونات ها نه بگوید.
him and she goes do you think he'd like
او را دوست دارم و او می رود، فکر می کنی او تو را دوست دارد
you and I go what do you mean she goes
و من می روم، منظورت این است که او می رود،
dad you hit snooze you skip working out
بابا می زنی چرت می زنی، ورزش را رد می کنی
and you love donuts and I'm like yeah
و عاشق دونات هستی، و من می گویم آره،
you're making a good [\h__\h] point I go
تو داری یک نکته لعنتی درست می کنی، من می روم
I but I but I do love that like I love
من اما من این را دوست دارم، مثل اینکه دوست دارم
to watch that brain work and go like
این کار مغز را تماشا کنم و مثل اینکه
like I don't I don't hit snooze like I
نمی کنم چرت نمی زنم مثل اینکه
don't hit snooze now I go [\h__\h] it
چرت نمی زنم حالا می روم لعنتش کنم
because I'm up but I and then and then I
چون بیدار هستم اما من و  بعد و بعد من
go to the gym every single morning I go
هر روز صبح به باشگاه می روم
to the gym every single morning and
هر روز صبح به باشگاه می روم و
today is National Donut Day I didn't
امروز روز ملی دونات است من
have a donut
دونات نداشتم
and so like I I like I try I like try to
و بنابراین مثل من دوست دارم سعی می کنم دوست دارم سعی کنم
apply these a little bit because I mean
اینها را کمی اعمال کنم زیرا من  یعنی
the other side of me is like tonight
طرف مقابلم مثل این است که امشب
after we do this
بعد از انجام این کار،
I'll do another podcast and then I'm
من یک پادکست دیگر می‌سازم و سپس با
gonna call Leanne and go yo we're in
لیان تماس می‌گیرم و می‌روم، ما در
Beverly Hills meet me out here let's go
بورلی هیلز هستیم، اینجا با من ملاقات کن بیا بریم
have drinks let's go have [\h__\h] couple
نوشیدنی بخوریم، بیایید بریم زوج لعنتی
Campari Spritz
کامپاری بخوریم.  اسپریتز خیلی خب، بیا
all right let's go over her friend's
برویم
house and overnight let's get some
خانه دوستش و یک شبه بیا چند
edibles and let's [\h__\h] have a night
خوراکی بخوریم و بیایید یک شب
about it get some sushi go have sex in
در مورد آن سوشی بخوریم، برو در وان آب گرم رابطه جنسی داشته باشیم
the hot tub and I gotta work out at
و من باید ساعت 10 صبح ورزش کنم،
I gotta tell you that nap let me press
باید آن چرت را به شما بگویم  بگذار
news is the sweetest
خبر را فشار بدهم شیرین ترین
that's that's my victory first Victory
چیزی است که اولین پیروزی من است پیروزی
is pressing snooze and getting a nap
فشار دادن چرت زدن و چرت زدن
onto the Belt have you ever had I had so
روی کمربند است آیا تا به حال داشتم تا امروز
this this morning I didn't work I didn't
صبح کار نکردم
work out I'd press at like five in the
ورزش نکردم می خواهم روی کمربند فشار بیاورم  پنج
morning until about six you're going
صبح تا حدود شش، شما در
hard right now yeah yeah yeah yeah
حال حاضر سخت می روید بله بله بله بله بله
flew to Austin I was like what
به آستین پرواز کردم.
then look you only get one shot at these
شما فقط یک شات از این
movies so you might as well do and look
فیلم‌ها می‌گیرید، بنابراین ممکن است این کار را انجام دهید و به نظر می‌رسد که
it's really hard to get people to go
واقعاً سخت است که مردم را
into the movie theater right now and so
در حال حاضر به سالن سینما بکشانید، بنابراین
I woke up at like six to five or six to
من در ساعت شش تا پنج یا شش به
seven did press
هفت از خواب بیدار شدم
and then I went
و سپس رفتم.
and I said and I'm really into a podcast
و من گفتم و من واقعاً در حال حاضر وارد یک پادکست هستم،
uh History Podcast right now and I was
اوه پادکست تاریخ و
Conquistadors and I was and I was like
داشتم به این یکی در مورد Conquistadors گوش می‌دادم و مثل
before when I woke up I was like I
قبل بودم وقتی از خواب بیدار شدم،
wouldn't mind going back to that and I
فکر نمی‌کردم به آن برگردم.  و
said I'll tell you what
گفتم بهت میگم چی
I'm gonna take a little nap
میخوام چرت بزنم
and go now I slept good last night I
و برم دیشب خوب خوابیدم دیشب
slept like seven hours last night
هفت ساعت خوابیدم
boy that 30 minute nap it felt like five
پسر اون چرت 30 دقیقه ای انگار پنج
hours and I woke up going
ساعت بود و بیدار شدم رفتم باید
I gotta readjust my sleep score that has
تنظیم کنم  نمره خواب من که باید
to be in the 97 that's the best [\h__\h]
در 97 باشد بهترین
nap those little snooze naps are
چرت لعنتی است آن چرت های کوچک
monsters you know there's I don't care
هیولا هستند شما می دانید وجود دارد مهم نیست
that's probably for me one of the peak
که احتمالاً برای من یکی از اوج
experiences of life is those naps I
تجربه های زندگی همین چرت هاست که
don't know what that is have you ever
نمی دانم چیست  آیا تا به حال
slept in a tour bus
در یک اتوبوس تور خوابیده اید
a tour bus versus a regular bus like a
یک اتوبوس تور در مقابل یک اتوبوس معمولی مانند
tour bus like meaning like it's in a
اتوبوس تور مانند به این معناست که در یک
bunk
طبقه است،
no
نه
but I've taken a lot of buses in my life
اما من در زندگی ام اتوبوس های زیادی را سوار کرده ام،
though would mean like just like a like
اما به این معنی است که مانند اتوبوس
those are very different and uh
های مسافرتی  بسیار متفاوت است و اوه
well listen they
خوب گوش کنید آنها
that's just part of part of life and a
فقط بخشی از زندگی هستند و یک
greyhound I was on a Greyhound one time
تازی من یک بار در یک تازی بودم
one time right notorious b.i.g's album
یک بار آلبوم بدنام b.i.g
came out in college and I was going from
در کالج منتشر شد و من از
Tallahassee down to Tampa and the dude
تالاهاسی به تامپا می رفتم و آن شخص سوار شد
got on the tour bus got on the bus next
اتوبوس تور سوار اتوبوس کنار
to me black dude and he sat down he said
من شد رفیق سیاه پوست و او نشست و گفت
we had it and I said Tampa he said you
ما آن را داریم و من گفتم تامپا گفت تو
grew up in Tampa I said yeah I said you
در تمپا بزرگ شدی گفتم آره گفتم تو
and he goes yeah I said you go to school
و او می رود آره گفتم تو به مدرسه می روی.
fam and because family on Florida State
چون خانواده در ایالت فلوریدا
the two schools one's black ones white
دو مدرسه یکی سیاه پوست است
and he goes no I just got out of prison
و او می رود نه من همین الان از زندان بیرون آمدم
I said you go to prison and he goes yeah
گفتم تو برو زندان و او می رود آره
yeah man I got out of prison I stabbed a
مرد من از زندان بیرون آمدم یک شخص را با چاقو زدم
dude and uh and uh and I've been in
و اوه و اوه و من.
prison I just got out today because what
من در زندان بودم امروز بیرون آمدم چون چی
are you listening to I said Notorious
گوش می کنی گفتم Notorious
B.I.G and he goes oh [\h__\h] that's out and
B.I.G و او می رود اوه لعنتی که بیرون است و
I went yeah and he goes I want to hear
من رفتم بله و او می رود من می خواهم آن را بشنوم
it can I hear it and I was like yeah and
می توانم آن را بشنوم و من مثل اینکه بله و
he used my headsets the whole bus ride
او استفاده کرد  هدست‌های من تمام سفر اتوبوس
to Tampa I didn't have the Bible I was
به تامپا من انجیل نداشتم،
like he stabbed a man they're yours now
مثل این بودم که مردی را با چاقو زد، حالا
I guess and then I just sat next to him
حدس می‌زنم که آنها مال شما هستند و بعد فقط کنارش نشستم
and I was like is he enjoying it he's
و فکر می‌کردم که او از آن لذت می‌برد،
like this is good no tour bus naps yeah
این خوب است  نه اتوبوس تور چرت می زند بله
when you're in a bunk it's ice cold bust
وقتی در یک تخت خواب هستید، نیم تنه سرد یخ است ساعت
we work out from like up until like five
پنج حرکت نمی کند.
that five o'clock to six six thirty nap
ساعت تا شش شش سی و نیم چرت
Pitch Black it's like a coffin and it is
سیاه تیره مثل یک تابوت است و هوا
ice cold and you got all your pillows
سرد است و همه بالش ها
and blankets in there and you put a
و پتوهایت را در آنجا گذاشته ای و یک
little History podcast on in the corner
پادکست تاریخی را در گوشه ای قرار می دهی
and you just listen to like
و فقط به لایک
or like oh my God so you're talking
یا لایک گوش می دهی خدای من پس  شما در
about like five six p.m for a 7 P.M show
مورد ساعت 17:00 برای یک برنامه 7 بعدازظهر صحبت می کنید،
oh it's the best nap you'll ever have if
اوه این بهترین چرتی است که می توانید داشته باشید اگر آنقدر سرحال از
you wake up so refreshed yeah like I've
خواب بیدار شوید، آره، مثل اینکه من
woken up from naps like where I'm like
از چرت های خواب بیدار شده ام، مثل جایی که من مثل
[\h__\h] yeah like they're those those tour
آنها بیدار شده ام.  آن
bus naps are the best naps yeah I think
چرت‌های اتوبوس تور بهترین چرت‌ها هستند، بله، فکر می‌کنم
having a full productive day
داشتن یک روز پربار
[Music]
(موسیقی)
and then like five six p.m you do get a
و بعد از آن ساعت پنج بعدازظهر
nap and then you do something really
چرت می‌زنید و بعد از آن یک کار واقعاً
stressful after that like really hyper
استرس‌زا انجام می‌دهید، مانند واقعاً
like like a show but if I do like I
مانند یک نمایش، اما اگر  من
really like doing podcasts like late at
واقعاً دوست دارم پادکست انجام دهم مثل اواخر
night
شب
after a nap I think I [\h__\h] up my
بعد از چرت زدن، فکر می‌کنم
podcast Rhythm because we're doing them
ریتم پادکست‌ام را خراب کرده‌ام، زیرا ما آن‌ها را
in the day yeah and so sometimes I'm
در روز انجام می‌دهیم، بله، و بنابراین گاهی اوقات
just like like if I work out in the
مثل اینکه صبح‌ها ورزش می‌کنم.
morning I'm good on a podcast but if I
من در پادکست خوب هستم، اما اگر
don't work out I suck on a podcast and
ورزش نکنم، از پادکست لذت می برم و
I'm just like huh yeah yeah that's cool
من مثل این هستم که بله، بله، خیلی خوب است،
no I I I'm
نه، من
my favorite is I used to do this a lot I
مورد علاقه من هستم، من قبلاً این کار را انجام می دادم که
haven't done it in a while is
انجام نداده ام  بعد از مدتی
uh full busy day nap at home box of wine
یک چرت روزانه پر مشغله در خانه با جعبه شراب
on the treadmill
روی تردمیل است
and do that until like midnight watching
و این کار را تا نیمه شب در حال تماشای
TV box one box of wine on a treadmill
جعبه تلویزیون یک جعبه شراب روی تردمیل است
it's the best height weight how are you
که بهترین وزن قد است.
sipping it Jake you have a glass but you
شما
have a box the box fits on the corner on
جعبه ای دارید که جعبه آن در گوشه
the treadmill so it's got a little
تردمیل جا می شود، بنابراین کمی
spigot yeah and you sit there and just
پیچ است، بله و شما همانجا می نشینید و فقط
put on like Guys Grocery Games or like
مثل Guys Grocery Games یا
just something it's like a you walking
چیزی شبیه چیزی شبیه به راه رفتن شما
or are you running I walk I walk in like
یا می دوید، من راه می روم و وارد می شوم.  مانند
a three five so what will happen is if
سه پنج، پس چه اتفاقی می افتد این است که اگر
you started a three start a three casual
یک سه شروع کنید، یک
walk 20 minutes you're getting a mile in
پیاده روی معمولی 20 دقیقه ای را شروع کنید، یک مایل وارد می شوید
and then you and you're gonna feel loose
و سپس شما و شما احساس شلوغی می کنید
get up to a three five
تا یک سه پنج که
you can do seven miles on these things
می توانید هفت مایل انجام دهید.  این چیزها
and just and just and you're just
و فقط و فقط و شما فقط از
enjoying your night especially like my
شب خود لذت می برید، به خصوص مثل
wife back in the day when we lived in
همسر من در آن روز که در
our old house my wife would come into
خانه قدیمی خود زندگی می کردیم، همسرم به
the man cave and she said on the couch
غار مرد می آمد و او روی کاناپه می گفت
and we watch TV together yeah and like
و ما با هم تلویزیون تماشا می کنیم بله و  مثل
watch Game of Thrones and use like for
تماشای Game of Thrones و استفاده از لایک برای
an hour and you just get on the
یک ساعت و شما فقط روی
treadmill and do it oh man I I loved I
تردمیل می‌روید و این کار را انجام می‌دهید اوه مرد من عاشقش بودم
haven't done that as much lately because
اخیراً آنقدر این کار را انجام نداده‌ام زیرا
that was the [\h__\h] you can lose
این کار لعنتی بود که می‌توانید خودتان را گم کنید،
yourself you can forget yourself you
می‌توانید خودتان را فراموش کنید و فراموشتان
forget you're on a treadmill and you
کنید  روی تردمیل هستید و
just are like walking and you're
فقط مثل راه رفتن هستید و
sweating and you're and you're having
عرق می کنید و شراب می خورید
wine and then at certain points you're
و سپس در برخی نقاط
like uh you like you you start jogging
مثل آه دوست دارید شروع به دویدن می کنید
especially like we were watching uh not
مخصوصاً مثل اینکه ما تماشا می کردیم نه
All Quiet on the rest in front what's
همه ساکت هستند در مقابل بقیه
the one where they've gotta they've got
باید چه چیزی را برای
to get the message to the front line
رساندن پیام به خط مقدم داشته باشند.  دوست داشتم
because they were doing drinks they'd be
چون نوشیدنی می‌نوشیدند،
like take a drink you gotta run up there
مثل نوشیدن یک نوشیدنی هستند که باید به آنجا بدوید
and be like okay
و خوب باشید،
yeah I'm really into I'm really into
بله، من واقعاً به
History Podcast right now like I've been
پادکست تاریخ علاقه دارم، مثل اینکه
in them for a while 20th century or
مدتی در آن‌ها بودم.  قرن بیستم یا همه چیزهایی که
everything everything everything I
من
listened to
گوش دادم،
was it Marcus Aurelius and Cleopatra
مارکوس اورلیوس و کلئوپاترا
today uh I know the podcasts are like
امروز بودند، می دانم که پادکست ها مثل
you know just so you know Cleopatra
شما هستند، فقط برای این که بدانید کلئوپاترا آنقدرها
wasn't as hot as everyone says I was
که همه می گویند داغ نبود، من
like why are you saying that yeah tell
مثل این بودم که چرا می گویی آره بگو
me she's a six she looks like Snooki
من او شش ساله است، او شبیه اسنوکی است،
yeah like why let me let me dream that
بله، به همین دلیل اجازه دهید من خواب ببینم که
she looks like Kim Kardashian yeah and
او شبیه کیم کارداشیان است، بله، و
then uh I listened to that one today I
سپس اوه من امروز به آن یکی گوش کردم،
listened to World War II a lot oh a lot
جنگ جهانی دوم را زیاد گوش کردم، اوه بسیاری
of books on World War II a lot of uh
از کتاب ها در مورد جنگ جهانی دوم
podcasts about it what's your favorite
پادکست های زیادی در مورد آن تئاتر مورد علاقه شما چیست،
theater the Pacific or or european
اقیانوس آرام یا اروپایی،
uh no European Pacific well because my
اوه هیچ اقیانوس آرام اروپایی خوب نیست، زیرا
family's so much of it has died in that
خانواده من خیلی از آن ها در آن تئاتر مرده اند،
theater so this person so much of it I
بنابراین این شخص خیلی از آن ها من از
hate this sound cliche like a Marlon
این کلیشه صوتی مثل مارلون
Schwarzenegger in an 80s movie but it's
شوارتزنگر در یک تئاتر متنفرم  فیلم دهه 80 اما
personal well you know what I find funny
شخصی است خوب می‌دانید چه چیزی در مورد من خنده‌دار است،
about that is Lennon
لنون است
who's Lenin right uh John Lennon no no
که لنین درست می‌گوید اوه جان لنون نه
no one was it Lennon was World War II
هیچ‌کس این بود که لنون درست جنگ جهانی دوم بود
right or was it Stalin Stalin Stalin
یا استالین بود استالین استالین
Stalin thought him and Hitler would be
استالین فکر می‌کرد او و هیتلر با هم دوست خواهند شد،
friends yeah I think that's so cute that
بله من  فکر کن این خیلی بامزه است که
he was like we're gonna be buddies yeah
او مثل این بود که ما با هم رفیق خواهیم شد، بله
like we're boys yeah and then Hitler's
مثل اینکه ما پسر هستیم، بله، و بعد هیتلر
like oh [\h__\h] you I'm Hitler bro this is
مثل اوه لعنت به تو، من هیتلر هستم برادر این
what I do well at first he was like
چیزی است که من خوب انجام می دهم او در ابتدا مثل
[\h__\h] yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah we'll
لعنتی بود بله بله بله بله بله  ما با هم
be friends yeah yeah sure sure and then
دوست خواهیم بود بله بله مطمئناً و بعد با
call me call me better yet I'll show up
من تماس بگیرید بهتر است با من تماس بگیرید اما
in Winter how's that sound yeah that uh
در زمستان ظاهر می شوم این صدا چگونه است بله که اوه اوه
that uh I find that I find all of that
من متوجه شدم که
so fascinating when I was a kid I had a
وقتی بچه بودم همه اینها را بسیار جذاب می دانم.
hard time understanding how because we
درک این موضوع برایم سخت بود زیرا
were always at war with Russia when I
زمانی که من بچه بودم همیشه با روسیه در جنگ بودیم
was a kid and I had a hard time
و
understanding how we could be on the
درک اینکه چگونه می‌توانیم در
same team as Russia in World War II
همان تیم روسیه در جنگ جهانی دوم باشیم مشکل داشتم
and I was like wait how did that turn
و مثل این بودم که صبر کنم چگونه به سمت
South and then you guys listen to
جنوب حرکت کردیم و سپس  شما بچه ها به
podcasts yeah I'm that
پادکست ها گوش می دهید بله، من فکر می کنم که
all of that all of that like
همه این ها، مانند
all of the World War II I got really
تمام جنگ جهانی دوم، من
into the Pacific [\h__\h] for a while but
برای مدتی واقعاً وارد ماجراهای اقیانوس آرام شدم، اما
I'm really deep in the
من واقعاً عمیقاً
in the whole we we went to Normandy from
در کل چیزهایی که به نرماندی رفتیم، هستم.  از
The Cliffs of Dover and to think so
The Cliffs of Dover و فکر کردن
that's the [\h__\h] beach
که این ساحل لعنتی است، این
that's the [\h__\h] beach oh [\h__\h] this is
ساحل لعنتی است آه لعنتی، این
cold as [\h__\h] these dudes jumped in ice
سرد است زیرا لعنت به این آدمها در
cold water yeah and this isn't like a
آب سرد یخ پریدند، آره، و این مثل
cool beach like this is
ساحل خنکی مثل این نیست
and it's just so insane
و خیلی دیوانه کننده است
to and then to see like the the it's
و بعد اینکه ببینم
pretty intense I don't know why I got
خیلی شدید است، نمی‌دانم چرا
into history late in life I wasn't I was
در اواخر زندگی وارد تاریخ شدم، به
kind of into it but I'm really into it
نوعی در آن نبودم، اما الان واقعاً به آن علاقه دارم
now and I love just learning a little
و دوست دارم فقط کمی در مورد آن یاد بگیرم.  می‌دانی که
you know today was I listened to like
امروز من به نویز گوش دادم
the noise or has a great history stuff
یا چیزهای تاریخی خوبی داشتم،
it's like History For Dummies I think
مثل History For Dummies فکر می‌کنم
like I get to I can't listen to the
مثل اینکه به
really smart stuff starts losing me too
چیزهای هوشمندانه گوش می‌دهم، نمی‌توانم به چیزهای واقعاً هوشمند گوش بدهم، نام‌های زیادی برایم از دست می‌دهد
many names and I'm gone yeah well Dan
و من خوب رفتم، بله خوب است.  دن
Carlin is always the best
کارلین همیشه بهترین
your podcast with Dan Carlin yeah was so
پادکست شما با دن کارلین است. آره
[\h__\h] good he is
خیلی خوب بود
he is I mean I only know about Martin
او هم هست، منظورم این است که من فقط در مورد مارتین لوتر
Luther because of Dan Carlin I only know
به خاطر دن کارلین می دانم.
and everyone laughed and I was like did
همه خندیدند و من فکر می کردم آیا
you guys listen to the same podcast I
شما بچه ها به همان پادکستی که من گوش دادم،
did because I just am quoting Dan Carlin
چون من فقط از دن کارلین نقل قول می کنم که
uh that his podcast I mean we all quoted
پادکست او را نقل می کنم، منظورم این است که همه ما
the same [\h__\h] about uh Genghis Khan
در مورد آه چنگیز خان حرف های مشابهی زدیم
about how he could shoot a dove off a
که چگونه او می تواند یک کبوتر را از روی اسب شلیک کند.
horseback but we knew that all four
ما می‌دانستیم که هر چهار
hoofs had to be off the ground at the
سم باید
same time they shot they would sometimes
همزمان با شلیک از زمین جدا شوند، آنها گاهی اوقات
take their meat and stick it under their
گوشتشان را می‌گیرند و زیر
Saddles and that I mean Dan Carlin is he
زین‌هایشان می‌چسبانند و منظورم این است که دن کارلین او
is the [\h__\h] yeah God those were
مادر لعنتی است، بله، خداییش، آن‌هایی بودند که
man discovering podcasts was the coolest
انسان‌ها پادکست‌ها را کشف کردند.  جالبترین
time of my life and the interesting
دوران زندگی من و
thing about him is his audio
نکته جالب در مورد او صدای او است
and so this is the voice
و بنابراین این صدا است
so for me I mean everybody has a story
بنابراین برای من منظورم این است که همه داستانی
with a prostitute in a motel
با یک فاحشه در متل دارند
Dan Carlin was my prostitute in the most
دن کارلین فاحشه من بود.
I invited him to a motel I don't even
من او را به یک متل دعوت کردم.  حتی
remember in the middle of nowhere he
یادت نره در وسط ناکجاآباد
shows up with that voice
با اون صدا ظاهر میشد
and the rest the rest is history so good
و بقیه چیزها تاریخ است آنقدر
things that we'll never know what
چیزهای خوب که ما هرگز نخواهیم فهمید چه اتفاقی
happened oh boy did he like no just
افتاده اوه پسر دوست داشت نه فقط
kidding I'm I'm really running yeah but
شوخی می کند من واقعا دارم می دوم  بله، اما
yes we did we got along with I mean he's
بله، ما با آنها کنار آمدیم، منظورم این است که او
an incredibly kind and thoughtful person
فردی فوق‌العاده مهربان و متفکر است که
constantly self-critical thinking he's
دائماً خودانتقاد می‌کند و فکر می‌کند به
not good enough he just works on those
اندازه کافی خوب نیست، او فقط
episodes forever forever and he just
برای همیشه روی آن قسمت‌ها کار می‌کند و فقط
thinks that there's these uh just like
فکر می‌کند که این‌ها وجود دارند، درست مثل
with Goggins there's these
گوگینز، این‌ها
other historians that I think like weigh
هم هستند.  مورخانی که فکر می‌کنم مثل
or something like this in his mind I
این است که او را قضاوت کنند یا چیزی شبیه به این در ذهنش.
hang up is Collins is he's not a he he's
آیا کالینز نیست، او
not like this like he doesn't feel like
اینگونه نیست، مثل اینکه احساس نمی کند
he's a real historian yeah but he is
یک مورخ واقعی است، بله، بله،
yeah yeah I mean it's the way he shares
بله، منظورم این است که او
the story The Queen history teacher in
داستان را به اشتراک می گذارد معلم تاریخ ملکه در
seventh grade who's a con artist and he
کلاس هفتم که یک کلاهبردار است و او
came and taught her seventh grade and it
آمد و کلاس هفتم را به او آموزش داد و
was the whole con artist all he taught
تمام کلاهبردار چیزی بود که او به
us about was barnstorming barnstorming
ما یاد داد
small blip on Americana but I know a lot
طوفان در انبار و قتل JFK بود.
about barnstorming because of this guy
پسر
and he because he was passionate about
و او چون علاقه زیادی به طوفان
barnstorming it was a funny seventh
در انبار داشت این یک کلاس خنده دار
grade history class I've ever taken my
تاریخ کلاس هفتم بود که من
entire life
تمام عمرم را گذراندم اوه
uh you mentioned tour bus uh what's the
شما به اتوبوس تور اشاره کردید آه
best road trip you've been on have you
بهترین سفر جاده ای که رفته اید اگر در
have you driven across the country just
سراسر کشور رانندگی کرده اید چیست؟
you no
شما نه،
we had one road trip in college
ما یک سفر جاده ای در کالج داشتیم
where a bar had burned down and we found
که در آن یک بار سوخته بود و
out that the alcohol was still in the
متوجه شدیم که الکل هنوز در
bar yeah so we took my Jetta yeah over
بار است، بله، بنابراین جتا بله را
to the bar and we emptied out the bar of
به بار بردیم و میله
all the burnt up liquor we didn't know
مشروبات الکلی سوخته را خالی کردیم.  ما نمی دانستیم
what anything was
چیزی چیست
let's go into the trunk with no clothes
بیایید بدون لباس بدون لباس برویم داخل صندوق عقب
like no no clothes and we said let's
و گفتیم بیایید
just start driving
رانندگی را شروع کنیم و
and we drove from Tallahassee and ended
از تالاهاسی رانندگی کردیم و
up in West Virginia and just just drove
به ویرجینیای غربی ختم شدیم و فقط رانندگی کردیم
just drove it was like five dudes we
مانند پنج نفر بودیم.
drank one person drove I I wasn't a big
نوشید یک نفر رانندگی کرد من بزرگ نبودم
and this I was going crazy I wasn't a
و این داشتم دیوونه می شدم من
big drinker in college until I went to
در کالج مشروب خوار بزرگی نبودم تا اینکه به روسیه رفتم و بنابراین
and so I drove the majority of the way
اکثر مسیر را رانندگی کردم
and then we we get somewhere
و سپس به جایی می رسیم و
and and we'd get a hotel room
یک اتاق هتل بگیرید
and it was one of the most epic [\h__\h]
و این یکی از حماسی ترین
weekends of just debauchery and chaos
آخر هفته های لعنتی فقط فسق و هرج و مرج بود
and I think we took mushrooms
و من فکر می کنم ما قارچ گرفتیم
and we we we uh went down a river in
و از رودخانه ای در
tubes so it's mostly about the bond
لوله ها پایین رفتیم، بنابراین بیشتر در مورد پیوند
between the five people versus like
بین پنج نفر است در مقابل مانند
throwing yourself into meeting like
پرتاب کردن خودت.  در ملاقاتی مانند
strangers and this kind of stuff yeah
غریبه ها و این جور چیزها،
and it was when it was when I was like I
بله، زمانی بود که انگار در
was trying to be a poet at that time and
آن زمان سعی می کردم شاعر باشم و
so like we were actual poetry yeah it
مثل اینکه شعر واقعی بودیم، بله،
was a really bad part of my life I was
بخش بسیار بدی از زندگی من بود.
just we were like it's like music is
ما مثل این بودیم که موسیقی
there too somewhere yeah I tried to be
هم در جایی وجود دارد، بله، من هم سعی کردم
in a band too that didn't work out the
در گروهی باشم که آنطور که می‌خواستم پیش نمی‌رفت.
good serious person like I'm a good
مثل اینکه من یک
funny person I'm good to be the fool but
آدم بامزه خوبی هستم، برای احمق بودن خوب هستم، اما
I'm not good when I try to be serious it
وقتی سعی می کنم جدی باشم، خوب نیستم،
looks foolish and so even like you know
احمقانه به نظر می رسد و حتی مثل اینکه می دانید
someone said showed me throwing out the
یکی به من گفت که
first pitch the other day as something
روز قبل اولین زمین بازی را به من نشان داد.  چیزی
and all I could see is my gut flying
و تنها چیزی که می‌توانستم ببینم این بود که روده‌ام به
everywhere and I was like that's why it
همه جا پرواز می‌کند و من اینطور بودم که به همین دلیل
went viral I was like [\h__\h] I thought it
ویروسی شد. من فکر می‌کردم این
was my throwing Style
سبک پرتاب من بود
that was a pretty epic one the best road
که بسیار حماسی بود بهترین
trips I ever took was during the
سفرهای جاده‌ای که تا به حال انجام دادم در
pandemic during the pandemic when we
طول همه‌گیری بود.  همه‌گیری زمانی که ما در چه زمانی
were when when we would we're doing that
بودیم، ما در حال انجام آن
drive-in movie theater tour
تور سینمای درایو بودیم،
I created a drive-in movie theater tour
من یک تور سینمای درایو ایجاد کردم
when no one was working and the very
زمانی که هیچ‌کس کار نمی‌کرد و
first one we all no one had left our
اولین توری که همه ما هیچ‌کس خانه‌هایمان را ترک نکرده بودیم،
houses we all went to my house we got my
همه به آنجا رفتیم.  خانه من،
tour bus we had just wrapped the day the
اتوبوس تورم را گرفتیم، روزی که
tour bus showed up we just wrapped the
اتوبوس تور نشان داده شد، بسته بندی کرده بودیم،
cabin just wrapped doing the cabin on
کابین را پیچیده کردیم و کابین را در
Netflix and we got covered tested we got
نتفلیکس انجام دادیم و تحت پوشش آزمایش قرار گرفتیم، سوار
in the tour bus and we said let's create
اتوبوس تور شدیم و گفتیم بیایید
our bubble and stay safe and that night
حباب خود را ایجاد کنیم و بمانیم.  امن و آن شب
we drove I think just outside uh
رانندگی کردیم، فکر می‌کنم درست بیرون آه
gallop and we stayed in a and when no
گالوپ بود و در آنجا ماندیم و زمانی که هیچ‌کس
one had been outside and we stayed at a
بیرون نبود و در
at a a KOA camp on arrival and we
یک کمپ KOA در بدو ورود ماندیم و
watched thunderstorms come in on a lake
رعد و برق را تماشا کردیم که وارد دریاچه شد
and we were all smoking cigars and
و همگی سیگار سیگار می‌کشیدیم.  و
drinking ipas and and it was [\h__\h]
نوشیدن ipas و و و آن مت لعنتی بود
Matt and that whole road trip we Road
و کل آن سفر جاده ای ما جاده در
tripped across the country to start the
سراسر کشور رفتیم تا
tours and then we just and we were
تورها را شروع کنیم و سپس ما فقط و
outside for the first time when we were
برای اولین بار که بودیم بیرون بودیم
and it was that period of my life I'm so
و آن دوره از زندگی من بود.  خیلی
grateful I didn't make a ton of money so
ممنون که پول زیادی به دست نیاوردم، بنابراین
we had a big crew and I made sure I was
خدمه بزرگی داشتیم و مطمئن شدم که
trying to make sure everyone because no
سعی می‌کنم همه را مطمئن کنم، زیرا
one had paid bills in a while but that
مدتی بود که هیچ‌کس صورت‌حساب‌ها را پرداخت نکرده بود، اما آن
[\h__\h] tour was the funnest we took up
تور لعنتی خنده‌دارترین توری بود که
pickleball we took up disc golf and
ما در آن شرکت کردیم.  تا دیسک گلف و
everything was wide open in the middle
همه چیز در وسط کشور کاملاً باز بود
of the country you could do things but
شما می توانید کارهایی انجام دهید، اما
we were still in our bubble and we lived
ما هنوز در حباب خود بودیم و
in that tour bus and at the at night we
در آن اتوبوس تور زندگی می کردیم و شب
just get back in the tour bus by
فقط خودمان به اتوبوس تور بازمی گردیم
ourselves and get [\h__\h] wasted and and
و لعنتی می شویم  هدر رفته و
I mean that [\h__\h] run it'll nothing
منظورم این است که دویدن لعنتی، هیچ چیز
will ever be like that yeah because
مثل آن نخواهد بود، بله، زیرا
you like rediscovered the humanity the
دوست دارید انسانیت را دوباره کشف کنید،
camaraderie because uh the pandemic kind
رفاقت، زیرا اوه نوع همه گیر
of killed that really suffocated us from
کشته شده ای که واقعاً ما را خفه کرد،
like their basic connection yeah and
مانند ارتباط اصلی آنها، بله و
then and and there was this
بعد و و این بود
you always had an anxiety attack halfway
تو همیشه در نیمه راه یک حمله اضطراب داشتی
through that you got Cove and this one
که کاوی گرفتی و این یکی که می
you know kova was killing people and you
دانی کوا داشت مردم را می کشت و تو
were like I know I've got coveted and
مثل این بودی که من می دانم طمع شده ام و
then and then we come in
بعد و بعد وارد
to Sedona you know this is also why I
سدونا شدیم، می دانی که دلیل من هم به همین دلیل است.
didn't make a ton of money we'd come
پول زیادی به دست می‌آوریم که
into Sedona and we get a house in Sedona
وارد سدونا می‌شدیم و
for five days an Airbnb and we'd all
برای پنج روز یک Airbnb در سدونا می‌گیریم و همه ما
isolate there before we went home to our
قبل از اینکه به خانه نزد خانواده‌هایمان برویم آنجا منزوی می‌شدیم،
families yeah
بله،
I remember I remember the first time we
یادم می‌آید اولین باری که این کار را
did it we didn't isolate we just pulled
کردیم، یادم می‌آید.  منزوی نشدیم ما فقط
back into LA and all our families were
به لس آنجلس برگشتیم و همه خانواده‌هایمان
freaked out so I had to live on the tour
وحشت زده شدند، بنابراین من مجبور شدم در
bus in at a different house and it was
اتوبوس تور در خانه دیگری زندگی کنم و
Fourth of July and I came in and they
چهارم ژوئیه بود و من وارد شدم و آنها
were doing an egg toss and they're like
داشتند تخم‌مرغ می‌کردند و آنها  مثل اینکه می‌توانی
well you can do an egg toss they need to
تخم‌مرغ پرت کنی، آن‌ها باید
stop at my anxiety guts you can do an
در اضطراب من توقف کنند، می‌توانی
egg toss with their daughter Isla so
با دخترشان Isla یک تخم مرغ پرتاب کنی، بنابراین
Island I did an egg toss and we [\h__\h]
جزیره من یک تخم مرغ پرتاب کردم و ما
got it to like legit like 40 [\h__\h]
آن را به اندازه 40
feet where I was throwing overhand
فوت لعنتی جایی که من بودم دوست داشتیم.  با دست
lobbing them to her
پرتاب کردن آنها به سمت او
and the Egg cracked in her hands and it
و تخم مرغ در دستانش ترک خورد و
broke over her face and I got in bed
روی صورتش شکست و من آن شب با علف های هرز مست لعنتی به رختخواب رفتم
[\h__\h] drunk and I went what if I gave
و رفتم اگر به
my daughter kovid from an egg toss I go
دخترم کووید را از پرتاب تخم مرغ بدهم
that would be the most horrific way to
چه می شود.  وحشتناک ترین راه برای
kill a child yeah she got it from an egg
کشتن یک کودک آره او آن را از یک تخم مرغ
toss it broken her face her dad did
پرتاب کرد و صورتش شکست پدرش
covet yeah I mean that's the scariest
طمع کرد بله منظورم این است که این ترسناک ترین
thing about kovid I think is not you
چیز در مورد کووید است که فکر می کنم شما نمی
dying but because of you somebody else
میرید بلکه به خاطر شما یکی دیگر
dies oh my God that feel that's that
می میرد خدای من که  احساس می‌کنم این همان
that's the fear I think that really like
ترسی است که فکر می‌کنم واقعاً
took hold on people that's why they're
مردم را تحت تأثیر قرار داده است، به همین دلیل
they were way more cautious than perhaps
آنها بسیار محتاط‌تر از آن چیزی هستند که شاید
they needed to be it's just like I don't
لازم باشد، درست مثل این است که من نمی‌خواهم
want to be the guy that's responsible
کسی باشم که مسئول
for killing somebody I love or somebody
کشتن کسی است که دوستش دارم.  یا کسی
that somebody else loves but Leanne gave
که یکی دیگر او را دوست دارد اما لیان به
everyone in our family covet she came up
همه اعضای خانواده ما طمع داد او آمد
to me and she gave me a hug yeah after
پیش من و بعد از کریسمس مرا در آغوش گرفت و
matter she goes I think I have coveted I
من را در آغوش گرفت.
go [\h__\h] yeah the [\h__\h] you doing yeah
لعنت به تو داری انجامش
like we can still go to Park City so we
میدی آره پشتی  به پارک سیتی تا
all go to Park City then Georgia gets
همه به پارک سیتی برویم سپس جورجیا
covered and then Georgia starts crying
تحت پوشش قرار می گیرد و سپس جورجیا شروع به گریه می کند و
and she goes I think I gave you covet
او می رود فکر می کنم من به شما طمع دادم
and I was like I'm fine she goes you're
و فکر می کردم خوب هستم او می رود شما
at high risk and I'm like what she's
در معرض خطر هستید و من مانند چیزی هستم  او
like you're a fat alcoholic I'm like
مثل اینکه تو یک الکلی چاق هستی من
whoa easy where the [\h__\h] what about
خیلی راحت هستم که لعنتی چه
feelings yeah and then Georgia got
احساسی دارد، بله و جورجیا
covered me and I live are still in Park
من را تحت پوشش قرار داد و من هنوز در پارک
City Leanne had it my tour bus came up
سیتی زندگی می کنم، اگر اتوبوس تور من آمد و
picked George up Georgia land took him
جورج را برد زمین جورجیا او را برد.
back to L.A and I was Island over there
به لس آنجلس برگشتم و من آنجا جزیره بودم و
and I tested and then we get on the
آزمایش دادم و سپس سوار
plane and I I cough and Isla's got her
هواپیما شدیم و من سرفه می‌کنم و ایسلا ماسکش را پوشیده است
mask on and I just looks at me you know
و من فقط به من نگاه می‌کنم شما می‌دانید
the best the one thing we miss are the
بهترین چیزی که از دست می‌دهیم
eyes over masks yeah the uh the yeah and
چشم‌های روی ماسک است، بله.  آره و
then we get home and I had coveted and I
بعد به خونه برمی گردیم و من طمع کرده بودم و
was like if you gave me [\h__\h] covet
انگار به من طمع لعنتی می دادی و
and then she never got covered she never
بعد اون هیچ وقت تحت پوشش قرار نمی گرفت اون هیچ وقت
got covered
پوشیده نمی شد آه
uh you mentioned ipas what's the lay of
تو اشاره کردی که
the land of great beers
سرزمین آبجوهای عالی
in um in this expansive world of ours I
در این پهناور چیه؟  دنیای ما من
like pilsners I'm a Pilsner guy I'm an
پیلسنر را دوست دارم من یک پسر پیلسنر هستم من یک
ice cold beer guy ice cold pilsner I
بچه آبجوی یخی هستم پیلزنر من
like an ice cold beer I like an ice
یک آبجو سرد دوست دارم یک
call one of the best beer buzzes I ever
تماس یخی دوست دارم یکی از بهترین وزوزهای آبجوی که تا به حال
had
داشتم این است که
we had bought a new house but we weren't
ما یک آبجو جدید خریده بودیم  خانه اما ما در حال
building it and over covered I didn't
ساختن آن نبودیم و بیش از حد سرپوشیده بود من
drink for like three months four months
حدود سه ماه و چهار ماه مشروب ننوشیدم
until we decided to go back out on tour
تا اینکه تصمیم گرفتیم به تور برگردیم
and we figured that out and I was in the
و این را فهمیدیم و من در
backyard and Leanne came back with like
حیاط خلوت بودم و لیان با
two tall boy German pilsners and cracked
دو قد بلند برگشت.  پسر پیلسنر آلمانی و آنها را ترک کرد
them she goes let's have a beer and I
او می رود بیا یک آبجو بخوریم و من
was like [\h__\h] yeah
مثل لعنتی آره
and man that second that beer buzz is
و مرد بودم که وزوز آبجو
different than anything yeah cause the
با هر چیز دیگری فرق می کند، بله، زیرا در
second it it touches you you feel the
ثانیه ای که شما را لمس کرد، درخشش را احساس می کنید
Sparkle and you're just like
و شما دقیقاً مانند
yeah baby I'm back and then she's like
بله عزیزم هستید.  من برگشتم و بعد مثل اینکه
you want another one I'm like [\h__\h] yeah
تو یکی دیگه میخوای من میخوام
and then we have another one and then
یکی دیگه داشته باشی و بعدش و اون وزوز آبجو
and that beer buzz is especially
مخصوصا
afternoon beer buzz is just so pretty
بعدازظهر است.
night beer buzz is like I guess we'll
حدس می‌زنم
have a beer and then I'll have a couple
یک آبجو بخوریم و بعد من یک زوج بخورم،
I gotta go to work tomorrow all right
من باید فردا بروم سر کار،
but that afternoon irresponsible beer
اما آن روز بعد از ظهر بی‌مسئولانه آبجو وزوز
buzz yeah
بله
pilsner pilsner there's I don't mind an
پیلسنر پیلسنر وجود دارد.
I gotta be at somewhere I gotta be at
من باید در جایی باشم باید در
somewhere like they gotta have an IP
جایی باشم مثل اینکه آنها باید یک IP داشته باشند
like I like a local IPA it's got to be
مثل من یک IPA محلی را دوست دارم باید
food involved and then I'm enjoying an
درگیر غذا باشد و سپس از یک IPA لذت می برم.
IPA I I threw up an IPA in a bathtub and
IPA IPA را در وان حمام انداختم و
uh Salt Lake City one time
سالت لیک سیتی  زمان این بود که
it was like what do you mean oh you
منظورت چیست، اوه، تو وان
throw up in the bathtub okay no no I was
حمام پرت می‌کنی، نه، نه،
you're sitting in the bathtub no I'm
داشتم در وان می‌نوشیدم مثل وان با مقداری آب در آن یا نه نه نه نه نه
getting ready to take a shower and I had
برای دوش گرفتن و من
a growler of IPA yeah it's about six in
یک غرغر از IPA گرفتم، بله، حدود شش
the morning yeah I have to fly that day
صبح است، بله، باید آن روز
to Vegas to jump off the stratosphere
به وگاس پرواز کنم تا از استراتوسفر بپرم،
yeah all I need is a little bit of a
بله، تنها چیزی که نیاز دارم کمی
buzz to get myself on this [\h__\h] plane
سر و صدا است تا خودم را سوار این هواپیمای لعنتی کنم.
yeah I have anxiety going through my
بله، من در سر لعنتی ام اضطراب دارم،
[\h__\h] head because I'm jump I'm gonna
زیرا دارم می پرم،
be the first person to jump off
اولین کسی خواهم بود که از استراتوسفر می پرم
and so I'm drinking an IPA out of a
و بنابراین ساعت شش صبح از یک غرغرو در وان حمام یک IPA می نوشم
and it just didn't sit right and I threw
و درست نشد.  درست ننشین و من
it up and I was off ipas for like 10
آن را پرت کردم و تقریباً 10
[\h__\h] years yeah I didn't have another
سال لعنتی از IPA استفاده نکردم، آره، من
IPA until I was like 46 because I was
تا 46 سالگی IPA دیگری نداشتم، زیرا فکر می کردم
like all I could think about was
تمام چیزی که می توانستم به آن فکر کنم
throwing up that IPA in a bathtub in a
پرتاب کردن IPA در وان حمام بود.
shower and being like I'm gonna throw up
دوش گرفتن و
thinking about it but yeah I don't I
فکر کردن به آن مثل اینکه دارم از خواب بیدار می شوم، اما بله، من
didn't [\h__\h] with IPS for a while and
مدتی با IPS ایراد نمی گرفتم و
then during the pandemic I got it I got
سپس در طول همه گیری آن را گرفتم،
back into ipas I was that way with Jack
دوباره وارد ipas شدم، با جک همینطور بودم
and Coke Jack Daniels and Coke really
و  جک دنیلز و کوکاکولا
got so drunk many many years ago that
سال ها پیش واقعاً آنقدر مست شده بودند که
just couldn't look at it I can't touch I
نمی توانستم به آن نگاه کنم، نمی توانم لمسش کنم،
can't touch uh uh what's Janice Joplin's
نمی توانم لمس کنم اوه اوه نوشیدنی جانیس جاپلین چیست Southern
drink Southern Comfort I can't say
Comfort نمی توانم بگویم ساترن
Southern Comfort he just drink it
کامفورت او فقط آن را می نوشد
straight uh well it was Southern
راستی خب،
Conference is at 40 that's hard no it's
کنفرانس جنوبی در 40 بود که سخت است، نه
almost like a liqueur honestly it's
تقریباً شبیه لیکور است، راستش
really sweet yeah Jack Jack double Jack
واقعاً شیرین است، بله جک جک دو جک
on the Rocks lots of rocks yeah I mean I
روی راک‌های فراوان، بله، منظورم این است
had a quote that I got a video that went
که من نقل قولی داشتم که ویدیویی
viral about I'll never quit drinking
در مورد من منتشر شد.  هرگز نوشیدن را ترک نمی‌کنم،
yeah and uh I have not gotten on a plane
بله، و اوه،
since that without having a flight
از آن زمان بدون داشتن
attendant not even ask what I want walk
مهماندار، سوار هواپیما نشده‌ام، حتی نپرسیدم که چه می‌خواهم
up with a double Jack on the Rocks lots
با یک جک دوتایی روی سنگ‌های زیاد راه بروم،
of rocks I mean it happens so on times I
منظورم این است که این اتفاق می‌افتد، بنابراین گاهی اوقات من
don't want to drink yeah I flew to
نمی‌خواهم.  نمی‌خواهم بنوشم بله،
Austin the other day I was like I'm not
روز پیش به آستین پرواز کردم، انگار
drinking on the plane because I felt
در هواپیما مشروب نمی‌خورم، چون احساس
sick yeah and man he walked up and he
بیماری می‌کردم، آره، او بلند شد و
goes double Jack in the Rocks lots of
دوبار جک در راک‌ها رفت.
rocks I was like [\h__\h] you know it yeah
بله
but yeah that's that's my drink uh
اما بله این نوشیدنی من است اوه اوه
uh wait what's your drink I thought
صبر کنید نوشیدنی شما چیست من فکر کردم که
you'd be a vodka guy
شما یک مرد ودکا خواهید بود
well uh vodka I associate with a lot of
خوب اوه ودکا من با
moments in my life of happiness because
لحظات زیادی در زندگی شاد همراه هستم زیرا
vodka is associated with shots and
ودکا با شات و رفاقت همراه است
and there's Eastern Europe in general a
و اروپای شرقی وجود دارد  به طور کلی
bunch of guys get together
تعدادی از پسرها دور هم جمع می شوند
and you celebrate life intensely yeah
و شما زندگی را به شدت جشن می گیرید، بله،
people fight people just feel people
مردم دعوا می کنند، مردم فقط احساس می کنند که مردم
experience life in a deep way just get
زندگی را عمیقاً تجربه می کنند، فقط
too drunk for for like for a reason but
به دلایلی بیش از حد مست می شوند، اما
I don't see that as like drinking
من این را مانند نوشیدن مشروب نمی بینم.
drinking that's like a a journey towards
سفر به سمت
a destination it's like uh to me
مقصدی برای من
drinking is like whiskey neat
مثل نوشیدن ویسکی تمیز است
or beer like you said ice cold beer yeah
یا آبجو مثل آبجوی سرد یخی، بله،
there's that afternoon beer like for a
آن آبجوی بعد از ظهر وجود دارد که برای
person like me who's extremely
فردی مثل من که بسیار
regimented and disciplined sometimes
منظم و منظم است، گاهی اوقات
you'll get the situation I just remember
شما به این وضعیت دست می یابید، فقط یادم می آید منظورم است.
I mean just I remember uh there's a bar
فقط یادم می آید اوه یک بار
at MIT where I just remember in the
در MIT وجود دارد که در آن
afternoon it was like a business meeting
بعدازظهر مثل یک جلسه کاری بود که
I sat down we just started with a beer
نشسته بودم و تازه با یک آبجو شروع کرده بودیم
and they're like really crisply cold uh
و آنها مثل خیلی سرد هستند،
some kind of lager and then just one
نوعی لیگر و سپس فقط یک
beer and two beers and all of a sudden
آبجو و  دو تا آبجو و یکدفعه می
you say [\h__\h] it let's just the rest of
گویی لعنت به آن بیا فقط بقیه
the day this is what this is and you
روز همین است و
said uh bright like you just life and
گفتی اوه مثل تو روشن است فقط زندگی و
nature is beautiful out there and you
طبیعت آنجا زیباست و
just said [\h__\h] it to all the meetings
فقط گفتی لعنت به آن به همه جلسات
[\h__\h] it to everything else just the
فک کن  به هر چیز دیگری فقط
camaraderie the the just talking about
رفاقت حرف زدن از
life being silly being you know all of
زندگی احمقانه بودن، می‌دانی که همه آنها می‌بینند که داری
something I'll never get because I'm not
چیزی را توصیف می‌کنی که من هرگز به دست نمی‌آورم، زیرا من رژیم ندارم، دوست
I would love I would love
دارم دوست دارم دوست دارم
I would love I only for the moment that
فقط من دوست دارم  برای لحظه ای که به آن دست می یابید
precious little Angel's breath that
با ارزش ترین نفس فرشته کوچولویی را می گیرید که
anyone's gonna get because you live this
هر کسی می تواند بگیرد، زیرا شما در این
life that's dialed in and it's scheduled
زندگی زندگی می کنید که شماره گیری شده و برنامه ریزی شده است
and so when you say [\h__\h] it it's like
و بنابراین وقتی می گویید لعنت به آن،
that's like me doing coke like it's like
مثل این است که من دارم کوکا می کنم، مثل این است که
oh [\h__\h] it like and you can just do that
اوه لعنتی  دوست دارم و شما فقط می توانید این کار را
with beer that is [\h__\h] amazing I
با آبجو انجام دهید که لعنتی شگفت انگیز است من
would love to live a regimented life
دوست دارم یک زندگی منظم داشته باشم
just to get the chance to go
فقط برای اینکه شانس رفتن را داشته باشم
hey guys I'm not performing surgery
هی بچه ها من امروز عمل جراحی انجام نمی دهم
hey guys yeah this this Bus full of kids
لعنت به بچه ها این اتوبوس پر از بچه است
kids gotta It's gotta drive itself home
باید خودش را به خانه برسانم
[\h__\h] it I couldn't even I couldn't even
لعنت به آن من حتی نمی‌توانستم به
tell you you know what's so interesting
تو بگویم می‌دانی چه چیز جالبی
about
در مورد
me and you was like yeah you know I'm a
من است و تو مثل این بودی که آره می‌دانی که من
fan of yours I couldn't even I don't
از طرفداران تو هستم، حتی نمی‌توانم
really know what AI is
واقعاً می‌دانم که هوش مصنوعی
like other than like dildos or ar right
چگونه است به غیر از دیلدوها یا درست
like if it has some Electronics in it
مثل اینکه اگر مقداری الکترونیک در آن باشد.
take over [\h__\h] mankind just well they
خوب آنها
start with these the [\h__\h] womanizer
با این زن زنی لعنتی شروع می کنند
that knows how to eat a [\h__\h] and then
که بلد است بیدمشک بخورد و بعد
they're like we don't need men anymore
انگار دیگر به مرد نیاز نداریم
but like it's so interesting that I
اما آنقدر جالب است که
couldn't even like I can barely tell you
حتی نمی توانم دوست داشته باشم به سختی می توانم به شما بگویم
what my dad does for a living he's a
پدرم چه می کند  برای امرار معاش او یک
lawyer I could kind of like he's called
وکیل است که می‌توانستم مثل اینکه او با من تماس گرفته است
me and said hey man you got to stop
و می‌گوید هی مرد، باید در
talking about what I do because you're
مورد کاری که من انجام می‌دهم حرف نزنید چون
not doing it right I go what do you mean
درست انجامش نمی‌دهید، من می‌روم یعنی
he's like that's not whatever you're
او اینطور نیست که شما می‌گویید.
saying I do I don't do
من انجام نمی‌دهم
and so but like I couldn't even begin to
و بنابراین، اما چون حتی نتوانستم
explain your job to my daughter
کار شما را به خوبی برای دخترم توضیح دهم،
well I think there's the way you do the
فکر می‌کنم راهی وجود دارد که شما کار را انجام می‌دهید، یعنی همان روشی است که
job which is the way you experience life
شما زندگی رژیمی را تجربه می‌کنید.  - پنج
nine-to-five job right you don't think
شغل درست است، شما فکر نمی کنید نه
you work nine to five no but I work much
تا پنج کار می کنید نه، اما من خیلی
more than that yeah but there's no
بیشتر از این کار می کنم، بله، اما
every kind of lifestyle has its
هیچ نوع سبک زندگی پیچیدگی های خود را ندارد.
every day do people tell you to pull it
آیا مردم به شما می گویند که آن را
back and they're like hey you're working
عقب بکشید و آنها مانند هی شما
too hard yeah a lot of people what I
بیش از حد سخت کار می کنید، بله بسیاری از مردم آنچه را که من
want in my life what I love in my life
در زندگی خود می خواهم آنچه را که در زندگی ام دوست دارم،
especially people close to me are the
به خصوص افراد نزدیک به من، کسانی هستند
ones that say work harder because
که می گویند سخت تر کار کنید زیرا
everybody how do you get them how do you
همه را چگونه به دست آورید چگونه آنها را بدست آورید
get them I don't have anyone in my life
من کسی را در زندگی من ندارم
that does that everybody's always
که این کار را انجام دهد که همه همیشه
worried about me I don't worry about me
نگران من هستند من نگران من نیستم
everyone's always worried about me the
همه همیشه نگران من هستند
only thing no one ever says if I showed
تنها چیزی که هیچ کس هرگز نمی گوید اگر من نشان دهم
you my DMs right now on my my text all
شما DM های من همین الان روی متن من همه
it is is like hey man I'm worried about
چیز مثل هی مرد من نگران
you yeah like Joe I I love Joe to death
تو هستم آره مثل جو من جو را تا حد مرگ دوست دارم
not once has he he always I don't know
نه یک بار او همیشه من نمی دانم
if you've seen the caring Joe eyes where
آیا شما چشم های مهربان جو را دیده اید یا نه  جایی
like I'm worried about you yeah where
که انگار من نگران تو هستم آره جایی که
it's like hmm
مثل هوم
and you're like yeah man don't do that
و تو مثل آره مرد این کار را نکن او
he's like I'm worried about you and
مثل من نگران تو هستم و
you're like don't [\h__\h] worry about me
تو مثل این هستی که نگران من نباش
I'm working it's I'm just working I love
من دارم کار می کنم  من فقط کار می کنم من عاشق
working I love what I do I love what I
کار هستم من عاشق کاری هستم که انجام می دهم من عاشق کاری هستم که
you do as much as I love what I do
انجام می دهم فقط می توانم تصور کنم که شما به همان اندازه که من کارهای من را انجام می دهم دوست دارید کاری که انجام می دهید را دوست داشته باشید
because that's all I ever want to think
زیرا این تنها چیزی است که من همیشه می خواهم به آن فکر کنم
about is all I ever want to talk about
تمام چیزی است که همیشه می خواهم  صحبت کردن در مورد
it's all I ever want to be like I I I I
آن تنها چیزی است که من همیشه می خواهم مثل من باشم،
when my wife wants me to take uh August
زمانی که همسرم از من می خواهد اوت
and whatever the August whatever the
و هر آگوست هر چه در
[\h__\h] September
سپتامبر لعنتی
no but like July and August off after we
نه، اما مثل جولای و آگوست تعطیل می شوند، بعد از اینکه ما
do fully loaded and
کاملاً بارگیری کردیم و
I was like no
من مثل نه
I was like what do you mean like so like
من بودم.  آیا منظورت این است که دوست
what I'll just am I like sit in a chair
دارم روی یک صندلی بنشینم
and stuff she's like no you can do like
و کارهایی که او انجام می دهد مثل این است که نه تو می توانی مانند
take up a hobby I go writing jokes I
یک سرگرمی
can't get on stage can I do sets in the
انجام دهم.
city because I'm not gonna [\h__\h] you
من تو را لعنتی نمی‌کنم، می‌خواهی
do you want me to like like I don't
دوست داشته باشم، من نمی‌فهمم چه چیزی را
understand what I don't understand
نمی‌فهمم
people who don't I don't understand
افرادی که نمی‌فهمند،
people who don't have to drive to work
افرادی را که مجبور نیستند همیشه با ماشین به سر کار بروند، نمی‌فهمم
all the time I don't understand that I
نمی فهمم که من به آن
envy it I envy it because I go I would
حسادت می کنم، به آن حسادت می کنم، زیرا می روم، دوست دارم
love to just be like I'm gonna play
اینطور باشم که قرار است
video games I can't play a video game
بازی های ویدیویی بازی کنم، اگر این کار را انجام می دادم نمی توانم یک بازی ویدیویی بازی کنم،
if I did I'd be on Twitch trying to make
در توییچ بودم و سعی می کردم
money like I love how do you find
مثل خودم پول در بیاورم.  دوست دارم چطور کسی را پیدا می کنی
someone who goes you need to work harder
که می رود، باید بیشتر کار کنی،
yeah especially when they see like I I
به خصوص وقتی می بیند که من
don't know what you look like but I I
نمی دانم چه شکلی هستی، اما من
look tormented when I'm working very
وقتی دارم خیلی سخت کار می کنم عذاب می کشم،
like it's easy to worry for my
مثل اینکه نگران شدن برای سلامتی من آسان است.  -اینطور
well-being it's not like I'm a
نیست که من یک
happy-go-lucky but I'm happy underneath
خوش شانس هستم، اما در زیر آن خوشحالم که
it am I working too hard is like on a
خیلی سخت کار می کنم، مثل این است که
plane every other day or every day
یک روز در میان در هواپیما یا هر روز از خواب
getting up at six working out and then
بیدار می شوم و در ساعت شش تمرین می کنم و سپس وارد می شوم.
going into like two in the morning or
صبح یا
one in the morning and then going to
یک بامداد و سپس به
sleep and then getting up at six working
خواب رفتن و سپس بیدار شدن ساعت شش برای ورزش کردن سوار
out getting on a plane going to another
هواپیما برای رفتن به مکان دیگری
like that's what my working is just a
مانند این چیزی است که کار من فقط
lot of travel in mind if I didn't drink
سفر زیادی را در ذهن دارم اگر
on planes I don't think anyone would
در هواپیما مشروب ننوشیدم.  فکر نمی‌کنم کسی
probably worry about me at all they'd be
اصلا نگران من باشد، آن‌ها می‌گویند
like no you're doing great but the
نه، تو عالی کار می‌کنی، اما
working out is there so I gotta ask you
کار وجود دارد، بنابراین باید از شما بپرسم
because you and I seem to have a similar
زیرا به نظر می‌رسد من و شما
relationship with running I like this
با دویدن رابطه مشابهی داریم، من این ایده را دوست دارم
idea of a slow treadmill I like running
از یک تردمیل آهسته دویدن
slow yeah
آهسته را دوست دارم بله می
you know like a 10 minute mile or
دانید مثل یک مایل 10 دقیقه ای یا
something like this so I'll just run
چیزی شبیه به این، بنابراین من فقط
forever just listen to an audiobook
برای همیشه می دوم فقط به یک کتاب صوتی گوش می دهم
listen to Brown noise think I love it
به نویز قهوه ای گوش کنید فکر کنید من آن را دوست دارم
what's brown noise it's actually
صدای قهوه ای در واقع
Brownian noise
صدای براونی است
um but short brown noise it's kind of
اما کوتاه  صدای قهوه‌ای شبیه
like white noise but deeper so it's just
نویز سفید است اما عمیق‌تر، بنابراین فقط
noise like
صدایی مانند
shh that oh wow it kind of sounds like a
هههه که اوه وای شبیه یک
waterfall just listen to it and
آبشار است فقط به آن گوش دهید و
something happens to me I think there's
اتفاقی برای من می‌افتد، فکر می‌کنم
you can ask Superman about this I don't
می‌توانید در این مورد از سوپرمن بپرسید،
but apparently there's some science it
اما ظاهرا  یک مقدار علمی وجود دارد که به
kind of focuses the mind and so on
نوعی ذهن را متمرکز می کند و غیره
it's funny because I think sometimes
خنده دار است زیرا من فکر می کنم گاهی اوقات
with people don't get about running is
افرادی که علاقه ای به دویدن ندارند این است که می روند سوار می شوند
they get on and they put it on like a
و آن را مانند یک
six right away on like a treadmill and
شش نفره فوراً مانند تردمیل می پوشند و
they go I can't do this for [\h__\h] 30
من می روند.  نمی توانی این کار را برای 30 دقیقه انجام دهم،
minutes but you can if you build
اما می توانی اگر
yourself up to your six
خودت را به 6 دقیقه برسانی و
and you play games I play games with
بازی کنی، من با
myself a lot like I'll play games where
خودم خیلی بازی می کنم، مثل اینکه هر جا می
um and I I can do this I can do this I
روم بازی می کنم و می توانم این کار را انجام دهم، می توانم این کار را انجام دهم.  من
can do this almost not all day long but
تقریباً نمی توانم این کار را در تمام طول روز انجام دهم، اما می
I can do this a lot longer like I did it
توانم این کار را خیلی طولانی تر انجام دهم، مانند
for two hours the other day before my
دو ساعت قبل از
workout or no hour and a half before my
تمرین یا بدون یک ساعت و نیم قبل از
workout where I started at 3.5 walking
تمرین، جایی که از 3.5 پیاده روی شروع کردم
and then I and then I get my jog up to
و سپس خودم و بعد.  من دویدنم را به
like a five and then I'm like 5.5 then I
پنج می‌رسانم و بعد به 5.5 می‌رسم، سپس می‌روم
go six and then I go and once I'm in a
شش و بعد می‌روم و وقتی در
six my body's really loose and so then
شش هستم بدنم واقعاً شل شده است و پس از آن
I'll go all right bring it down to a 3.5
خوب می‌روم آن را به یک پایین می‌آورم.  3.5
and then I go punch it to a 7.5 for a
و سپس من می روم آن را به 7.5 برای یک
quarter of a mile and then let's walk at
ربع مایل و سپس بیایید با
a four let's jog in a five right I can
یک چهار راه برویم، بیایید با پنج
let's I think and I love those like
بجنگیم.
where it's like it's
مثل
regimented running and sprinting at
دویدن و دویدن در
certain levels I love that and I love
سطوح مشخصی است که من عاشق آن هستم و همچنین دوست دارم
also when I work out to listen to music
زمانی که برای گوش دادن به موسیقی تمرین می‌کنم
but put on foreign language cooking
اما برنامه‌های آشپزی به زبان خارجی را
shows on Netflix
در نتفلیکس اجرا می‌کنم،
can you explain that they just put it on
می‌توانید توضیح دهید که آنها فقط آن را
mute you don't need to hear it for some
خاموش می‌کنند.  به دلایلی آن را بشنوید که
reason they're sexier the way they're
آنها جذاب تر هستند همانطور که به آنها
shot they're sexier yeah and it's like
شلیک می شود آنها جذاب تر هستند بله و مانند
street food Asia and they're just
غذای خیابانی آسیا است و آنها فقط به
watching them make street food in Asia
تماشای آنها در حال تهیه غذاهای خیابانی در آسیا هستند.
there's one called broth it's called
یکی به نام آبگوشت به نام
broth the nation of broth and they're
آبگوشت ملت آبگوشت و  آنها
just making broths and you're like [\h__\h]
فقط آبگوشت درست می کنند و شما مثل لعنتی هستید من
I want some broth so this is South
مقداری آبگوشت می خواهم پس این
America this is Asia South America Asia
آمریکای جنوبی است این آسیا است آمریکای جنوبی آسیا اوم
this one on pizzas that I've watched it
آنها یکی را روی پیتزا انجام می دهند.
there's like four episodes I've watched
اپیزودهایی که من
every episode so many times that my
هر قسمت را آنقدر تماشا کرده ام که
trainer goes God that's that [\h__\h] I
مربی من می رود خدایا این لعنتی است که
could watch that again yeah
می توانم دوباره آن را تماشا کنم آره ام
um I love watching foreign language
من عاشق تماشای
cooking shows on mute when I work out
برنامه های آشپزی زبان خارجی در حالت خاموش هستم وقتی تمرین می کنم در حالی که
while blasting music while Boston helps
موسیقی پخش می کنم در حالی که بوستون به شما کمک می کند
you Darren
دارن
all right well I usually run outside but
خیلی خوب است.  معمولاً بیرون می دوم، اوه،
I do oh I can't think I don't mind
نمی توانم فکر کنم که برای
hiking and I like I do like you know
پیاده روی مهم نیستم و دوست دارم می خواهم بدانی
what my fun thing the fun thing I would
چه چیز سرگرم کننده ای است، کار سرگرم کننده ای که
do and this is a this is ripped off
انجام می دهم و این یک چیزی است که
totally from cam Hanes is I like to go
کاملاً از بادامک Hanes is I حذف شده است.  دوست دارم بروم،
uh there's a great hike called Fryman
یک پیاده‌روی عالی به نام فریمن
Canyon out in the valley where I live
کانیون در دره‌ای که من زندگی می‌کنم وجود دارد.
Canyon and then I'm gonna jog back
سپس من می خواهم به عقب برگردم
and I wonder how long that is I think
و تعجب می کنم که چقدر طول می کشد، فکر می کنم به
don't think about it just know that
آن فکر نکن، فقط بدان که
that's your thing just know that that's
این چیز توست، فقط بدان که این
your thing and then all of a sudden
چیز توست و بعد ناگهان
you're like [\h__\h] that was eight miles
تو مانند یک چرندی می شوی که هشت مایل
you're like that's a [\h__\h] beast the
تو بود  مثل این که یک جانور لعنتی است،
hike doesn't even feel like anything the
پیاده‌روی حتی احساس نمی‌کند
hike once you do the jogs the hard part
پیاده‌روی وقتی دویدن را انجام می‌دهی، قسمت سخت
there the jog home is a [\h__\h] Cake
آنجا دویدن در خانه یک پیاده روی لعنتی با کیک است،
walk I had the best jog when I was in
من بهترین دویدن را زمانی که در صربستان بودم داشتم،
Serbia I had the best jog I think it was
بهترین دویدن را داشتم.  فکر کنم
in Hyde Park I think the name of the
در هاید پارک بود، فکر کنم اسم
park is Hyde Park
پارک هاید پارک است،
it was get this it was 80 percent
این را دریافت کنید، 80 درصد سراشیبی بود
wow so this jog you started the park and
وای، پس این دویدن، پارک را شروع کردید و
it was like and I'll do it like this for
اینطور بود و من این کار را برای شما انجام خواهم داد که
you you went like downhill like this
شما رفتید.  مثل این سراشیبی مثل این سراشیبی
downhill like this downhill like this
مثل این سرازیری مثل این
and then it was like a little steep
و بعد مثل شیب کمی تند بود
incline to get to the beginning of it so
تا به ابتدایش برسم پس
it was like a little like nice like
مثل کمردرد کمی خوب بود
lower back pain you're like okay okay
شما خوب هستید خوب
and then the jog was perfect and you did
و سپس دویدن عالی بود  و تو این کار را
four times it was four miles I loved it
چهار بار انجام دادی چهار مایل بود، من آن را دوست داشتم
my very first day I did it a butterfly
اولین روزی که انجامش دادم، یک پروانه
got in front of me it's like six in the
جلوی من آمد، مثل شش
morning yeah six in the morning and a
صبح، بله شش صبح و یک
butterfly got in front of me and it ran
پروانه جلوی من آمد و تمام آن را دوید.
the whole first Mile in front of me and
اول مایل در مقابل من و
I just it was like so surreal it would
من فقط آنقدر سورئال بود که
disappear and then it would show back up
ناپدید می شد و بعد دوباره
in front of me yeah you sure it was real
جلوی من ظاهر می شد، بله مطمئن هستید که واقعی بود
no definitely real and then the next day
نه قطعا واقعی و سپس روز بعد
and so I go I'm on the right path I'm on
و بنابراین من ادامه می دهم  مسیر درست من در
the right path the next day I go for a
مسیر درست هستم روز بعد
jog six in the morning and it rained and
شش صبح برای دویدن می روم و باران بارید و
as I'm doing this deep uphill incline a
همینطور که دارم این سربالایی عمیق را انجام می دهم
tree collapsed in front of me just went
درختی از جلوی من فرو ریخت و رفتم
and I went whoa a tree fell in the woods
و رفتم درختی  در جنگل افتادم
and I was here to see it shut the [\h__\h]
و من اینجا بودم تا آن را ببینم خفه شو
up I was like that's crazy and it didn't
من انگار دیوانه بودم و به
hit me like I'm on the right path and
من برخورد نکرد که در مسیر درستی هستم و
then I started getting overthinking it
بعد شروع کردم به فکر کردن بیش از حد به آن
like the next day I saw a condom and I
مانند روز بعد که یک کاندوم دیدم  و فکر می‌کردم
was like this is a good place to join I
اینجا جای خوبی برای پیوستن است، من
was like people [\h__\h] here last night
مثل این بودم که دیشب مردم اینجا لعنتی می‌کردند،
but but yeah that was one of the best
اما آره، این یکی از بهترین
jobs I've ever had I could do that I
کارهایی بود که تا به حال داشته‌ام که می‌توانستم انجام دهم که می‌توانستم
could run that Park every single day and
آن پارک را هر روز اداره کنم و
no one jogged that Park in Serbia I
هیچ‌کس دوید.  آن پارک در صربستان من
actually recently had a condom on my
واقعاً اخیراً یک کاندوم در آستانم داشتم
doorstep and I I wanted to ask whoever
و می‌خواستم از هر کسی که
is up there above what what that means
بالای سرم است بپرسم این چه معنایی دارد.
off UPS guy I I just was it compromised
فقط به خطر افتاده بود
what do you mean compromised like was
یعنی چی به خطر افتاده بود مثل اینکه
there stuff inside it oh I didn't look I
داخلش چیزهایی بود آه من نگاه نکردم
mean very few people put on the calendar
یعنی تعداد کمی از مردم تقویم را گذاشتند
and go it's not for me I'm gonna take it
و رفتند برای من نیست من آن را برمی دارم
off yeah it's a little tight it could be
بله کمی تنگ است ممکن است
to send a message like a horse's head
پیامی مانند سر اسب ارسال کنید،
kind of thing oh yeah I don't know I
اوه بله، من نمی دانم،
don't know what the message is exactly
نمی دانم دقیقاً چه پیامی دارد، آیا
do you use condoms if you had a one
اگر یک
night stand would you use a condom I
شب ایستاده بودید، از کاندوم استفاده می کنید، من
don't know what a condom is I didn't
نمی دانم.  کاندوم چیست من
never heard it I'm learning good I'm
هرگز آن را نشنیدم دارم خوب یاد می گیرم دارم
learning I've learned about sex from you
یاد می گیرم امروز در مورد رابطه جنسی از شما یاد گرفتم
today if my wife dies there's no condoms
اگر همسرم بمیرد
in my future I'll get it I don't care I
در آینده من کاندوم ندارم من آن را دریافت خواهم کرد مهم نیست من
have babies I don't give a [\h__\h]
بچه دار شدن من اصلاً
your Mana principle I like it uh Mark
اصل مانای شما را به درد نمی آورم من از آن خوشم می آید اوه مارک
Maron wrote something about your book
مارون
many many many ages ago life of the
چندین سال پیش چیزی در مورد کتاب
eloquently about you Brooke Chrysler is
شما نوشته است.  کرایسلر
one of the Great American Wild men
یکی از مردان وحشی بزرگ آمریکایی
a Gonzo Warrior driven not by cynicism
یک جنگجوی گونزو است که نه به دلیل بدبینی
or a desire to reveal dark truths but
یا میل به افشای حقایق تاریک بلکه
instead by a deep almost essential need
به دلیل نیاز عمیق تقریبا اساسی به گذراندن
to have a good time no matter what his
اوقات خوش صرف نظر از اینکه
stories track the trials and
داستان های او آزمایشات و
tribulations of a big-hearted dude
مصائب یک بزرگ را دنبال می کند.  دوست دلسوز که
trying to fit in help out and party and
سعی می کند کمک کند و مهمانی کند و
find himself after all is said and done
بعد از اینکه همه چیز گفته شد و انجام شد خودش را پیدا کند،
we arrive with him at the true humility
ما با او به فروتنی واقعی
of Joy so
شادی می رسیم، بنابراین
when was this desire for pure joy born
این میل به شادی خالص از چه زمانی
in you it seems like
در شما متولد شد، به نظر می رسد که
you are driven towards this
شما به سمت این شادی سوق داده شده اید،
yeah
بله  فکر می‌کنم
I think I arrived at it in college I
در دانشگاه به آن رسیده‌ام،
wasn't always the guy I am I was really
همیشه آن پسری که هستم نبودم، واقعاً
a serious pretty serious dude like when
یک شخص جدی و جدی بودم، مثل وقتی که
I got to college like dark brooding
به دانشگاه رسیدم، مثل آدم‌های تاریک،
serious yeah I wanted to be like I want
بله، می‌خواستم
to be like Eddie Vedder I wanted to be
مثل ادی ودر باشم.  من می خواستم
like a poet and a [\h__\h] lead singer
مثل یک شاعر و یک خواننده لعنتی باشم
and I wanted to be taken seriously and I
و می خواستم جدی گرفته شوم و می
wanted to be attractive and I wanted to
خواستم جذاب باشم و می خواستم
be you know like
باشم مثل من می خواستم
I wanted to be wanted by chicks and and
جوجه ها بخواهند و
respected by dudes and you know
مورد احترام آدم ها باشم و می دانید
and slowly but surely I think the bird I
و آرام آرام  اما مطمئناً فکر می‌کنم پرنده‌ای که من
really am chipped away at that and was
واقعاً از این بابت منحرف شده‌ام و
like hey man like I would say funny I
مانند هی مردی بود که می‌گفتم خنده‌دار بود،
would say funny things that would
چیزهای خنده‌داری می‌گفتم که
surprise me they were so funny meaning
مرا شگفت‌زده می‌کرد، آنها خیلی خنده‌دار بودند، به این معنا
like in my fraternity I'd say things
که در برادری من چیزهایی می‌گفتم
that were the funniest thing that I I go
که خنده‌دارترین بودند.  چیزی که من می روم
how did I think of that yeah and then
چگونه به آن فکر کردم بله و سپس
slowly I was like
آرام آرام اینطور شدم
and I remember as that as I chipped away
و یادم می آید که وقتی آن را کنار زدم
at that and as I got older
و وقتی بزرگتر شدم به
I would I would lean towards that we
سمت آن متمایل می شدم که به
would go on a bus trip to like Clemson
یک سفر اتوبوس می رویم به  مثل کلمسون
and I would get on the the the
و من سوار دستگاه
walkie-talkie on the bus and I would do
واکی تاکی اتوبوس می شدیم و
stand up for like an hour I just make
یک ساعت ایستاده بودم، فقط
jokes for an hour and I and I loved
یک ساعت شوخی می کردم و من و من عاشق
the impulse of like you know you get on
انگیزه هایی بودیم که می دانی سوار
the bus and everyone's like we're gonna
اتوبوس می شوی و  همه مثل این هستند که ما می‌خواهیم مشروب
drink and you get that one group of
بخوریم و شما آن یک گروه از
girls that was gonna drink and then to
دختران را دریافت می‌کنید که می‌خواستند بنوشند و سپس
break them and they're like oh [\h__\h] it
آنها را بشکنند و آنها مثل این هستند که اوه لعنتی
fine let's drink and then that to to
خوب است، بیایید بنوشیم و بعد آن را برای
watch that happen and I think
تماشای آن اتفاق بیفتیم و فکر می‌کنم
then once I and then when I went to
یک بار من و  سپس وقتی به
Russia this is so cliche for me to say
روسیه رفتم این برای من خیلی کلیشه ای است که بگویم،
but interacting with those young banditi
اما در تعامل با آن راهزنان جوان،
they were they were pretty serious dudes
آنها آدم های بسیار جدی بودند،
they didn't have like they were pretty
آنها نداشتند، مثل اینکه آدم های بسیار رواقی بودند
and when you could make them laugh it
و وقتی می توانستید آنها را بخندانید،
was like a real it was a real Joy the
مثل یک واقعی بود.  این یک شادی واقعی بود
silliest things I remember you know we
احمقانه ترین چیزهایی که به یاد می آورم شما می دانید که به ما می
were told
گفتند
there was a club it was called cafe or
یک باشگاه وجود دارد به نام کافه یا
Europa or maybe Cafe Americana there's
اروپا یا شاید کافه آمریکاییانا آنجا
where everyone really hung out like all
جایی است که همه واقعاً مانند همه
the the real dudes the real dudes
آدم های واقعی، آدم های واقعی
in St Petersburg
در سن پترزبورگ
and they had told us that like they told
و آنها در آن حضور داشتند.  به ما گفت که همانطور که
us in our class that uh Russian women
در کلاس ما به ما گفتند که اوه زنان روسی
didn't have tampons so they were like
تامپون نداشتند، بنابراین آنها مثل این بودند که
bring tampons to give to the Babushka
تامپون بیاورند تا به بابوشکا
the devotchka that ran the floor
دوتچکا را بدهند که
after all this time the fact that your
بعد از این همه مدت روی زمین دوید.
Russian sucks is awesome yeah if you
شما مدام
keep mispronouncing words horribly I
کلمات را به طرز وحشتناکی اشتباه تلفظ می کنید من به طرز وحشتناکی من
horribly I'm so [\h__\h] bad I am so bad
خیلی بد هستم.  خخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخخ که
the look on their face was so it was so
قیافه اونها اینقدر
pure joy I remember the first night I
شادی خالص بود من آمدم تو اتاق.  شب اولی را که
pulled out lemons and this is it sounds
لیموها را بیرون آوردم به خاطر بیاور و این به نظر می رسد که
it sounds make-believe now to say it
اکنون گفتن آن ساختگی به نظر می رسد
because it's been in the movie and yeah
زیرا در فیلم بوده است و بله
but I brought out lemons we were in
اما من لیموها را بیرون آوردم که در
lemon drops I vodka and lemons and sugar
قطره های لیمو بودیم، ودکا و لیمو و شکر
and a pocket knife and a fanny pack and
و یک چاقوی جیبی  و یک بسته فننی و
I put out lemons and and this guy Igor
من لیموها را بیرون آوردم و این مرد ایگور می
goes oh the machine runs on lemons like
رود آه ماشین روی لیموها کار می کند انگار
it was just so foreign that you would
آنقدر خارجی بود که
need lemon for them and so I I think and
برای آنها به لیمو نیاز خواهید داشت و بنابراین فکر می کنم و
I made friends with those guys like I
با آن بچه ها دوست شدم.
mean like friends whatever you can but
هر چیزی که می‌توانید، اما
like definitely me and that guy equal
قطعاً من و آن پسر را دوست دارید
legit friends legit friends like but
دوستان قانونی، دوستانی که دوست دارند، اما
from a place of Joy like green yeah it
از یک مکان شادی مانند سبز، بله،
was like it was like real seeing them
مثل این بود که واقعاً آنها را
light up and then I remember backpacking
روشن کنم و بعد یادم می‌آید که
through Europe after that and realizing
بعد از آن در اروپا کوله‌پشتی را پشت سر گذاشتم و فهمیدم که
I could bring a spark of fun to like a
می‌توانم بیاورم.  یک جرقه سرگرم کننده برای دوست داشتن
campfire and I had little tricks like I
آتش کمپ و من ترفندهای کوچکی داشتم مثل اینکه
learned all the currencies around the
همه ارزهای
world and so I I challenge people to a
دنیا را یاد گرفتم و بنابراین مردم را به یک
currency game I go let's go head to head
بازی ارزی دعوت می کنم.
currency and I'll name a country in the
یک کشور را به
currency and I would I would slow roll
ارز نام می‌برم و
them I'd just do all the dollars right
آن‌ها را آهسته می‌گردانم، فقط همه دلارها را درست انجام می‌دهم
the Chinese dollar the American dollar
دلار چین، دلار آمریکا، دلار
the Australian dollar I'd run through
استرالیا.
only know the dollars and then and then
دلارها را بدانم و بعد و بعد
I get started getting really deep I
شروع به عمیق شدن می‌کنم،
could make an event out of a night in in
می‌توانم یک رویداد از یک شب در
Europe I could make an event I remember
اروپا بسازم، می‌توانم رویدادی بسازم، یادم می‌آید
we were in uh Strasbourg and the bar was
ما در استراسبورگ بودیم و بار قرار بود
supposed to close but I had friends
بسته شود، اما دوستانی داشتم که
coming to the bar the train hadn't
به  بار قطار
gotten uh in in yet and I said
هنوز وارد نشده بود و من گفتم
I said don't close the bar I'll stand on
میله را نبند من روی
the bar and I'll entertain everyone in
میله می ایستم و همه را در
this room I'll dance I'll do whatever if
این اتاق سرگرم می کنم، می رقصم، هر کاری می کنم انجام می دهم
you just keep the bar open and the guy
فقط نوار را باز نگه دار و آن مرد می
goes if you can keep me laughing I'll
رود اگر می توانی مرا بخندان من
keep the bar open and I danced and and
بار را باز نگه می دارم و رقصیدم و
made this guy laugh on a bar for legit
باعث شدم این پسر به طور
I'm not even like a legit 30 minutes
قانونی روی میله بخندد.
until my friends walked in and they're
من
like what the [\h__\h] going on I had this
این توانایی را داشتم که
to without humility I didn't mind
بدون تواضع انجام دهم. بدم نمی آمد
looking like a fool and like doing and
شبیه یک احمق به نظر برسم و دوست نداشتم انجام دهم و در
there were really stupid jokes at the
آن زمان جوک های احمقانه ای وجود داشت،
time just very like base American frat
دقیقاً مانند
boy jokes but I didn't Sparkle when I
جوک های پسر بچه آمریکایی ساده، اما من  وقتی برگشتم برق نمی زد
came back I feel I feel like I learned
احساس می کنم یاد گرفتم
how to like to do that and do funny
چطور این کار را دوست داشته باشم و کارهای خنده دار انجام دهم
things that were like fun like I would
که مثل سرگرمی بود مثل اینکه ما
we go to a football game and I'd I
به یک بازی فوتبال می رفتیم و
brought a camera around with me a lot I
یک دوربین با خودم می آوردم.  خیلی
like to take pictures
دوست دارم عکس بگیرم
and I remember one of the jokes I'd go
و یادم می آید یکی از جوک هایی که می رفتم این بود که می
is I go hey everybody I told my parents
روم هی همه به پدر و مادرم گفتم
I have a lot of friends can you guys
دوستان زیادی دارم بچه ها می توانید
gather around and we'll take a picture
دور هم جمع شوید و ما یک عکس می گیریم
and so you know like 50 people would
و بنابراین می دانید 50  مردم
lead around like hey and like just the
مثل هی و
dumbest yeah silliest things and and
احمقانه‌ترین چیزها، بله، احمقانه‌ترین چیزها را به اطراف هدایت می‌کردند و و و
and and I don't and I wasn't a big
و من نمی‌کنم و من یک خودفروش بزرگ نبودم،
self-promoter so these would happen and
بنابراین اینها اتفاق می‌افتد و
I would just I was just doing them for
من فقط داشتم آنها را برای
me and my friends
من و دوستانم انجام می‌دادم.
I'd bring a guitar out and I just make
من یک گیتار بیرون میاورم و فقط
up songs and and uh
آهنگ میسازم و و اوه و
and and so I think in in watching this
و بنابراین فکر می کنم در تماشای
this serious bird get chipped away at
این پرنده جدی
until my like six and a half year of
تا شش و نیم سال
college where it was just this silly guy
تحصیلی ام در کالج که این مرد احمق بود از دستش دور می شود.
and then Rolling Stones written about me
سپس رولینگ استونز در مورد من نوشت
and I'm like and then I'm like well and
و من دوست دارم و پس از آن من خوب هستم و
I remember a couple serious Dads going
یادم می آید که چند بابا جدی می روند
yo you got a chance to turn this into
شما این شانس را دارید که این را به
something you need to go to you need to
چیزی تبدیل کنید که باید به آن بروید و باید
follow your dream and I try to stand up
رویای خود را دنبال کنید و من سعی می کنم
the first night and I was like I maybe
شب اول ایستادم و من فکر می‌کردم شاید
not wasn't the funniest guy but man they
بامزه‌ترین آدم نبودم، اما آن‌ها
laughed and we had a good time for 30
خندیدند و 30 دقیقه خوش گذراندیم
minutes and it worked and it was stream
و کار کرد و جریان هوشیاری بود
and I was like yeah and then of course
و من مثل اینکه بله و بعدش البته  می‌دانی
you know that same little path you take
که همان مسیر کوچکی که طی می‌کنی
gets convoluted in in New York because
در نیویورک پیچیده می‌شود، زیرا می‌خواهی
you want to be a serious comic and you
یک کمیک جدی باشی، می‌خواهی
want to be taken seriously and you want
جدی گرفته شوند، و می‌خواهی
to be edgy and you want to say the and
عصبانی باشی و می‌خواهی بگوییم و
then slowly but surely that you're the
سپس به آرامی اما مطمئناً
real bird chips away at it and he's like
پرنده واقعی از او دور می‌شود و او مثل
yeah man just [\h__\h] take your shirt
این است که مرد لعنتی پیراهنت را از تنت
off kill a beer yeah like [\h__\h] tell
در می‌آورد یک آبجو را بکش آره مثل لعنتی
the machine stories tell a story about
به ماشین بگو داستان‌ها داستانی درباره
your stupid kids like just you don't
بچه‌های احمقت بگو، مثل اینکه لازم نیست تو
need to be the [\h__\h] edgiest dude in
لعنتی‌ترین رفیق باشی
the room leave that to the good ones let
اتاق را به افراد خوب بسپارید به
let Bill and [\h__\h] Joe and Tom they're
بیل و جو لعنتی و تام اجازه دهید آنها همان کسانی هستند که
Comics they're I mean those are the
کمیک های گانگستری لعنتی قانونی هستند.
gangsters do what you do have fun make
گانگسترهای لعنتی کارهایی را انجام می دهند که شما لذت می برید
life fun and seize the day and [\h__\h]
زندگی را سرگرم کننده می کنند و روز را غنیمت می شمارند و لعنتی
try to bring a spark to people and let
سعی می کنند جرقه ای به مردم بیاورند و بگذارند
them forget about their [\h__\h] day
روز لعنتی خود را فراموش کنند
and the the interesting thing about
و چیز جالب در مورد
alcohol that I've I don't really like
الکل که من واقعاً از نوشیدن خوشم نمی آید
in terms of the actual physical like how
از نظر جسمی واقعی، مانند
it makes me feel but there's the the
احساسی که به من می دهد، اما
camaraderie that happens
رفاقتی که اتفاق می افتد وجود دارد، ای
I I wish there was another way to get
کاش راه دیگری برای رسیدن به آن وجود داشت،
there but I don't think there is that
اما فکر نمی کنم آن
Joy you get of just everybody getting
لذتی وجود داشته باشد که فقط از اینکه همه
together and taking shots or drinking
دور هم جمع می شوند و عکس می گیرند یا مشروب می خورند وجود دارد.
not the polite kind of drinking but just
نه آن نوع مودبانه نوشیدن، بلکه
everybody just
همه فقط لعنتی این نوشیدنی را می
the the [\h__\h] it kind of drinking yeah
نوشند، بله،
and when someone goes all right I'm in
و وقتی کسی خوب می رود، من
like that all right yeah that's the
اینطور هستم، بله، این
funnest and then especially when you
خنده دارترین است، و به خصوص وقتی
have a big group yeah and there's like a
گروه بزرگی دارید، بله و مانند یک
big group and like we were at the
گروه بزرگ و مثل اینکه ما در
premiere the other night and and uh and
اولین نمایش شب گذشته بودیم و و اوه و
I was working I was legit working I do
من کار می کردم، من قانونی کار می کردم،
I'm trying to sell the movie to outlets
سعی می کنم فیلم را به رسانه های
media Outlets and uh Boston with the boy
رسانه ای بفروشم و اوه بوستون با پسری
Boston with the boys my wife flew them
بوستون با پسرهایی که همسرم پرواز کرد  آنها
in to surprise me and they're over on
وارد شدند تا من را غافلگیر کنند و آنها روی
the red carpet and they're like yo this
فرش قرمز رفته اند و آنها مانند شما هستند این
the skull a beer let's kill a beer and I
جمجمه یک آبجو بیایید یک آبجو بکشیم و من
was like oh and then I'm like ah [\h__\h] it
مثل اوه بودم و بعد من مثل آه
I Don't Give A F this is what life's
لعنت به آن هستم.  این چیزی است که زندگی در
about and that moment where they're like
مورد آن است و آن لحظه ای که آنها انگار
yeah that's the funnest [\h__\h]
آره این خنده دارترین اتفاق است
especially when I can get Leanne to do
مخصوصاً وقتی که می توانم لیان را وادار کنم که
it when I get Leanne to get a drink and
این کار را انجام دهد وقتی که لیان را وادار به نوشیدن می کنم و
she'll and she's like
او می خواهد و او مثل این است که
like I wasn't supposed to drink last
من قرار نبود آخرین نوشیدنی را بنوشم.
night and she was like you want to just
شب و او انگار میخواهی فقط
we still have a glass of wine in the
یک لیوان شراب در
front yard and you're like oh my heart
جلوی حیاط داریم و تو مثل این هستی که آه قلبم
skips a beat I go glass one in the front
ضربانش را می زند، من می روم شیشه یکی در
yard are we gonna talk wild are we gonna
حیاط جلو، آیا ما می خواهیم وحشیانه صحبت کنیم، آیا می
say crazy [\h__\h] to each other like [\h__\h]
گوییم دیوانه  به همدیگر مثل لعنتی
yeah in the front yard front yard what
آره تو حیاط جلوی حیاط چیکار
are you doing in the front yard let the
میکنی تو حیاط جلوی حیاط جلوی حیاط جلو چیکار میکنی بذار
dogs play oh Big Trees in the front yard
سگ ها بازی کنن درخت های بزرگ جلوی حیاط جلو
in the Adirondacks on the front porch
در آدیرونداکس در ایوان جلو و
letting the dogs play letting the dogs
اجازه دادن به سگ ها بازی کردن و اجازه دادن به سگ ها
rest in the front yard maybe go over
در حیاط جلویی استراحت کنند  شاید برو
pick some cherries look at the [\h__\h]
گیلاس را انتخاب کن و به درختان لعنتی نگاه کن که
trees hear the wind going through the
باد را از
front yard and then you go to the
حیاط جلویی می شنوند و بعد به حیاط خلوت می روی،
backyard that's where the cigar comes
جایی که سیگار
out a little more privacy but yeah
بیرون می آید کمی حفظ حریم خصوصی بیشتر اما بله،
red wine Mall back
مرکز خرید شراب قرمز،
keep our sulfites low
سولفیت ما را کم نگه داریم،
yeah wine is a whole nother one too I
بله شراب یک  در کل من هم
feel sophisticated oh yeah I've went I
احساس پیچیده ای می کنم، بله، من رفتم،
traveled uh before Ukraine I went to
قبل از اوکراین به
Paris for the first time I drank wine
پاریس رفتم، برای اولین بار به پاریس رفتم و در آنجا شراب خوردم
there and I felt like
و احساس کردم که
I was uh a sophisticated man
یک مرد ماهر هستم، می
you know dude
دانید دوست
I didn't speak much French but you don't
من زیاد فرانسوی صحبت نمی کردم.  اما تو
need to you don't need to just start
نیازی به این نداری، لازم نیست فقط
smoking too just have a [\h__\h]
سیگار کشیدن را شروع کنی، فقط یک سیگار لعنتی بخور، می‌خواستم با
poetry duding Hemingway there's uh like
همینگوی شعر بنویسم، اوه مثل
a glass of wine in Italy and like uh
یک لیوان شراب در ایتالیا است و
like just out in like we went we went oh
مثل اینکه بیرون رفتیم  اوه
the most beautiful [\h__\h] day of my
زیباترین روز لعنتی زندگی من
just outside Florence
در خارج از فلورانس رفت،
they have all the Vineyards and stuff
آنها همه تاکستان ها و چیزهای دیگر را دارند
and we took a Vespa tour nice and uh and
و ما یک تور وسپا را خوب انجام دادیم و اوه،
it was [\h__\h] and Isla's too young to
لعنتی بود و ایلا برای
ride so she's on the back and now
سوار شدن خیلی جوان است، بنابراین او پشت سر است و حالا
everyone can drink there you know you're
همه می توانند آنجا بنوشند.  می دانی که
not supposed to drink and drive Vespas
قرار نیست وسپا بنوشی و رانندگی کنی،
but they don't they go a glass of wine
اما آن ها نمی روند، یک لیوان شراب چیزی نیست، آره
is nothing yeah and you're like okay
و تو خوب هستی، حدس می زنم
I guess I'll have a couple then if you
من یک زوج داشته باشم، اگر
think one's nothing then I think two's
فکر می کنی یکی چیزی نیست، پس فکر می کنم دوتا است.
nothing also so this is drunk Bert on a
هیچی هم پس این مست است برت روی
Vespa drunk not even drunk but just
وسپا مست نه حتی مست اما فقط
lightly lightly feathered yeah where
کمی پردار آره کجا و
and it's beautiful my wife hasn't been
زیباست همسرم مشروب نخورده
drinking Georgia has Georgia's too young
گرجستان دارد گرجستان خیلی
Isla is too young but I had at dinner we
جوان است ایسلا خیلی جوان است اما من شام خوردم ما
had a couple and we're going through
یک زن و شوهر داشتیم و  ما از
these Hills and it starts raining
این تپه ها می گذریم و باران شروع می شود
and it starts raining and I go
و باران شروع می شود و من می روم
Isla what are we missing and she goes
ایسلا چه چیزی را از دست می دهیم و او می رود
music big boy and I go what do you want
موسیقی پسر بزرگ و من می روم آنچه را که می خواهی
to hear and then she just starts going
بشنوی و بعد او شروع به رفتن می کند
I can't stop this feeling she's
من نمی توانم جلوی این را بگیرم  احساس می کنم که او دارد
screaming it and behind and then I hear
آن را فریاد می زند و پشت سر و سپس می شنوم که
George is screaming it and then Leanne's
جورج دارد آن را فریاد می
singing it and then Sandy and her two
زند و سپس لیان دارد آن را می خواند و سپس سندی و دو
daughters are singing it we're on these
دخترش دارند
Vespas and we're all singing it and and
آن را می
I and I swear to God if I hadn't been
خوانند.  اگر
lightly feathered I don't know if I
کمی پر نشده بودم، نمی‌دانم آیا
would have been like Idol what are we
می‌توانستم مثل بت بودم، چه چیزی را
missing because you know alcohol will
از دست می‌دهیم، زیرا می‌دانی که الکل
give you that thing like what's next
آن چیزی را به شما می‌دهد، مثلاً
what's bigger how do we take this to the
چه چیزی بزرگتر است، چگونه این را به
next level and then I got this little
سطح بعدی برسانیم و سپس من  این
girl who's still my little girl at that
دختر کوچولویی که هنوز دختر کوچولوی من است در آن
moment when she's singing sing it all
لحظه‌ای که دارد می‌خواند آن را می‌خواند و تمام
the good times aiming up so long yeah
اوقات خوب را هدف قرار می‌دهد، آره
give it up girl and then we stop at the
آن را رها کن دختر و سپس ما در
and we stop at the light and all of us
نور متوقف می‌شویم و در نور متوقف می‌شویم و همه ما
are looking and it's pouring rain
نگاه می‌کنیم و این  باران سیل آسا
don't do the feeling don't it is I mean
این احساس را انجام نده اینطور نیست منظورم این است که
I remember uh solving crying sobbing
یادم می آید حل کردن گریه گریه گریه گریه گریه
crying sobbing crying and then I was
گریه گریه کردن و بعد من
like let's get these [\h__\h] Vespers up
مثل این بودم که این شام لعنتی را بلند کنیم
and get to a Vineyard and then we went
و به یک تاکستان برسیم و سپس
to a Vineyard and the all the girls
به یک تاکستان و همه چیز رفتیم.  دخترها
tried a little wine no one got buzzed or
کمی شراب امتحان کردند، هیچ کس وزوز نکرد یا
anything but you're just sitting there
هیچ چیز دیگری، اما تو
with your family going like
با خانواده ات نشسته ای
[\h__\h] dude it and I'm not certain you get
و مطمئن نیستم که
that without a little bit of a little
بدون
bit but then a lot is also interesting I
مقدار کمی شراب را دریافت کنی، اما بعد از آن خیلی هم  جالب بود من
had uh a lot of whiskey with Rogan once
با روگان مقدار زیادی ویسکی خوردم، یک بار
I think I saw that yeah I think I saw
فکر می کنم دیدم که بله، فکر می کنم دیدم
that with Whitney too he was in the
که با ویتنی هم او در
push-up concert contest with uh David
مسابقه کنسرت پوش آپ با اوه دیوید بود،
got is the only time I met David Goggins
تنها زمانی بود که دیوید گوگینز را شخصا ملاقات کردم.
embarrassments of my life is uh trashed
شرمساری های بزرگ زندگی من از ذهنم پاک شده است،
out of my mind I'm trying to say how
سعی می کنم بگویم که چقدر
much of a fan I am and I could tell by
طرفدار هستم و از نگاه چشمانش می توانم بفهمم
the look in his eye that what is
که آنچه در
actually coming out of my mouth is not
واقع از دهان من بیرون می آید
good
خوب نیست.
it's not good and his wife is
خوب است و همسرش
embarrassed standing right there also
خجالت می کشد همان جا ایستاده است، همچنین
just everybody's embarrassed for me man
همه برای من خجالت می کشند مرد
I'm trying my best and then somehow I
من تمام تلاشم را می کنم و
find myself a minute later doing
بعد یک دقیقه متوجه می شوم که
push-ups with him as a challenge I
با او تمرینات فشاری به عنوان یک چالش انجام می دهم.
didn't it wasn't counting all I knew I'm
می‌دانستم
not stopping
توقف نمی‌کنم
and he was polite enough to stop I think
و او آنقدر مؤدب بود که متوقف شود، فکر می‌کنم
probably like 50 I don't know
احتمالاً مثل 50 سالگی، نمی‌دانم
there's a gift someone gives you when
هدیه‌ای وجود دارد که کسی به شما می‌دهد وقتی
they get drunk and they allow they get
مست می‌شوند و اجازه می‌دهند
drunk and they lower their guard and
مست شوند و گارد خود را پایین می‌آورند و به
they allow you to see them that way it's
شما اجازه می‌دهند.  آن‌ها را اینطور ببین، این
a gift it's a real gift it's just as
یک هدیه است، یک هدیه واقعی است، به همان اندازه
cool as like pulling someone's side and
جالب است که مثل کشیدن کنار کسی و
going yo I'm into anime like are you
رفتن به یو، من عاشق انیمه هستم، مثل اینکه آیا تو
cool with that and then they're going
با آن خوب هستی، و بعد آنها می‌روند
yeah oh yeah can I show you some cool
بله، بله، می‌توانم چند انیمه باحال به شما نشان دهم
anime and then you're like that's not my
و بعد تو انگار این چیز من نیست،
thing but it's like a cool thing it's
اما مثل یک چیز جالب است،
like sharing cool music with someone or
مثل به اشتراک گذاشتن موسیقی باحال با کسی یا
like telling them something about your
مثل این است که چیزی در مورد دوران کودکی خود به او بگوییم،
childhood when you when you get drunk
وقتی وقتی
like real drunk around someone
مثل مستی واقعی در اطراف کسی مست می‌شوی، به
you're giving them a gift yeah and that
او هدیه می‌دهی بله  و آن
gift is I want you to see me for
هدیه این است که من می خواهم مرا برای
everything I am yeah you're not going to
هر چیزی که هستم ببینی آره تو
get any lies you're not going to get any
هیچ دروغی نخواهی گرفت تو هیچ
[\h__\h] this is me at my absolute worst
مزخرفی نخواهی گرفت این من هستم در بدترین حالت من
I have a rule I will never never get mad
یک قانون دارم که هرگز عصبانی نخواهم شد
at someone for getting too [\h__\h] up
به کسی که بخاطر اینکه خیلی
because they're giving you a gift
بهت هدیه میده بهت
they're saying like yo I did this on
میگه من تصادفی این کارو کردم
accident but I trust you enough to let
اما اونقدر بهت اعتماد دارم که
you know that this is who I am and this
بفهمی من این هستم و این چیزیه که
is what you're getting I love it I love
تو میگیری من  دوستش دارم،
it especially when it comes to someone
مخصوصاً وقتی صحبت از کسی باشد که
you don't expect like you shut the [\h__\h]
انتظارش را نداری، مثل اینکه ببندی
up David gockins should have hugged you
لعنتی، دیوید گوکینز باید تو را در آغوش می گرفت
and said thanks for showing me this yeah
و می گفت متشکرم که این را به من نشان دادی، بله،
I guess that really you're right I
حدس می زنم واقعاً حق با شماست،
haven't thought of it that way there's
فکر نکرده بودم.  به این ترتیب
an intimacy to that because that is a
یک صمیمیت در آن وجود دارد زیرا این
gift of like fragility like this is me I
موهبتی از شکنندگی است مانند این من هستم
mean I'm I'm a very loving drunk but I'm
یعنی من یک مست هستم بسیار دوست داشتنی هستم اما من
boy am I a dumb drunk
پسر هستم آیا من یک مست
well dumb in terms of the eloquence of
خنگ هستم از نظر فصاحت
the words that are coming out of my
کلماتی که از دهانم بیرون می‌آیند
mouth so like you're just not stitching
طوری که انگار
words together correctly to make
کلمات را به درستی به هم نمی‌پیوندی تا
sentences no I turn into Hemingway Lost
جملات بسازید نه من تبدیل به همینگوی گمشده
in Translation like I'll start saying
در ترجمه می‌شوم مثل شروع به گفتن
random words but like translated to
کلمات تصادفی، اما مانند ترجمه به
Japanese and back to English it's not
ژاپنی و بازگشت به انگلیسی اینطور نیست
making any sense but there's love like I
منطقی است اما عشق وجود دارد، مثل اینکه من
think what you feel is this kind of
فکر می کنم آنچه شما احساس می کنید این نوع
desire to connect that I think I always
میل به برقراری ارتباط است که فکر می کنم همیشه
feel towards other people but when I'm
نسبت به دیگران احساس می کنم، اما وقتی
drunk I'm just say [\h__\h] it I don't need
مست هستم فقط می گویم لعنت به آن من نیازی
to be polite I'll just be loving fully
به مودب بودن ندارم.  "فقط به طور کامل دوست خواهم داشت
yeah yeah it's uh
بله بله، خیلی
it's cool when people let you see that
خوب است وقتی مردم به شما اجازه می دهند این را
in them because some people are really
در آنها ببینید زیرا برخی از افراد
like measured like not one drink and
واقعاً مانند یک نوشیدنی اندازه گیری می شوند و
then I'm done I don't want it no no no
بعد من تمام می کنم من آن را نمی خواهم نه نه نه
no and you're like show me a little more
نه و شما"  دوست دارم کمی بیشتر به من نشان بده
and then like it's cool and I never like
و بعد دوست دارم که این باحال است و من هرگز دوست ندارم
I love my favorite moments in the next
لحظات مورد علاقه ام را در صبح روز بعد دوست دارم،
morning when they're like did I make an
زمانی که آنها مثل این هستند که من
ass out of myself and you get to say not
از خودم دست و پا زدم و تو اصلاً نمی گویی
at all yeah not at all that's the
آره اصلا  این
coolest thing because some people bad
جالب‌ترین چیز است، زیرا برخی از افراد بد از
people will leverage that over yeah you
آن استفاده می‌کنند، بله،
can you see it's a bully tactic they'll
می‌توانید ببینید که این یک تاکتیک قلدرانه است، آنها از
leverage that the bad interactions I've
تعاملات بدی که من
had with in this business
با آنها در این تجارت داشتم
that we were talking about earlier
که قبلاً در مورد آن صحبت می‌کردیم استفاده می‌کنند، آنها
they were people that that when you got
افرادی بودند که وقتی  تو
[\h__\h] up they used it against you yeah
لعنتی شدی، آنها از آن علیه تو استفاده کردند، آره،
they held it over your head and they
آن را بالای سرت نگه داشتند و
said listen man
گفتند گوش کن،
I don't know what the [\h__\h] but if you
من نمی دانم چه لعنتی، اما اگر می
want and you're like hold on and then
خواهی و مثل این هستی که دست نگه دار و بعد
and then they made you they Gaslight you
و بعد مجبورت کردند که تو را گاز لایت کنند.
into thinking you're the only one that
به این فکر می کنم که تو تنها کسی هستی که
was [\h__\h] up and you're like okay I
گند شدی و خوب هستی، حدس می‌زنم می‌دانم
guess I know who you are now and I was
الان کی هستی و
like didn't you get [\h__\h] up a little
فکر می‌کنم که آیا تو هم کمی گند نشدی،
bit too yeah like I know we smoked weed
بله، مثل اینکه می‌دانم ما علف هرز می‌کشیدیم
and I thought we ate Xanax but like what
و من  فکر کردم زاناکس خوردیم اما می‌دانم که
about the I know I had a couple beers
من چند آبجو خوردم
but like I wasn't that [\h__\h] up
اما مثل اینکه من آنقدرها هم خوب نبودم
well Whitney's really good at that
ویتنی واقعاً در این کار خوب است
because she's the person I woke up next
زیرا او همان کسی است که صبح روز بعد از خواب بیدار شدم
morning and she just she said yeah yeah
و او فقط گفت بله بله
you're wonderful you're eloquent you're
شما هستید.  فوق العاده هستی تو خوش بیانی
great I I'm sure she was making that up
عالی هستی مطمئنم که اون داشت درست میکرد
completely it was funny I got blackout
کاملا خنده دار بود من
drunk at Whitney's roast of me like
از کباب ویتنی از من مست شدم مثل
black don't remember any of it and don't
مشکی هیچی یادم نمیاد و
remember any of it don't remember
هیچی یادم نمیاد  یادم می‌آید
speaking on the microphone I don't
با میکروفون صحبت می‌کردم، یادم نمی‌آید که
remember talking in the microphone
با میکروفون صحبت کرده‌ام
and and I I did the set apparently yeah
و من صحنه را انجام دادم ظاهراً آره
and I said to Whitney like in a real
و به ویتنی گفتم مثل یک
moment of vulnerability Whitney's like a
لحظه آسیب‌پذیری واقعی ویتنی
sister to me like a legit sister
برای من مثل یک خواهر است مثل یک خواهر قانونی که
my daughter's call her aunt Whitney
دخترم او را صدا می‌کند.  عمه ویتنی
Leanne shook his sister Leanne if she
لین خواهرش لیان را تکان داد اگر او
comes over to do a podcast with Neil
برای پخش پادکست با نیل بیاید
show up an hour early and sit with
یک ساعت زودتر حاضر شود و با
Leanne out in Leon's rose garden and
لیان بیرون در باغ گل رز لئون بنشیند و
just talk and Whitney I
فقط صحبت کند و ویتنی
I said the next day I called Whitney and
من گفتم روز بعد به ویتنی زنگ زدم و
I was getting on a plane
داشتم سوار می شدم.  هواپیما
and I was new I was hungover I said how
و من تازه وارد بودم خمار بودم گفتم
bad was I last night she goes you were
دیشب چقدر حالم بد بود اون میره تو
[\h__\h] fantastic and just didn't let me
فوق العاده بودی و نگذاشت
sit with it and then I watched the video
باهاش ​​بشینم و بعد ویدیو رو دیدم
and I was like oh I'm [\h__\h] out of
و انگار دارم از
control I was way out of control thank
کنترل خارج شدم لعنتی  من کاملاً خارج از کنترل بودم،
you for lying to me yeah so while being
ممنون که به من دروغ گفتی، بله، در حالی که
a wild out there comic she's also this
او یک کمیک وحشی است، همچنین
like caring and loving human being she's
مانند یک انسان دلسوز و دوست داشتنی است،
so interesting she is she is the most
او بسیار جالب است، او
nurturing
پرورش دهنده ترین
Sensibility
احساسات است.
out of nowhere just out of nowhere to
از هیچ جا فقط از هیچ جا برای
send Georgia gifts up to college it's
فرستادن هدایای جورجیا به کالج
just a gift box like she is just she
فقط یک جعبه هدیه است مثل او فقط
takes care of people that's her love
از مردم مراقبت می کند که زبان عشق او هستند
language and she's also the person that
و همچنین کسی است که
taught me what what the hell love
به من یاد داد زبان عشق جهنمی چه
language even means apparently there's a
معنایی دارد ظاهراً یک
book and there's like five of them oh
کتاب و پنج تا از آنها وجود دارد آه
you and Whitney I would love to sit in
شما و ویتنی من دوست دارم در
the [\h__\h] room and watch YouTube talk
اتاق لعنتی بنشینم و صحبت های یوتیوب را تماشا کنم بله
yeah she has a robot yeah it looks like
او یک ربات دارد بله شبیه
her
او است
and um
و اوم این
that's the future that robot I told her
آینده ای است که ربات به او گفتم
she should have that robot do porn
باید آن ربات را انجام دهد.  پورنو
unless someone [\h__\h] that robot and then
مگر اینکه کسی آن ربات را لعنت کند و بعد
if she wants but I go
اگر بخواهد می تواند چهره اش را جعلی کند، اما من می روم
promote it promote a special that way
آن را تبلیغ کنم به این صورت
like a full-on not like Showtime
مثل یک پورن نرم افزاری کامل نه مثل Showtime
softcore porn like full-on foreign full
پورن نرم افزاری مثل فیلم خارجی کامل
on like the dude like it's like hi
مثل شخص  مثل اینکه سلام
welcome inside you looked tired do you
خوش آمدید درونتان خسته به نظر می رسید آیا به
need a drink yeah oops I'm stuck in the
نوشیدنی نیاز دارید آره اوه من در
dryer you know what's the promotion
خشک کن گیر کرده ام می دانید چه تبلیغی است که به آن
you're most proud of that you've done
افتخار می کنید که انجام داده اید
without a doubt it's got to be what I
بدون شک باید همان چیزی باشد که من
took dance lessons yeah that was epic
رقصیدم  درس‌ها بله حماسی بود
because I tried to get Joe and Tom and
چون سعی کردم جو و تام و
Ari to do it for sober October I was
آری را برای اکتبر هوشیارانه انجام دهند. داشتم
reading for you and they said no she was
برای شما می‌خواندم و آنها می‌گفتند نه او
like absolutely not I knew Joe was gonna
کاملاً نه می‌دانستم جو قرار است
say no but Joe's a legit dancer like he
نه بگوید، اما جو یک رقصنده قانونی است که
can legit dance he took like dance
می‌تواند  رقص قانونی او مانند
lessons for a movie and is apparently an
درس های رقص برای یک فیلم است و ظاهراً یک
amazing dancer and so you're right he
رقصنده شگفت انگیز است و بنابراین شما درست می گویید او
could have said yes
می توانست بگوید بله
he could have said yes because I don't
می توانست بله بگوید زیرا من
remember listening to that podcast where
یادم نمی آید به آن پادکستی گوش کرده باشم که در آن
you really made the pitch yeah and I
شما واقعاً در آن بازی کرده اید بله و  من
said we all Take hip-hop dance lessons
گفتم همه ما در کلاس های رقص هیپ هاپ شرکت می کنیم، این کاردیو
and and those you do an hour dance loss
شما از پشت بام است.
against each other and we see who has
ببینید چه کسی
the best hip-hop dance it's different
بهترین رقص هیپ هاپ را دارد متفاوت
than the typical stuff we do it's fun
از کارهای معمولی است که ما انجام می دهیم سرگرم کننده است
and we can also work out we can do
و همچنین می توانیم تمرین کنیم که می توانیم
everything but like let's do hip-hop
همه کارها را انجام دهیم اما مثلاً بیایید رقص هیپ هاپ انجام دهیم
dance and Joe Adam Lee was like that's a
و جو آدام لی
horrible idea I will not do that and
ایده وحشتناکی است که من نمی خواهم  این کار را انجام بده و
then and then Tom and Ari just you know
بعد تام و آری فقط می دانی که
just whatever they were like yeah I
هر چه که بودند، بله، من
started with Joe we'll do something else
با جو شروع کردم، ما کار دیگری انجام خواهیم داد
and then I was like but I knew I liked
و بعد من دوست داشتم، اما می دانستم که
hip-hop dance and so I was like I'm
رقص هیپ هاپ را دوست دارم و بنابراین من اینطور بودم
Gonna Take hip-hop dance lessons anyway
به هر حال می‌خواهم دروس رقص هیپ‌هاپ را بگذرانم،
I'm gonna just do it over sub October
من فقط می‌خواهم آن را در ماه اکتبر انجام دهم
and I'm just gonna I'm gonna [\h__\h] do
و فقط می‌خواهم این کار را انجام دهم
it and then maybe maybe I'll do a
و بعد شاید یک
hip-hop dance video and then show it to
ویدیوی رقص هیپ‌هاپ بسازم و بعد آن را به او نشان دهم.
them and let them rape me and then we
آنها و اجازه دادند به من تجاوز کنند و سپس ما این کار را
did it
انجام دادیم
and I and it was twelve hundred dollars
و من و دوازده صد دلار بود
and I for hip-hop dance lessons for like
و من برای
a month or whatever for like a couple
یک ماه یا هر چیز دیگری برای چند
weeks
هفته دروس رقص هیپ هاپ
and then when we did it I thought you
و سپس وقتی این کار را انجام دادیم فکر کردم می
know what I bet we could put tour dates
دانید من چه هستم.  شرط می‌بندیم که می‌توانیم تاریخ‌های تور را
next to this because it's it was it
در کنار این قرار دهیم، زیرا به
turned out being like kind of good but
نظر می‌رسد که به نوعی خوب است اما به
kind of funny but we could put tour
نوعی خنده‌دار است، اما می‌توانیم
dates next to this and it was the
تاریخ‌های تور را در کنار این قرار دهیم و این
beginning of me figuring out the whole
آغازی بود که من متوجه شدم
like my promos were short and quick and
که کل تبلیغات من کوتاه بودند.  و سریع و
they were always like something silly
آنها همیشه مثل یک چیز احمقانه بودند
what's up guys it's your boy Brooke
بچه ها، پسر شما بروک
Chrysler
کرایسلر است
and then that one blew up and
و بعد آن یکی منفجر شد و
immediately I was announcing the tour
بلافاصله من تور را اعلام کردم
and immediately every tour date sold out
و بلافاصله هر تاریخ تور فروخته شد
and then every we added shows that day
و سپس هر برنامه ای که اضافه کردیم آن روز
we added shows and every one of those
برنامه ها را اضافه کردیم و هر  یکی از آن‌هایی که
sold out and I was like whoa and then
فروخته شد و من مثل او بودم و بعد
Tom was like the [\h__\h] was that and I was
تام مثل این بود که لعنتی بود و
I think I just sold out my whole [\h__\h]
من فکر می‌کردم تمام تور لعنتی‌ام را فروختم
and
و
and then Tom and then when Tom did his
بعد تام و بعد وقتی که تام
one like that and put his tour dates on
یکی از آن‌ها را انجام داد و تورش را گذاشت.  تاریخ‌های
it went over the top he sold all his
آن بالا رفت، او تمام تورهایش را فروخت
tours and and he was like whoa he's like
و مثل این بود که من
did I sold out every [\h__\h] show we've
همه برنامه‌های لعنتی را که
added shows I'm doing like an arena here
اضافه کرده‌ایم فروختم، نمایش‌هایی که من در اینجا مثل یک عرصه انجام می‌دهم
and this is before we were doing Arenas
و این قبل از اجرای Arenas
I was like shut the [\h__\h] up and that
من بود.  مثل خفه شو و این
changed my game where I was like all
بازی من را تغییر داد، جایی که من کاملاً
right so everything's got to be
خوب بودم، بنابراین همه چیز باید باشد، و
and then and then I was like I don't
بعد و بعد من
mind spending a little money and then
فکر نمی‌کردم کمی پول خرج کنم و بعد
the next one I did was the marching band
نفر بعدی که انجام دادم گروه راهپیمایی بود
and I was just like and but it was you
و من  درست مثل بود و اما این بود که می‌دانی
know it's real crazy I just said
واقعاً دیوانه‌کننده است، من فقط گفتم
can you guys get me a marching band and
بچه‌ها می‌توانید برای من یک گروه راهپیمایی تهیه کنید و
bucks I go cool and they're like what do
آنها مثل این بودند که بله مثل 2400 دلار است.
you want them to do and I go I don't
برو نمی
know we'll figure it out and they came
دانم متوجه می شویم و آنها آمدند
over and they had outfits and they were
و لباس هایی داشتند و
like so where did what do you want us to
اینطور بودند، پس کجا می خواهید چه آهنگی را
play what song do you guys know and then
پخش کنیم، بچه ها چه آهنگی را می شناسید و بعد
they didn't even know each other they
آنها حتی همدیگر را نمی شناختند.
were all hired people and they were like
همه آنها افراد استخدام شده بودند و مانند
rubber Band Man and I was like oh sure
مرد لاستیک باند بودند و من مثل اوه، مطمئناً بله،
yeah and then we just scripted it out I
و سپس ما فیلمنامه آن را منتشر کردیم،
was like all right I'll pretend it's a
مثل اینکه خوب است، وانمود می کنم که این یک
regular thing let's go wait so I'll walk
چیز عادی است، بیایید صبر کنیم تا
out and then I'll blow a whistle and
بیرون بروم و سپس  من یک سوت می زنم و
then you come out with the room
بعد شما با اتاق بیرون بیایید
and then and then we should we got like
و بعد و بعد باید مانند
two videos out of that and that sold out
دو ویدیو از آن و
dates and I was like [\h__\h]
تاریخ های فروخته شده دریافت کنیم و من مثل لعنتی بودم و بعد و بعد و بعد و بعد و
and then and then and then and then and
بعد و
then the real baller one the [\h__\h]
بعد واقعی  بالر یکی لعنتی
real one the real one was
واقعی یکی واقعی این بود که
I tore all the muscles in my arm going
من تمام عضلات بازویم را پاره کردم و وارد
into and do shooting the movie and I
فیلم شدم و
ripped all the tricep muscles off and
تمام عضلات سه سر را پاره کردم و
they were retracted so I'd go in for
آنها جمع شدند بنابراین برای جراحی بروم
and the anesthesiologist said to me
و متخصص بیهوشی گفت:  من
the night before he's like what music do
شب قبلش مثل اینکه
you want going in going under and I was
میخوای بری زیر چه موزیکی و من
like what he goes you can pick your
مثل اونی بودم که میره تو می تونی
music going under I said wait hold on
آهنگت رو انتخاب کنی زیرش گفتم صبر کن
what is it like he go I go is it like
چیه مثل اون برم من برم مثل
casual and he was like yeah
معمولی بود و اون مثل  بله،
I said I'm doing a promo read going
گفتم دارم تبلیغی انجام می‌دهم و می‌خوانم
under he goes what do you mean so I'll
او می‌گوید منظور شما چیست، پس
explain it to you tomorrow but I'm gonna
فردا آن را برای شما توضیح می‌دهم، اما
I'm not gonna count backwards I'm just
نمی‌خواهم برعکس بشمارم، فقط می‌خواهم
gonna do a promo read until I pass out
تبلیغی را بخوانم تا زمانی که من  از حال می رود
and my phone's gonna fall on the ground
و گوشی من روی زمین می افتد
all I need you to do is hit
تنها کاری که باید انجام دهید این است که
stop record
رکورد استاپ را بزنید
and
و
so they rolled me into surgery I had Red
بنابراین آنها مرا به عمل جراحی بردند.
the biggest venue I'd ever played in and
من تا به حال بازی می کردم و
I rolled in with my thing with CCR
من با وسایلم با CCR که
playing in the background and I just was
در پس زمینه بازی می کرد، غلت می زدم و
like as I lay here on this mat or on
انگار وقتی اینجا روی این تشک دراز کشیده بودم یا روی
this steel terrified as I go into
این فولاد دراز کشیده بودم، وقتی به
surgery I want you to know one thing I'm
عمل جراحی می روم وحشت داشتم، می خواهم یک چیز را بدانید که من  در
playing Red Rock September 10th and I
10 سپتامبر در حال نواختن رد راک بودم و من
started doing my promo read and he was
شروع به خواندن پروموی خود کردم و او می‌گوید
like yeah I go Jimmy Buffett's there the
بله می‌روم جیمی بافت
night before the night after he's like
شب قبل از شب آنجاست، بعد از اینکه
for real I go yeah you want to come he's
واقعاً من می‌روم آره تو می‌خواهی بیایی
like hell yeah he's like all right he's
او مثل جهنم است، بله او
like you're going under and he hits it I
مثل شما خوب است.  می رود زیر و او به آن ضربه می زند، من از آن
go through and I drop the phone
عبور می کنم و گوشی را رها می کنم و
woke up out of surgery and the first
از عمل جراحی بیدار می شوم و اولین
thing I said is where's my phone and he
چیزی که گفتم این است که گوشی من کجاست و او
goes you got it and Leanne's like I've
می گوید شما آن را گرفتید و لیان مثل اینکه من
already watched it it's good and I went
قبلاً آن را تماشا کرده ام خوب است و من
for real and so like that was a that was
واقعاً اتفاق افتاد و به همین ترتیب بود که خیلی بزرگ بود،
was a big one too yeah that was genius
خیلی هم بزرگ بود، بله، نابغه بود،
but that was the sort of opportunity
اما این یک نوع فرصت بود برای
kind of jumping on an idea have you ever
پرش به یک ایده آیا تا به حال
met Mr Beast Jimmy no
آقای هیولا جیمی را ملاقات کرده اید  نه،
so he he's I got to hang out with him
پس او اوست، من باید یک روز با او بنشینم
for uh a day and listen to him
و به او گوش دهم که
brainstorm with the team ideas yeah he
با ایده های تیمی طوفان فکری می کند، بله، او به نظر
kind of sounds like you but on steroids
شما شبیه است، اما در مورد استروئیدها
in terms of like
از نظر این که
first of all
اول از همه
willing to spend any amount of money on
مایل به خرج کردن هر مبلغی برای خرید است.
an idea like anything anything is
فکر می کنم هر چیزی
allowed anything is allowed I love that
مجاز است هر چیزی مجاز است من آن انرژی را دوست دارم
energy uh the only thing is no like
آه تنها چیزی که مانند
rated R stuff so he's really trying to
چیزهای R رتبه بندی شده نیست، بنابراین او واقعاً سعی می کند
go like
مانند
um for the broader audience for kids and
او برای مخاطبان گسترده تر برای بچه ها و
so on so that's the limitation so you
غیره رفتار کند، بنابراین این محدودیت است، بنابراین شما
can't do like most of the ideas that pop
نمی توانید انجام دهید  مانند بسیاری از ایده‌هایی که
into my head when anything's allowed
وقتی اجازه هر چیزی به ذهنم می‌رسد، به
it's kind of dark yeah but the point is
نوعی تاریک است، بله، اما نکته این است که
to really aggressively brainstorm every
هر
single day at the Whiteboard like what
روز در تخته سفید با طوفان فکری واقعاً تهاجمی فکر می‌کنم، مثلاً چه چیزی
and he does that for YouTube shorts too
و او این کار را برای فیلم‌های کوتاه یوتیوب نیز
for one minute videos really it's just
برای ویدیوهای یک دقیقه‌ای انجام می‌دهد، واقعاً درست مثل این است.
like really like what is the coolest
واقعاً دوست دارم جالب ترین
thing we could possibly do I love that I
کاری را که می توانیم انجام دهیم دوست دارم که من
love that energy and that energy most
آن انرژی را دوست دارم و آن انرژی که اکثر
people don't do that and they should
مردم این کار را نمی کنند و
basically YouTubers do that because
اساساً یوتیوبرها باید این کار را انجام دهند زیرا
they're obsessed about this particular
آنها در مورد این الگوریتم خاص یوتیوب و غیره وسواس وسواس دارند.
Jimmy is the best at that but like that
جیمی در این زمینه بهترین است، اما
can benefit you if you're a scientist if
اگر دانشمند هستید، اگر
you're a comedian if you're whatever
کمدین هستید، اگر همه چیز را
just go all out it's there's something
انجام دهید، این می تواند برای شما مفید باشد، این چیزی است که
really fun authentically fun about
واقعاً سرگرم کننده است که در آن
just coming up with a really stupid idea
ایده ای واقعا احمقانه به ذهن خطور می کند.
and just going let's see what happens
فقط برو ببینیم چه اتفاقی می‌افتد که چه اتفاقی می‌افتد،
who gives a [\h__\h] we've had those like I
ما کسانی را داشتیم که من
thought I could catch an arrow one time
فکر می‌کردم می‌توانم یک بار تیری بگیرم
and
و
yeah and my wife's like absolutely
آره و همسرم کاملاً
[\h__\h] not like I really think I can I
لعنتی می‌کند، نه مثل من واقعاً فکر می‌کنم می‌توانم
go let's just get really close shoot it
بروم، بیایید خیلی نزدیک به آن شلیک کنیم.
and then I'll see if I can catch it and
بعد می بینم که آیا می توانم آن را بگیرم و
she's like no that's not what you're
او می گوید نه این کاری نیست که تو انجام می دهی
doing and then my cousin's like hey we
و بعد پسر عموی من مانند هی ما
could cheat it to make you look like you
می توانیم آن را تقلب کنیم تا به نظر بیایید که شما
caught narrow and I went what he was
باریک شده اید و من رفتم همان چیزی که او
here just okay let's do it like this and
اینجا بود، باشه بیایید انجام دهیم  اینطور بود و
so we did it and it got sold a ton of
بنابراین ما آن را انجام دادیم و تعداد زیادی
tickets it looked like I really caught
بلیط فروخته شد، به نظر می رسید که من واقعاً
it everyone knows I didn't catch an
آن را گرفتم همه می دانند که من یک
arrow I mean for the movie we did a
فلش نگرفتم منظورم این است که برای فیلم ما یک
promo legendary was like you do all the
تبلیغ افسانه ای انجام دادیم مثل اینکه شما همه تبلیغات را انجام می دهید
promos and we did a promo and I thought
و  ما یک تبلیغی انجام دادیم و من فکر کردم که
I could slide out of my car like Tom
می توانم مانند تام
Cruise did
کروز
in a in a helicopter yeah and with
در هلیکوپتر و با
roller skates and get behind the car and
اسکیت های غلتکی از ماشینم بیرون بیایم و پشت ماشین بنشینم و
then skate behind the car and we just
سپس پشت ماشین اسکیت بزنم و ما فقط
ran over my foot and it was real and it
از روی پایم دویدیم و این واقعی بود  و
was scary but we just caught it all and
ترسناک بود اما ما فقط همه چیز را فهمیدیم و
in doing it my cousin's like give me the
در انجام آن پسر عموی من دوست دارد آن را به من
read and I'm like duh my movie comes out
بخواند و من انگار فیلم من در
Memorial Day Weekend uh I think we have
آخر هفته روز یادبود منتشر می شود اوه فکر می کنم باید
to go to the hospital and then we went
به بیمارستان برویم و سپس
to the hospital and I'm in the speedo
به بیمارستان رفتیم.  بیمارستان و من
with a helmet on one broken roller skate
با یک کلاه ایمنی روی یک اسکیت شکسته در سرعت هستم
and then
و بعد
and then that did really well and so
و بعد خیلی خوب انجام شد و
like I said the whole thing is just turn
همانطور که گفتم همه چیز این است که فقط دوربین را روشن کنید هرگز
the camera on you never know what's
نمی دانید چه اتفاقی
gonna [\h__\h] happen
می افتد
and don't be afraid to look stupid and
و نباشید  می ترسی احمق به نظر بیای و
all that kind of stuff just go all out
همه چیز از این قبیل فقط از بین رفتن
[\h__\h] ego's the death of Comedy like
نفس لعنتی مرگ کمدی است مثل
when you when you really give like
وقتی که وقتی واقعاً لایک می کنی
if it's hard to be the coolest guy in
اگر باحال ترین مرد در
the room and still want to be a comedian
اتاق باشی سخت است و هنوز هم می خواهی کمدین باشی
is just let yourself be whoever you are
فقط به خودت اجازه بده  هر که هستی باش
and you'll see the great ones they're
و بزرگ‌ها را می‌بینی که آن‌ها
like that they don't the you know
این‌طور هستند که نمی‌دانند
they're they're just regular [\h__\h]
آنها فقط آدم‌های لعنتی معمولی هستند
dudes and you get some real slick ones
و شما چند نفر ساده
like Dave Dave's probably might be the
مثل دیو دیو را می‌بینید که احتمالاً
coolest guy in the [\h__\h] room he might
باحال‌ترین آدم هستند.  در اتاق لعنتی ممکن است
really might be yeah but I think that's
واقعاً آره باشد، اما من فکر می‌کنم این
just who the [\h__\h] he is
لعنتی است که
who are the outside your close friend
بیرون از گروه دوستان صمیمی شما هستند
group who are the greats to you top five
که برای شما پنج نفر برتر
outside of my friend group so uh like
خارج از گروه دوستان من هستند، بنابراین
for me probably no McDonald's Mitch
برای من احتمالاً هیچ مک‌دونالد میچ نیست.
Hedberg
هدبرگ
George Carlin
جورج کارلین
Thompson Gore number one oh yeah no
تامپسون گور شماره یک اوه بله نه می
I wanted to say that it's an interesting
خواستم بگویم که این یک
pairing No Mitch Hedberg Dave Attell
جفت جالب است نه میچ هدبرگ دیو آتل
David Patel David everybody deeply
دیوید پاتل دیوید همه عمیقاً به
respects David more than even his comedy
دیوید بیشتر از حتی کمدی او احترام می گذارند.
Insomniac insomniac he's so good at just
فقط
the the natural comedy of human
کمدی طبیعی
interaction he's a brilliant comic he's
تعامل انسانی، او یک کمیک درخشان است، او
just a brilliant [\h__\h] mind
فقط یک ذهن لعنتی درخشان است
um Norm MacDonald's a [\h__\h] genius an
امم، نورم مک دونالد یک نابغه لعنتی، یک نابغه
absolute genius
مطلق است.
know and that's understanding that like
بدانید و این درک این است که مثل اینکه
I'm still friends with some of the best
من هنوز با برخی از بهترین های
in our generation but like just the way
نسل ما دوست هستم، اما نحوه
their brains work is really on the next
عملکرد مغز آنها واقعاً در سطح بعدی است،
level like you know those are guys Stan
مثل اینکه می دانید آنها پسرانی هستند استن
hope is the same way just [\h__\h] genius
امید همان روشی است که می
you know Rogan's to grow those are my
دانید نابغه لعنتی است.  روگان برای رشد،
friend group that's my really close
گروه دوستان من هستند که واقعاً
friend group but like those other guys
گروه دوستان صمیمی من هستند، اما مثل آن بچه های دیگری که
I'm friends with but they're not like
با آنها دوست هستم، اما آنها اینطور نیستند، بله،
yeah Louis CK bro Louis CK [\h__\h] he's
برادر لوئیس سی.کی.
start like forgetting the like people
آدم‌های مشابه
and then it's almost like people go oh
و بعد تقریباً مثل این است که مردم می‌روند، اوه،
so you didn't like that person you're
پس تو آن شخص را دوست نداشتی، تو
like no I [\h__\h] love that person yeah
مثل نه، من آن شخص را دوست دارم، آره،
I mean there's uh for me like Robin
منظورم این است که برای من مثل رابین
Williams which is a whole nother thing
ویلیامز وجود دارد که چیز دیگری است،
oh yeah Sarah Silverman uh [\h__\h] uh I
اوه، سارا سیلورمن، اوه  لعنتی اوه من
love Janine I mean I'm a [\h__\h] big
عاشق جانین هستم منظورم این است که من یک
Janine fan I love her brain Marin's
طرفدار پر و پا قرص جانین هستم، من عاشق مغزش هستم. مارین، لعنتی،
[\h__\h] hilarious you know uh Patton's
خنده دار است، می دانی اوه،
brilliant David Cross I mean there's
دیوید کراس درخشان پاتون، منظورم این است که
like it's you know it's really to ignore
شما می دانید که واقعاً باید
those guys and those guys were like the
آن بچه ها را نادیده بگیرید و آن بچه ها مانند
whole Forefront of the alternative
کل خط مقدم بودند  در
comedy front they're [\h__\h] amazing
بخش کمدی جایگزین، آنها فوق العاده هستند،
yeah and the people that have like Marin
بله، و افرادی که مانند مارین
or Joe that have podcasts is interesting
یا جو دارند که پادکست دارند جالب است.
gotten I've gone to Joe's Club a lot
من زیاد به کلاب جو رفته‌ام،
listen Joe and just that whole group of
جو گوش کن و فقط آن گروه از
comics do comedy and go to the same set
کمیک‌ها کمدی می‌کنند و
over and over and over and to see how it
بارها و بارها به یک مجموعه می‌روند و ببینم چطور
changes it's really cool it's the
تغییر می‌کند، واقعاً جالب است.
watch someone I could tell was really
کسی که می‌توانستم بگویم واقعاً
brilliant at it because you'd watch him
در این کار فوق‌العاده بود، زیرا شما او را
Tinker with a set yeah and he'd he'd
با یک مجموعه تماشا می‌کردید، بله، او
have an idea like hitting someone over
فکر می‌کرد مثل ضربه زدن به سر یک نفر
the head with a hammer from behind and
با یک چکش از پشت و
then he'd work it nine different ways
سپس آن را 9 متفاوت کار می‌کرد.  راه هایی که می
you know and you'd be like whoa so
دانی و می خواهی مانند اوهو پس چکش
you're the hitting hammer in the head is
در سرت باشد
the thing that he's working on
چیزی است که او روی آن کار می کند
I hope uh Eddie Murphy comes back
امیدوارم ادی مورفی برگردد
he's one of the greats Chris Rock Chris
او یکی از بزرگان کریس
Rock's [\h__\h] bring the pain is like
راک است.
the reason I got into comedy yeah
دلیل اینکه وارد کمدی شدم بله، آیا
do you have advice for Young Folks you
توصیه ای برای افراد جوان دارید، به
seem like a stellar example of a
نظر می رسد نمونه ای درخشان از یک
successful human being
انسان موفق
um or more seriously a very kind of
یا به طور جدی تر، یک نوع
non-linear life idea of advice for young
ایده زندگی غیرخطی از مشاوره برای
people in high school and college I
جوانان در دبیرستان و دانشگاه.
don't have a a good life they can be
زندگی خوبی ندارند که می توانند به آن
proud of don't worry too much
افتخار کنند،
about what you do when you get older
وقتی بزرگتر شدی زیاد نگران کارهایی که انجام می دهی نباش،
but when you do start worrying
اما وقتی شروع به نگرانی کردی
find the thing you love and it'll never
چیزی را که دوستش داری پیدا کن و هرگز به
to [\h__\h] I can't imagine what it must
نظر نمی رسد کار به لعنتی برسد.
feel like to be a lawyer and have to
وکیل بودن و مجبور به
read papers or whatever they do all day
خواندن مقالات یا هر کاری که در طول روز انجام می دهند باید چه حسی داشته باشد
and know that that's my day yeah I mean
و بداند که این روز من است، بله، منظورم این است که
if you find that thing you love to do
اگر آن کاری را که دوست دارید انجام دهید، باید احساسی را داشته باشم که مدرسه برای من چه احساسی دارد.
hard as [\h__\h] [\h__\h] every day and
هر روز بی‌دردسر و سخت کار می‌کنی و
you'll love every day of your life fine
هر روز از زندگی‌ات را دوست خواهی داشت
when you love and let it kill you
وقتی عاشق شوی و بگذار آن را بکشد
Bukowski said that for then that's the
بوکوفسکی می‌گوید پس این
[\h__\h] thing because that's what I'm
لعنتی است، زیرا این کاری است که
doing I'm gonna [\h__\h] take I'm I'm
من انجام می‌دهم.  می خواهم لعنتی بگیرم من دارم
[\h__\h] I'm I'm on that [\h__\h] bullet
لعنتی می شوم من در آن قطار گلوله لعنتی هستم که
train to [\h__\h] nowhere on this [\h__\h]
در این
comedy journey I love it I love it so
سفر کمدی لعنتی به جایی نمی رسم.
what is it however you put it he
او
basically you're not supposed to be uh
اساساً قرار نیست
end up in a well-preserved box you slide
در یک جعبه به خوبی حفظ شده باشی،
it in sideways smoke just beat up yeah
آن را در دود کناری می‌کشی، بله فقط
just just a giant mess I love I love
یک آشفتگی بزرگ
life that are like yeah man I'm breaking
است.  دارم آن را می‌شکنم،
it I'm breaking it down like a guy like
مثل آدم‌هایی مثل
Tony Hawk or Matt Hoffman who like yeah
تونی هاوک یا مت هافمن می‌شکنم که دوست دارند بله،
if I if I don't [\h__\h] break the [\h__\h]
اگر
out of this thing before I I'm then I'm
قبل از این که این کار را انجام ندهم، این کار را
not doing it right then again there's
انجام نمی‌دهم.  دوباره
also Churchill who tried to break the
چرچیل بود که سعی کرد این
thing and he couldn't lived into his 90s
چیز را بشکند و نتوانست تا دهه 90 خود زندگی کند،
a bad [\h__\h] just a bad
یک مادر لعنتی بد، فقط یک
[\h__\h]
مادر لعنتی بد،
so I guess the only hope we can have for
بنابراین حدس می‌زنم تنها امیدی که می‌توانیم برای
bird Chrysler is that you're going to be
پرنده کرایسلر داشته باشیم این است که شما
the Winston Churchill of Comedy my life
وینستون شوید.  چرچیل کمدی زندگی من
has lived perfectly
کاملاً زندگی کرده است
if I'm 95 years old and All My Friends
اگر من 95 ساله باشم و همه دوستان من
Are Dead yeah
مرده باشند بله
believe sagura 600 pounds and they had
آنها مانند
to carry him out in a crane out of that
آنها هستند.  بیرون با جرثقیل از آن
house
خانه
can you believe that it's just Burt
می توانی باور کنی که فقط برت
Chrysler and Joey Diaz laughing
کرایسلر و جوی دیاز
just standing there in October October
در اکتبر ایستاده اند و می خندند،
just the two of you left just laughing
فقط شما دو نفری فقط با خنده رفتید
October is just I'm 95 at the Mark Twain
اکتبر فقط من 95 ساله هستم در جوایز مارک تواین
Awards and they're like Bert Chrysler
و آنها هستند  مثل برت کرایسلر
still [\h__\h] here who saw that coming
که هنوز اینجا لعنتی می‌کند و می‌دید که آمد،
I hope so Bert I'm a huge fan of yours
امیدوارم برت من از طرفداران تو باشم،
it meant so much to me when you said
وقتی گفتی که می‌دانستی من
that you knew who I was like we were
کیستم، مثل اینکه داشتیم در
talking about it just it's so cool it's
موردش صحبت می‌کردیم،
so cool thank you for putting so much
خیلی برایم مهم بود.  ازت ممنونم که اینهمه
joy and love out there in the world I'm
شادی و عشق رو تو دنیا گذاشتی من
a huge fan and thank you for the love
طرفدار بزرگی هستم و ممنونم از عشقی که به
you've given me thank you man I am a
من دادی ممنون مرد من یکی از
huge fan of yours you keep doing you
طرفداران بزرگ تو هستم تو به انجامت ادامه بدی
I'll keep doing me and then let's see if
من به انجام دادن ادامه میدم  من و سپس بیایید ببینیم آیا می
we can meet in the middle sometime
توانیم
having cold beer in the afternoon love
بعدازظهر با آبجو سرد ملاقات کنیم یا نه.
let me leave you some words from Hunter
شما چند کلمه از زندگی Hunter
S Thompson
S Thompson
life should not be a journey to the
نباید سفری به
Grave with the intention of arriving
قبر با هدف رسیدن
safely in a pretty and well-preserved
سالم در بدنی زیبا و به خوبی حفظ شده باشد،
body but rather to Skid in broadside in
بلکه باید در
a cloud of smoke thoroughly used up
یک ابر دود که کاملاً
totally worn out and loudly proclaiming
فرسوده شده است و با صدای بلند اعلام می‌کند، باید به سمت قبر بروید.
wow what a ride
وای چه سواری
thank you for listening I hope to see
ممنون که گوش دادی امیدوارم
you next time
دفعه بعد ببینمت